<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>technology on TechnoStreet</title>
    <link>https://technostreet.github.io/categories/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in technology on TechnoStreet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 04:35:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://technostreet.github.io/categories/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Twitter API appears to be down, breaking Tweetbot and third-party clients</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-api-appears-to-be-down-breaking-tweetbot-and-third-party-clients/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 04:35:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-api-appears-to-be-down-breaking-tweetbot-and-third-party-clients/</guid>
      <description>Twitter API appears to be down, breaking Tweetbot and third-party clients The past several weeks since Elon Musk’s takeover have seen Twitter in turmoil as rapid changes hit the platform, and tonight it appears something is going on with the Twitter API as Tweetbot and many third-party Twitter clients are down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garena Free Fire Max Redeem Codes for January 10: Grab premium bundles, diamonds and more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/garena-free-fire-max-redeem-codes-for-january-10-grab-premium-bundles-dia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 05:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/garena-free-fire-max-redeem-codes-for-january-10-grab-premium-bundles-dia/</guid>
      <description>Garena Free Fire Max Redeem Codes for January 10: Grab premium bundles, diamonds and more The developers of the game are always incorporating new alphanumeric codes into it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Docs gets these new useful features: All the details</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-docs-gets-these-new-useful-features-all-the-details/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 05:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-docs-gets-these-new-useful-features-all-the-details/</guid>
      <description>Google Docs gets these new useful features: All the details The tech giant keeps adding new features to Docs and now two more features are soon arriving for users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iQoo 11 5G launch in India today at 12pm: How to watch live stream | Mint - Mint</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/iqoo-11-5g-launch-in-india-today-at-12pm-how-to-watch-live-stream-mint-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 05:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/iqoo-11-5g-launch-in-india-today-at-12pm-how-to-watch-live-stream-mint-/</guid>
      <description>iQoo 11 5G launch in India today at 12pm: How to watch live stream | Mint - Mint iQoo 11 5G launch in India today at 12pm: How to watch live stream | Mint MintiQOO 11 5G Launching in India Today: How to Watch Live Event Online, Expected Price in India, Specifications, MySmartPriceiQOO 11 5G Indian pricing tipped ahead of imminent launch, first sale date also leaked gizmochinaiQOO 11 India launch today: How to watch livestream, expected price and specifications India TodayView Full coverage on Google News</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter’s advanced search filters for iOS coming soon</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitters-advanced-search-filters-for-ios-coming-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 05:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitters-advanced-search-filters-for-ios-coming-soon/</guid>
      <description>Twitter’s advanced search filters for iOS coming soon According to social media analyst Matt Navarra, Twitter&#39;s advanced search filters for smartphone users are &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CES 2023: LG OLED TV Lineup With Dolby Vision, a9 AI Processor Gen 6 Launched</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ces-2023-lg-oled-tv-lineup-with-dolby-vision-a9-ai-processor-gen-6-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 06:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ces-2023-lg-oled-tv-lineup-with-dolby-vision-a9-ai-processor-gen-6-launch/</guid>
      <description>CES 2023: LG OLED TV Lineup With Dolby Vision, a9 AI Processor Gen 6 Launched LG has introduced its new lineup of premium OLED televisions at CES 2023 in Las Vegas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon पर धांसू कॉन्टेस्ट हुआ लाइव, घर बैठे आज जीत सकते हैं 1250 रुपये</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/amazon-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 06:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/amazon-/</guid>
      <description>Amazon पर धांसू कॉन्टेस्ट हुआ लाइव, घर बैठे आज जीत सकते हैं 1250 रुपये हम यहां आज के Amazon App Quiz के पांच सवालों और साथ ही उनके जवाब भी आपको बता रहे हैं, जिससे आप ढेरों इनाम जीत सकते हैं.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motorola ThinkPhone with carbon fiber style back panel to launch soon: Check renders</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/motorola-thinkphone-with-carbon-fiber-style-back-panel-to-launch-soon-chec/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 14:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/motorola-thinkphone-with-carbon-fiber-style-back-panel-to-launch-soon-chec/</guid>
      <description>Motorola ThinkPhone with carbon fiber style back panel to launch soon: Check renders Lenovo already has its ThinkPad lineup for businesses that offers an edge when it comes to security and hardware.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Pixel to get 5G support in India in Q1 2023: Report</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-pixel-to-get-5g-support-in-india-in-q1-2023-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 13:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-pixel-to-get-5g-support-in-india-in-q1-2023-report/</guid>
      <description>Google Pixel to get 5G support in India in Q1 2023: Report 5G connectivity arrived in India in October this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple iPhone&#39;s &#39;Find My&#39; feature helps locate car crash victim in US</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-iphones-find-my-feature-helps-locate-car-crash-victim-in-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 06:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-iphones-find-my-feature-helps-locate-car-crash-victim-in-us/</guid>
      <description>Apple iPhone&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Find My&amp;rsquo; feature helps locate car crash victim in US After following the smartphone&#39;s location, they found the car and called 911</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US House bans TikTok on mobiles over national security concerns</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/us-house-bans-tiktok-on-mobiles-over-national-security-concerns/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 05:42:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/us-house-bans-tiktok-on-mobiles-over-national-security-concerns/</guid>
      <description>US House bans TikTok on mobiles over national security concerns Washington, December 29 Chinese short-form video making app TikTok has been banned on mobile devices issued by the US House of Representatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung’s Galaxy S24 Ultra for 2024 will feature a new telephoto sensor</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsungs-galaxy-s24-ultra-for-2024-will-feature-a-new-telephoto-sensor/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 05:39:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsungs-galaxy-s24-ultra-for-2024-will-feature-a-new-telephoto-sensor/</guid>
      <description>Samsung’s Galaxy S24 Ultra for 2024 will feature a new telephoto sensor Samsung’s Galaxy S24 Ultra for 2024 will feature a new telephoto sensor</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google working on option to block insecure HTTP downloads in Chrome</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-working-on-option-to-block-insecure-http-downloads-in-chrome/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 05:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-working-on-option-to-block-insecure-http-downloads-in-chrome/</guid>
      <description>Google working on option to block insecure HTTP downloads in Chrome Hypertext transfer protocol secure (HTTPS), an extension of HTTP, has become very common across the web</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>आप फोन में सिर्फ 25 रुपये का रिचार्ज भी करवा सकते हैं, जानिए इसमें इंटरनेट के साथ क्या-क्या मिलता है</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-25-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 02:12:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-25-/</guid>
      <description>आप फोन में सिर्फ 25 रुपये का रिचार्ज भी करवा सकते हैं, जानिए इसमें इंटरनेट के साथ क्या-क्या मिलता है नए साल से पहले ही वोडाफोन-आइडिया (VI) ने अपने प्रीपेड पोर्टफोलियो में 2 नए प्लान ऐडउप किए हैं.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Twitter suppress Covid mismanagement by US govt ? Files make big revelation</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/did-twitter-suppress-covid-mismanagement-by-us-govt-files-make-big-revela/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 05:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/did-twitter-suppress-covid-mismanagement-by-us-govt-files-make-big-revela/</guid>
      <description>Did Twitter suppress Covid mismanagement by US govt ? Files make big revelation Shared in a series of tweets by David Zweig – a New York-based independent journalist and writer, the files show how top-executives rewrote the platform’s rules to accommodate their own political desires.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to book a Uber ride via WhatsApp: A step-by-step guide</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-book-a-uber-ride-via-whatsapp-a-step-by-step-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 04:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-book-a-uber-ride-via-whatsapp-a-step-by-step-guide/</guid>
      <description>How to book a Uber ride via WhatsApp: A step-by-step guide WhatsApp users will be able to manage their rides and receive the trip receipt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Year Ender: ये हैं साल के बेस्ट मोबाइल गेम्स, फ्री फायर और बैटलग्राउंड भी हैं शामिल</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/year-ender-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 05:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/year-ender-/</guid>
      <description>Year Ender: ये हैं साल के बेस्ट मोबाइल गेम्स, फ्री फायर और बैटलग्राउंड भी हैं शामिल Year Ender: आज हम आपको 2022 के बेस्ट ऑनलाइन गेम्स के बारे में बताने जा रहे हैं.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung के ये दो नए स्मार्टफोन्स हुए भारत में लॉन्च, कीमत 9,299 रुपये से शुरू, जानें फीचर्स</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 06:59:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-/</guid>
      <description>Samsung के ये दो नए स्मार्टफोन्स हुए भारत में लॉन्च, कीमत 9,299 रुपये से शुरू, जानें फीचर्स Samsung Galaxy A04 और Galaxy A04e को भारत में लॉन्च किया गया है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laptop vs Desktop: लैपटॉप लेना अच्छा है या डेस्कटॉप, कैसे करेंगे पता? यहां समझिये दोनों के नुकसान और फायदे</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/laptop-vs-desktop-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 07:35:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/laptop-vs-desktop-/</guid>
      <description>Laptop vs Desktop: लैपटॉप लेना अच्छा है या डेस्कटॉप, कैसे करेंगे पता?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Not Safer Under Elon Musk, Says Former Head of Trust and Safety</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-not-safer-under-elon-musk-says-former-head-of-trust-and-safety/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 02:37:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-not-safer-under-elon-musk-says-former-head-of-trust-and-safety/</guid>
      <description>Twitter Not Safer Under Elon Musk, Says Former Head of Trust and Safety Twitter&#39;s former head of trust and safety Yoel Roth on Tuesday said the social media company was not safer under new owner Elon Musk, warning in his first interview since resigning this month that the company no longer had enough staff for safety work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aadhaar-Mobile Link : सभी मोबाइल आधार से होंगे लिंक! ऐसे घर बैठे हो जाएगा काम</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/aadhaar-mobile-link-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 04:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/aadhaar-mobile-link-/</guid>
      <description>Aadhaar-Mobile Link : सभी मोबाइल आधार से होंगे लिंक! ऐसे घर बैठे हो जाएगा काम अगर आप आधार को मोबाइल नंबर से लिंक करना चाहते हैं, तो Online आधार से मोबाइल नंबर को लिंक किया जा सकता है। आइए जानते हैं इस बारे में विस्तार से.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotify expands audiobooks to more countries beyond US: Details here</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/spotify-expands-audiobooks-to-more-countries-beyond-us-details-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 05:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/spotify-expands-audiobooks-to-more-countries-beyond-us-details-here/</guid>
      <description>Spotify expands audiobooks to more countries beyond US: Details here Audiobooks shows up with a lock icon on the play button, indicating that users have to purchase it in order to listen</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google ने दिया धोखा! एक क्लिक में लुटी जिंदगीभर की कमाई, भूलकर भी न करें ये गलती</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 04:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-/</guid>
      <description>Google ने दिया धोखा! एक क्लिक में लुटी जिंदगीभर की कमाई, भूलकर भी न करें ये गलती Fake Fraud Online : अगर आप ऑनलाइन बैंक बैलेंस चेक करना चाहते हैं, तो आपके सतर्क रहना चाहिए वरना आपको बड़ा नुकसान उठाना पड़ सकता है।</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OnePlus का शानदार ऑफर, 17,000 रुपये से कम में खरीदें 55 इंच टीवी, लोग दबाकर कर रहे ऑर्डर</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oneplus-17000-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 06:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oneplus-17000-/</guid>
      <description>OnePlus का शानदार ऑफर, 17,000 रुपये से कम में खरीदें 55 इंच टीवी, लोग दबाकर कर रहे ऑर्डर OnePlus TV U1S Series 55 inch Smart TV : वनप्लस स्मार्ट टीवी की खरीद पर भारी डिस्काउंट दिया जा रहा है। आइए जानते हैं इसके बारे में विस्तार से.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZTE Launched 6G Key Technology Research and Registered for Related Patents</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/zte-launched-6g-key-technology-research-and-registered-for-related-patents/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 06:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/zte-launched-6g-key-technology-research-and-registered-for-related-patents/</guid>
      <description>ZTE Launched 6G Key Technology Research and Registered for Related Patents Chinese telecommunications firm ZTE announced that the firm tethers the utmost importance to research and development investments; as part of the process, the company ultimately joined forces to provide a place where we can connect with a 6G network from a sitting at the park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next Year’s iPhone 15 Ultra Could Cost More Than iPhone 14 Pro Max</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/next-years-iphone-15-ultra-could-cost-more-than-iphone-14-pro-max/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 08:27:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/next-years-iphone-15-ultra-could-cost-more-than-iphone-14-pro-max/</guid>
      <description>Next Year’s iPhone 15 Ultra Could Cost More Than iPhone 14 Pro Max Apple is going to make a slew of changes with next year&#39;s iPhone 15 series, which could see the arrival of a new Ultra variant that could push the price levels further.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musk Says Twitter to Soon Enable Organizations to Identify Their Associated Accounts</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/musk-says-twitter-to-soon-enable-organizations-to-identify-their-associated/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 03:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/musk-says-twitter-to-soon-enable-organizations-to-identify-their-associated/</guid>
      <description>Musk Says Twitter to Soon Enable Organizations to Identify Their Associated Accounts Twitter&#39;s billionaire owner Elon Musk on Sunday said that Twitter will soon enable organizations to identify twitter accounts associated with them as the new Twitter owner continues to find ways to limit fake accounts on the platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Quiz: सुबह-सुबह 2,500 रुपये जीतने का मौका, बस देना होगा इन 5 सवालों का सही जवाब</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/amazon-quiz-2500-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 03:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/amazon-quiz-2500-/</guid>
      <description>Amazon Quiz: सुबह-सुबह 2,500 रुपये जीतने का मौका, बस देना होगा इन 5 सवालों का सही जवाब Amazon Quiz: अगर आप इन 5 सवालों के सही जवाब देते हैं तो आपको रिवॉर्ड जीतने का मौका मिलता है। यहां हम आपको आज के 5 सवाल और उसके जवाब की जानकारी दे रहे हैं।</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Koo introduces four new features: Schedule Koos, save drafts and more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/koo-introduces-four-new-features-schedule-koos-save-drafts-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 15:21:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/koo-introduces-four-new-features-schedule-koos-save-drafts-and-more/</guid>
      <description>Koo introduces four new features: Schedule Koos, save drafts and more The Koo users can now save a Koo, upload up to 10 profile pictures, schedule Koos and save drafts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s How Much Apple Has Spent On Its SOS Emergency Satellite Feature For iPhones</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/heres-how-much-apple-has-spent-on-its-sos-emergency-satellite-feature-fo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 04:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/heres-how-much-apple-has-spent-on-its-sos-emergency-satellite-feature-fo/</guid>
      <description>Here’s How Much Apple Has Spent On Its SOS Emergency Satellite Feature For iPhones Apple introduced the new satellite connectivity feature on the iPhone 14 series, but the company has spent big to get this technology working.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Realme 10 review</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/realme-10-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 07:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/realme-10-review/</guid>
      <description>Realme 10 review gsmarena</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Realme 10 unveiled with Helio G99, 6.4&#34; 90Hz AMOLED display</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/realme-10-unveiled-with-helio-g99-64-90hz-amoled-display/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 07:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/realme-10-unveiled-with-helio-g99-64-90hz-amoled-display/</guid>
      <description>Realme 10 unveiled with Helio G99, 6.4&amp;quot; 90Hz AMOLED display The first of Realme’s 10-series phones is here and it places a focus on performance and efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A new PlayStation 5 ‘Slim’ model could be in the works, may feature tweaked design</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/a-new-playstation-5-slim-model-could-be-in-the-works-may-feature-twe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 06:50:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/a-new-playstation-5-slim-model-could-be-in-the-works-may-feature-twe/</guid>
      <description>A new PlayStation 5 ‘Slim’ model could be in the works, may feature tweaked design indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wear OS3: Older watch faces are affecting some users</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/wear-os3-older-watch-faces-are-affecting-some-users/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 04:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/wear-os3-older-watch-faces-are-affecting-some-users/</guid>
      <description>Wear OS3: Older watch faces are affecting some users Several Wear OS 3 smartwatch owners seemed to have discovered that the older watch faces don’t fully support the AOD feature on their wearables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail’s old design is going away forever: What that means for you</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gmails-old-design-is-going-away-forever-what-that-means-for-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 04:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gmails-old-design-is-going-away-forever-what-that-means-for-you/</guid>
      <description>Gmail’s old design is going away forever: What that means for you Google today announced that it is making the new Gmail interface standard for all users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple’s brain drain hinders efforts to pick its next Jony Ive</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apples-brain-drain-hinders-efforts-to-pick-its-next-jony-ive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 04:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apples-brain-drain-hinders-efforts-to-pick-its-next-jony-ive/</guid>
      <description>Apple’s brain drain hinders efforts to pick its next Jony Ive indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter will introduce ‘Official’ label for some high-profile verified accounts</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-will-introduce-official-label-for-some-high-profile-verified-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 03:50:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-will-introduce-official-label-for-some-high-profile-verified-/</guid>
      <description>Twitter will introduce ‘Official’ label for some high-profile verified accounts Billionaire Elon Musk’s social media platform Twitter will introduce an “Official” label for select verified accounts including major media outlets and governments when it launches its new $8 premium subscription product, its early stage products executive Esther Crawford said on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transforming industries: The human-first digital approach</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/transforming-industries-the-human-first-digital-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 03:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/transforming-industries-the-human-first-digital-approach/</guid>
      <description>Transforming industries: The human-first digital approach Customer experience is everything for a business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid work improves productivity and work-life balance, say employees: HP Study</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hybrid-work-improves-productivity-and-work-life-balance-say-employees-hp-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 03:42:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hybrid-work-improves-productivity-and-work-life-balance-say-employees-hp-/</guid>
      <description>Hybrid work improves productivity and work-life balance, say employees: HP Study HP Inc commissioned a global hybrid work survey that offers key insights into Indian employees’ workplace attitudes, career growth, and retention issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter roundup: Elon Musk ‘alone’ as he considers paywalling the whole platform; more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-roundup-elon-musk-alone-as-he-considers-paywalling-the-whole/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 13:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-roundup-elon-musk-alone-as-he-considers-paywalling-the-whole/</guid>
      <description>Twitter roundup: Elon Musk ‘alone’ as he considers paywalling the whole platform; more Another day, another Twitter roundup – ranging from an early investor describing Elon Musk as “alone and winging it” to the billionaire owner considering putting the entire Twitter platform behind a paywall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lyft forecasts operating profit above estimates, follows bigger rival Uber</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/lyft-forecasts-operating-profit-above-estimates-follows-bigger-rival-uber/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 13:52:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/lyft-forecasts-operating-profit-above-estimates-follows-bigger-rival-uber/</guid>
      <description>Lyft forecasts operating profit above estimates, follows bigger rival Uber Ride-hailing company Lyft Inc on Monday projected current-quarter operating profit above Wall Street estimates, helped by a resurgence in trips to airports and commutes to office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp starts rolling out rich text preview on iOS</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-starts-rolling-out-rich-text-preview-on-ios/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 13:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-starts-rolling-out-rich-text-preview-on-ios/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp starts rolling out rich text preview on iOS WhatsApp has been testing several new features on iOS and Android versions of its app as a part of its beta program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virgin Galactic Investors Can Continue Richard Branson Suit, Judge Rules</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/virgin-galactic-investors-can-continue-richard-branson-suit-judge-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 13:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/virgin-galactic-investors-can-continue-richard-branson-suit-judge-rules/</guid>
      <description>Virgin Galactic Investors Can Continue Richard Branson Suit, Judge Rules A New York federal judge ruled Richard Branson must face a shareholder suit alleging he concealed safety problems with Virgin Galactic Holdings Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily deals Nov. 8: $110 off Apple Watch Series 8, $89 1TB Samsung T7 Shield, $200 Lego Icons Boutique Hotel, more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/daily-deals-nov-8-110-off-apple-watch-series-8-89-1tb-samsung-t7-shiel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 13:47:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/daily-deals-nov-8-110-off-apple-watch-series-8-89-1tb-samsung-t7-shiel/</guid>
      <description>Daily deals Nov. 8: $110 off Apple Watch Series 8, $89 1TB Samsung T7 Shield, $200 Lego Icons Boutique Hotel, more Tuesday&#39;s best deals include an M2 MacBook Air for $1,599, 15% off Anker chargers, an $80 Belkin USB Type-C Docking Station, and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AirPods Pro 2 at $234 headline Monday’s best deals alongside M2 iPad Pro first discounts, more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/airpods-pro-2-at-234-headline-mondays-best-deals-alongside-m2-ipad-pro-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 16:48:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/airpods-pro-2-at-234-headline-mondays-best-deals-alongside-m2-ipad-pro-/</guid>
      <description>AirPods Pro 2 at $234 headline Monday’s best deals alongside M2 iPad Pro first discounts, more Kicking off the work week, all of today’s best deals are now live and headlined by a rare discount on Apple’s new AirPods Pro 2 at $234.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install Android 13 on a Samsung Galaxy device</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-install-android-13-on-a-samsung-galaxy-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 16:37:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-install-android-13-on-a-samsung-galaxy-device/</guid>
      <description>How to install Android 13 on a Samsung Galaxy device Android 13 is finally making its way to Samsung Galaxy devices en mass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter $8 Blue tick subscription coming soon to India</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-8-blue-tick-subscription-coming-soon-to-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 04:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-8-blue-tick-subscription-coming-soon-to-india/</guid>
      <description>Twitter $8 Blue tick subscription coming soon to India Twitter verification subscription is available in select countries for iOS users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA again gears up for Artemis Moon mission launch attempt</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nasa-again-gears-up-for-artemis-moon-mission-launch-attempt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 04:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nasa-again-gears-up-for-artemis-moon-mission-launch-attempt/</guid>
      <description>NASA again gears up for Artemis Moon mission launch attempt Washington, November 7 After several failed attempts, the US space agency is hopeful that on November 14, it will be able to finally launch the Artemis I Moon mission into space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After Google, Apple reportedly facing huge penalties in India: Here&#39;s why</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/after-google-apple-reportedly-facing-huge-penalties-in-india-heres-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 04:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/after-google-apple-reportedly-facing-huge-penalties-in-india-heres-why/</guid>
      <description>After Google, Apple reportedly facing huge penalties in India: Here&amp;rsquo;s why &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple to change the ‘Hey Siri’ voice assistant command to just ‘Siri’</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-to-change-the-hey-siri-voice-assistant-command-to-just-siri/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 04:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-to-change-the-hey-siri-voice-assistant-command-to-just-siri/</guid>
      <description>Apple to change the ‘Hey Siri’ voice assistant command to just ‘Siri’ Looks like Apple wants to change the “Hey Siri” trigger phrase to just “Siri”, according to a report from Bloomberg’s Mark Gurman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Several people move to Mastodon amid Twitter chaos; social media buzzes with memes</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/several-people-move-to-mastodon-amid-twitter-chaos-social-media-buzzes-wit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 12:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/several-people-move-to-mastodon-amid-twitter-chaos-social-media-buzzes-wit/</guid>
      <description>Several people move to Mastodon amid Twitter chaos; social media buzzes with memes It&#39;s a protocol on top of a product, much like Twitter ought to have been.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Former Twitter CEO apologizes to staff after massive layoffs</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/former-twitter-ceo-apologizes-to-staff-after-massive-layoffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 11:54:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/former-twitter-ceo-apologizes-to-staff-after-massive-layoffs/</guid>
      <description>Former Twitter CEO apologizes to staff after massive layoffs Twitter co-founder and former CEO Jack Dorsey on Saturday apologized to company staff for growing the social media giant &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter to roll out &#39;Blue Tick Subscription&#39; in THIS month in India; Check what Elon Musk said</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-to-roll-out-blue-tick-subscription-in-this-month-in-india-check-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 04:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-to-roll-out-blue-tick-subscription-in-this-month-in-india-check-/</guid>
      <description>Twitter to roll out &amp;lsquo;Blue Tick Subscription&amp;rsquo; in THIS month in India; Check what Elon Musk said According to a Twitter update, countries including the United States, Canada, Australia, New Zealand, and the United Kingdom would be allowed to use the new service with verification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk’s Twitter updates app to start charging $7.99 monthly for Twitter Blue</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musks-twitter-updates-app-to-start-charging-799-monthly-for-twitt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 04:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musks-twitter-updates-app-to-start-charging-799-monthly-for-twitt/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk’s Twitter updates app to start charging $7.99 monthly for Twitter Blue Twitter on Saturday updated its app in Apple’s App Store to begin charging $8 for sought-after blue check verification marks, in Elon Musk’s first major revision of the social media platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s when your Oppo smartphone is getting latest Android 13-based ColorOS 13</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/heres-when-your-oppo-smartphone-is-getting-latest-android-13-based-coloros/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 04:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/heres-when-your-oppo-smartphone-is-getting-latest-android-13-based-coloros/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s when your Oppo smartphone is getting latest Android 13-based ColorOS 13 Oppo has been releasing monthly updates on when its smartphone will get a stable or beta version of the ColorOS 13 skin based on Android 13.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>With Indian roots and aesthetics, DailyObjects now has a cover for smartphone growth story</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/with-indian-roots-and-aesthetics-dailyobjects-now-has-a-cover-for-smartpho/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 04:19:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/with-indian-roots-and-aesthetics-dailyobjects-now-has-a-cover-for-smartpho/</guid>
      <description>With Indian roots and aesthetics, DailyObjects now has a cover for smartphone growth story indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IND vs ZIM LIVE Cricket Score Streaming Update: When, Where to watch T20 WC match online</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ind-vs-zim-live-cricket-score-streaming-update-when-where-to-watch-t20-wc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 04:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ind-vs-zim-live-cricket-score-streaming-update-when-where-to-watch-t20-wc/</guid>
      <description>IND vs ZIM LIVE Cricket Score Streaming Update: When, Where to watch T20 WC match online The T20 World Cup match between India and Zimbabwe will be held today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stray Blade interview: &#34;button mashing will probably get you killed&#34;</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/stray-blade-interview-button-mashing-will-probably-get-you-killed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 13:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/stray-blade-interview-button-mashing-will-probably-get-you-killed/</guid>
      <description>Stray Blade interview: &amp;ldquo;button mashing will probably get you killed&amp;rdquo; We spoke to Point Blank Games about upcoming action-RPG Stray Blade</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD unveils Radeon RX 7900 XTX, RX 7900 XT, its most advanced graphic cards</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/amd-unveils-radeon-rx-7900-xtx-rx-7900-xt-its-most-advanced-graphic-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 13:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/amd-unveils-radeon-rx-7900-xtx-rx-7900-xt-its-most-advanced-graphic-cards/</guid>
      <description>AMD unveils Radeon RX 7900 XTX, RX 7900 XT, its most advanced graphic cards According to AMD, these graphics cards are the world’s gaming graphics cards to feature an advanced AMD chipset design and come with the latest AMD RFNA 3 architecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Unfortunately there is no choice&#39;: Elon Musk reacts to layoffs; says Twitter losing $4 million daily</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/unfortunately-there-is-no-choice-elon-musk-reacts-to-layoffs-says-twitt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 04:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/unfortunately-there-is-no-choice-elon-musk-reacts-to-layoffs-says-twitt/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;Unfortunately there is no choice&amp;rsquo;: Elon Musk reacts to layoffs; says Twitter losing $4 million daily Tesla CEO and Twitter owner Elon Musk today reacted to the layoffs happening at the micro-blogging site and said that there is no choice for him as the company is losing $4 million per day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New technology to reduce potholes</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-technology-to-reduce-potholes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 16:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-technology-to-reduce-potholes/</guid>
      <description>New technology to reduce potholes Researchers have developed new &#34;intelligent compaction&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roku&#39;s Streaming Stick 4K hits a new low of $25, plus the rest of the week&#39;s best tech deals</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rokus-streaming-stick-4k-hits-a-new-low-of-25-plus-the-rest-of-the-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 16:45:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rokus-streaming-stick-4k-hits-a-new-low-of-25-plus-the-rest-of-the-week/</guid>
      <description>Roku&amp;rsquo;s Streaming Stick 4K hits a new low of $25, plus the rest of the week&amp;rsquo;s best tech deals Black Friday doesn&#39;t officially arrive for a few more weeks, but we&#39;re already starting to see retailers run early holiday sales on several gadgets we recommend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Photos automatic Shared Albums: How to create and manage them for others</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-photos-automatic-shared-albums-how-to-create-and-manage-them-for-ot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 16:44:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-photos-automatic-shared-albums-how-to-create-and-manage-them-for-ot/</guid>
      <description>Google Photos automatic Shared Albums: How to create and manage them for others Sharing photos with others goes beyond sending them in messaging apps like Telegram.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Father of the iPod&#39; Tony Fadell joins Arm&#39;s board</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/father-of-the-ipod-tony-fadell-joins-arms-board/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 16:43:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/father-of-the-ipod-tony-fadell-joins-arms-board/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;Father of the iPod&amp;rsquo; Tony Fadell joins Arm&amp;rsquo;s board Nest and iPod co-designer Tony Fadell has joined the board of processor designer Arm, which works with Apple on the M- and iPhone A-series chips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung says Apple is likely to launch a foldable tablet by 2024</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-says-apple-is-likely-to-launch-a-foldable-tablet-by-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 07:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-says-apple-is-likely-to-launch-a-foldable-tablet-by-2024/</guid>
      <description>Samsung says Apple is likely to launch a foldable tablet by 2024 South Korean giant Samsung has predicted that its arch-rival Apple is set to launch a foldable tablet by 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung asks Apple fanboys to ?get off the fence!? Check out this funny advert</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-asks-apple-fanboys-to-get-off-the-fence-check-out-this-funny-adv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 07:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-asks-apple-fanboys-to-get-off-the-fence-check-out-this-funny-adv/</guid>
      <description>Samsung asks Apple fanboys to ?get off the fence!? Check out this funny advert Samsung has released a new advertisement teasing Apple for lack of innovation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oppo A98 With 6.7-Inch AMOLED Display Listed on TENAA, Specifications Leaked</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oppo-a98-with-67-inch-amoled-display-listed-on-tenaa-specifications-leake/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 07:13:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oppo-a98-with-67-inch-amoled-display-listed-on-tenaa-specifications-leake/</guid>
      <description>Oppo A98 With 6.7-Inch AMOLED Display Listed on TENAA, Specifications Leaked The Oppo A98 has surfaced on the TENAA database, which suggests its key specifications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wi-Fi flaw lets drone track your smart devices through walls: How it works</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/wi-fi-flaw-lets-drone-track-your-smart-devices-through-walls-how-it-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 04:41:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/wi-fi-flaw-lets-drone-track-your-smart-devices-through-walls-how-it-works/</guid>
      <description>Wi-Fi flaw lets drone track your smart devices through walls: How it works Wi-Fi is one of the most commonly used wireless standards that is used for connecting devices such as personal computers, tablets, smartphones, printers, smart TVs, smart home devices such as lights and speakers and smart home appliances such as washing machines, refrigerators and air conditioners with the internet in a small space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA’s Artemis 1 launch now set for November 14</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nasas-artemis-1-launch-now-set-for-november-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 04:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nasas-artemis-1-launch-now-set-for-november-14/</guid>
      <description>NASA’s Artemis 1 launch now set for November 14 indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bharat Electronics partners Motorola in broadband, push-to-talk service</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bharat-electronics-partners-motorola-in-broadband-push-to-talk-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 04:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bharat-electronics-partners-motorola-in-broadband-push-to-talk-service/</guid>
      <description>Bharat Electronics partners Motorola in broadband, push-to-talk service Navratna Defence PSU Bharat Electronics Ltd (BEL) has signed an MoU with Motorola Solutions India Pvt Ltd for co-operation in the field of broadband, push-to-talk service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hands-on: T-Mobile’s new suitcase packs a wireless charging pocket behind its vibrant looks</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hands-on-t-mobiles-new-suitcase-packs-a-wireless-charging-pocket-behind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hands-on-t-mobiles-new-suitcase-packs-a-wireless-charging-pocket-behind/</guid>
      <description>Hands-on: T-Mobile’s new suitcase packs a wireless charging pocket behind its vibrant looks T-Mobile probably isn’t the first name you think of with a suitcase, but the carrier is today debuting the “Un-Carrier On,” the first suitcase with built-in wireless charging and a vibrant magenta look that ought to prove tough to misplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netflix&#39;s $6.99 Basic With Ads tier rolls out today</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/netflixs-699-basic-with-ads-tier-rolls-out-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/netflixs-699-basic-with-ads-tier-rolls-out-today/</guid>
      <description>Netflix&amp;rsquo;s $6.99 Basic With Ads tier rolls out today Netflix is rolling out its ad-supported tier, which offers access to the streaming video service at the same $6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to get free Amazon Prime and Disney&#43;Hotstar on your Vodafone-Idea number</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-get-free-amazon-prime-and-disneyhotstar-on-your-vodafone-idea-numbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 03:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-get-free-amazon-prime-and-disneyhotstar-on-your-vodafone-idea-numbe/</guid>
      <description>How to get free Amazon Prime and Disney+Hotstar on your Vodafone-Idea number indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk plans to eliminate half of Twitter jobs to cut costs</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-plans-to-eliminate-half-of-twitter-jobs-to-cut-costs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 02:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-plans-to-eliminate-half-of-twitter-jobs-to-cut-costs/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk plans to eliminate half of Twitter jobs to cut costs indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple TV&#43; promotes new Selena Gomez documentary with two-month free subscription</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-tv-promotes-new-selena-gomez-documentary-with-two-month-free-subscri/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 02:34:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-tv-promotes-new-selena-gomez-documentary-with-two-month-free-subscri/</guid>
      <description>Apple TV+ promotes new Selena Gomez documentary with two-month free subscription Earlier this year, Apple TV+ announced the release of the new documentary film “My Mind &amp; Me” featuring popular actress and singer Selena Gomez.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5G support coming to iPhone users in India with iOS 16.2 as regional sales boom</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/5g-support-coming-to-iphone-users-in-india-with-ios-162-as-regional-sales-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 16:28:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/5g-support-coming-to-iphone-users-in-india-with-ios-162-as-regional-sales-/</guid>
      <description>5G support coming to iPhone users in India with iOS 16.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond passenger cars and pickups: Five questions answered about electrifying trucks</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/beyond-passenger-cars-and-pickups-five-questions-answered-about-electrifyi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 16:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/beyond-passenger-cars-and-pickups-five-questions-answered-about-electrifyi/</guid>
      <description>Beyond passenger cars and pickups: Five questions answered about electrifying trucks As part of its effort to reduce air pollution and cut greenhouse gas emissions that contribute to climate change, California is pursuing aggressive policies to promote clean trucks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We may finally be getting a sequel to one of my favorite Chromebooks of 2021</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/we-may-finally-be-getting-a-sequel-to-one-of-my-favorite-chromebooks-of-202/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 16:23:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/we-may-finally-be-getting-a-sequel-to-one-of-my-favorite-chromebooks-of-202/</guid>
      <description>We may finally be getting a sequel to one of my favorite Chromebooks of 2021 One of the most surprising and most delightful Chromebooks of the entire year in 2021 may finally be ready for a sequel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple confirms next iOS 16 beta will bring 5G to India</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-confirms-next-ios-16-beta-will-bring-5g-to-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 16:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-confirms-next-ios-16-beta-will-bring-5g-to-india/</guid>
      <description>Apple confirms next iOS 16 beta will bring 5G to India Users of 5G iPhones in India will begin to be able to use the faster cellular service shortly, as the company says the next iOS 16 software beta will enable it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>B&amp;H&#39;s Holiday Head Start Sale knocks up to 46% off Macs, iPads, HomePod mini, photo gear</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bhs-holiday-head-start-sale-knocks-up-to-46-off-macs-ipads-homepod-min/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 16:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bhs-holiday-head-start-sale-knocks-up-to-46-off-macs-ipads-homepod-min/</guid>
      <description>B&amp;amp;H&amp;rsquo;s Holiday Head Start Sale knocks up to 46% off Macs, iPads, HomePod mini, photo gear The Holiday Head Start Sale at B&amp;H Photo is packed with discounts on electronics and Apple products, making shopping for top gift ideas a breeze.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New process for digital printing on textiles now ready for industry</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-process-for-digital-printing-on-textiles-now-ready-for-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 16:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-process-for-digital-printing-on-textiles-now-ready-for-industry/</guid>
      <description>New process for digital printing on textiles now ready for industry A new process for digital printing on textiles, developed within a research project at the University of Borås, can now be an important part of the solution for the textile industry to deal with the enormous consumption of water and emissions of hazardous substances, for which the industry is responsible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Etsy adds image-based search, but only on iOS for now</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/etsy-adds-image-based-search-but-only-on-ios-for-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 16:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/etsy-adds-image-based-search-but-only-on-ios-for-now/</guid>
      <description>Etsy adds image-based search, but only on iOS for now Etsy has begun testing visual search.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DJI unveils Mavic 3 Classic - a cheaper Mavic 3 without the tele camera</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dji-unveils-mavic-3-classic-a-cheaper-mavic-3-without-the-tele-camera/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 16:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dji-unveils-mavic-3-classic-a-cheaper-mavic-3-without-the-tele-camera/</guid>
      <description>DJI unveils Mavic 3 Classic - a cheaper Mavic 3 without the tele camera The DJI Mavic 3 was unveiled a year ago with a price of €2,100 for the base pack and though the price has come down a bit since, it may still be too pricey for some.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glasgow Apple Store employees first in the UK to unionize, call it a ‘historic moment’</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/glasgow-apple-store-employees-first-in-the-uk-to-unionize-call-it-a-his/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 16:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/glasgow-apple-store-employees-first-in-the-uk-to-unionize-call-it-a-his/</guid>
      <description>Glasgow Apple Store employees first in the UK to unionize, call it a ‘historic moment’ As unionization efforts continue around the globe at Apple Stores, a notable moment has occurred in Scotland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deals: Samsung Galaxy Z Flip 4 hits second-best price at $801, Lenovo Smart Clock 2 $35, more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/deals-samsung-galaxy-z-flip-4-hits-second-best-price-at-801-lenovo-smart/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 16:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/deals-samsung-galaxy-z-flip-4-hits-second-best-price-at-801-lenovo-smart/</guid>
      <description>Deals: Samsung Galaxy Z Flip 4 hits second-best price at $801, Lenovo Smart Clock 2 $35, more All of today’s best deals are now live and headlined by a more affordable way to get in the foldable game with the Samsung Galaxy Z Flip 4 at $199 off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI Test Kitchen adding text-to-image demos as Google releases short stories co-written with AI</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ai-test-kitchen-adding-text-to-image-demosas-google-releases-short-storie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 16:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ai-test-kitchen-adding-text-to-image-demosas-google-releases-short-storie/</guid>
      <description>AI Test Kitchen adding text-to-image demos as Google releases short stories co-written with AI Google announced AI Test Kitchen as a way to let people “learn about, experience, and give feedback on emerging AI technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wednesday’s best deals: Apple TV 4K $100, Satechi 40% off Apple accessory sale, more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/wednesdays-best-deals-apple-tv-4k-100-satechi-40-off-apple-accessory/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 16:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/wednesdays-best-deals-apple-tv-4k-100-satechi-40-off-apple-accessory/</guid>
      <description>Wednesday’s best deals: Apple TV 4K $100, Satechi 40% off Apple accessory sale, more All of today’s best deals for this fine Wednesday are now headlined by a chance to score an all-time low on Apple TV 4K at just $100.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp won’t let you send or open ‘View Once’ messages on Desktop soon</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-wont-let-you-send-or-open-view-once-messages-on-desktop-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 07:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-wont-let-you-send-or-open-view-once-messages-on-desktop-s/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp won’t let you send or open ‘View Once’ messages on Desktop soon indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mi clearance sale 2022: Get THESE Redmi phones at half price, check top deals here</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mi-clearance-sale-2022-get-these-redmi-phones-at-half-price-check-top-dea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 07:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mi-clearance-sale-2022-get-these-redmi-phones-at-half-price-check-top-dea/</guid>
      <description>Mi clearance sale 2022: Get THESE Redmi phones at half price, check top deals here The device boasts respectable camera specifications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp desktop users cannot send view once messages</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-desktop-users-cannot-send-view-once-messages/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 07:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-desktop-users-cannot-send-view-once-messages/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp desktop users cannot send view once messages If you receive a view once message on your phone, you will not be able to open it on the desktop as the feature is no longer supported in desktop applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter discontinues ad-free articles for premium Blue subscribers</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-discontinues-ad-free-articles-for-premium-blue-subscribers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 06:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-discontinues-ad-free-articles-for-premium-blue-subscribers/</guid>
      <description>Twitter discontinues ad-free articles for premium Blue subscribers The feature was based on the platform Twitter acquired from Scroll, a service that specialised in removing ads from news sites</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T-Mobile will start charging a $35 fee on all new activations and upgrades</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/t-mobile-will-start-charging-a-35-fee-on-all-new-activations-and-upgrades/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 06:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/t-mobile-will-start-charging-a-35-fee-on-all-new-activations-and-upgrades/</guid>
      <description>T-Mobile will start charging a $35 fee on all new activations and upgrades T-Mobile may be joining rivals Verizon and AT&amp;T by introducing an $35 charge for all new postpaid activations and upgrades, according to The T-Mo Report and some Redditors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft allows users to add pictures from Android in MS Word, Powerpoint</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/microsoft-allows-users-to-add-pictures-from-android-in-ms-word-powerpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 06:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/microsoft-allows-users-to-add-pictures-from-android-in-ms-word-powerpoint/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft allows users to add pictures from Android in MS Word, Powerpoint To link the Android device to the system, scan the QR provided under a Mobile Device and follow the onscreen instructions</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canon R6-II hands-on: Faster, more resolution and reduced heating issues</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/canon-r6-ii-hands-on-faster-more-resolution-and-reduced-heating-issues/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 04:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/canon-r6-ii-hands-on-faster-more-resolution-and-reduced-heating-issues/</guid>
      <description>Canon R6-II hands-on: Faster, more resolution and reduced heating issues Just two years after the launch of the original EOS R6, Canon has unveiled its successor, the $2,500 EOS R6 Mark II.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No, the Canon EOS R6 Mark II doesn&#39;t have a stacked sensor, but it&#39;s still a fine upgrade</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/no-the-canon-eos-r6-mark-ii-doesnt-have-a-stacked-sensor-but-its-still-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 04:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/no-the-canon-eos-r6-mark-ii-doesnt-have-a-stacked-sensor-but-its-still-/</guid>
      <description>No, the Canon EOS R6 Mark II doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a stacked sensor, but it&amp;rsquo;s still a fine upgrade The Canon EOS R6 Mark II is a new 24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iCloud Mail down for some users</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/icloud-mail-down-for-some-users/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 03:55:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/icloud-mail-down-for-some-users/</guid>
      <description>iCloud Mail down for some users toi</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon quiz today, November 1: Here&#39;re the answers to win Rs 5,000</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/amazon-quiz-today-november-1-herere-the-answers-to-win-rs-5000/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 03:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/amazon-quiz-today-november-1-herere-the-answers-to-win-rs-5000/</guid>
      <description>Amazon quiz today, November 1: Here&amp;rsquo;re the answers to win Rs 5,000 You have to answer all five questions to win today&#39;s prize.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Former New York Post employee apologizes for racist posting spree</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/former-new-york-post-employee-apologizes-for-racist-posting-spree/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 17:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/former-new-york-post-employee-apologizes-for-racist-posting-spree/</guid>
      <description>Former New York Post employee apologizes for racist posting spree The former New York Post employee who hijacked the outlet’s content management system and Twitter account to post a series of racist and sexist headlines last week has apologized for his actions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supporting innovation with automation: Researcher develops autonomous hot cell tool</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/supporting-innovation-with-automation-researcher-develops-autonomous-hot-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 17:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/supporting-innovation-with-automation-researcher-develops-autonomous-hot-c/</guid>
      <description>Supporting innovation with automation: Researcher develops autonomous hot cell tool Scientific progress is anything but automatic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia Shield TV’s latest update brings new controls, tons of bug fixes</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nvidia-shield-tvs-latest-update-brings-new-controls-tons-of-bug-fixes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 17:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nvidia-shield-tvs-latest-update-brings-new-controls-tons-of-bug-fixes/</guid>
      <description>Nvidia Shield TV’s latest update brings new controls, tons of bug fixes The long-standing Nvidia Shield TV is getting yet another Android TV update, this time with Shield Experience 9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Assistant ditches light mode theme on Android to be ‘consistent’ with Wear OS and TV</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-assistant-ditches-light-mode-theme-on-android-to-be-consistent/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 17:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-assistant-ditches-light-mode-theme-on-android-to-be-consistent/</guid>
      <description>Google Assistant ditches light mode theme on Android to be ‘consistent’ with Wear OS and TV If you’re not using dark mode on your Android device, you might notice that Google Assistant is using a dark theme regardless, and Google says that’s intentional.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart windows that can polarize sunlight could offer a low energy alternative to Wi-Fi</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/smart-windows-that-can-polarize-sunlight-could-offer-a-low-energy-alternati/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 17:11:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/smart-windows-that-can-polarize-sunlight-could-offer-a-low-energy-alternati/</guid>
      <description>Smart windows that can polarize sunlight could offer a low energy alternative to Wi-Fi Sunshine streaming through a window could be directly harnessed for wireless data transmission to electronic devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indie game ‘Wavetale’ survives Stadia’s obliteration, coming soon to consoles and PC</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indie-game-wavetale-survives-stadias-obliteration-coming-soon-to-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 17:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indie-game-wavetale-survives-stadias-obliteration-coming-soon-to-/</guid>
      <description>Indie game ‘Wavetale’ survives Stadia’s obliteration, coming soon to consoles and PC When Google Stadia made the insanely rash decision to shutter its consumer-facing cloud gaming platform, a handful of games were threatened to be dragged into the pit with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google halts Play Store billing in India; developers get compliance relief: All you want to know</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-halts-play-store-billing-in-india-developers-get-compliance-relief/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-halts-play-store-billing-in-india-developers-get-compliance-relief/</guid>
      <description>Google halts Play Store billing in India; developers get compliance relief: All you want to know Developers in India were given an extension until October 31, 2022 to comply due to unique circumstances with the payments landscape in the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xiaomi to launch Redmi Note 12 Pro&#43; as Xiaomi 12i in India soon: Check launch date, price &amp; more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/xiaomi-to-launch-redmi-note-12-pro-as-xiaomi-12i-in-india-soon-check-laun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/xiaomi-to-launch-redmi-note-12-pro-as-xiaomi-12i-in-india-soon-check-laun/</guid>
      <description>Xiaomi to launch Redmi Note 12 Pro+ as Xiaomi 12i in India soon: Check launch date, price &amp;amp; more The renamed Redmi Note 12 Pro+, Xiaomi 12i HyperCharge, is anticipated to have a 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Tab A7 Lite Kids Edition launches in the US</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-galaxy-tab-a7-lite-kids-edition-launches-in-the-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-galaxy-tab-a7-lite-kids-edition-launches-in-the-us/</guid>
      <description>Samsung Galaxy Tab A7 Lite Kids Edition launches in the US Samsung and AT&amp;T announced an exclusive Galaxy Tab A7 Lite Kids Edition - a slightly modified version of the Galaxy Tab A7 Lite with a rugged case and additional education and entertainment content suitable for kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nothing rolls out Ear (1) and Ear (Stick) support for Phone (1), other smartphones</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nothing-rolls-out-ear-1-and-ear-stick-support-for-phone-1-other-smar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nothing-rolls-out-ear-1-and-ear-stick-support-for-phone-1-other-smar/</guid>
      <description>Nothing rolls out Ear (1) and Ear (Stick) support for Phone (1), other smartphones Nothing said that users need not wait for Ear (stick) launch and can control all of Ear (1)’s features in Phone (1)’s Device Details or the Nothing X app now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft takes a $100-$200 loss on all Xbox Series X|S sales</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/microsoft-takes-a-100-200-loss-on-all-xbox-series-xs-sales/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/microsoft-takes-a-100-200-loss-on-all-xbox-series-xs-sales/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft takes a $100-$200 loss on all Xbox Series X|S sales Phil Spencer reiterated the company&#39;s loses</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EA and Marvel Unveil 3-Game Deal, to Kick Off With Iron Man</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ea-and-marvel-unveil-3-game-deal-to-kick-off-with-iron-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ea-and-marvel-unveil-3-game-deal-to-kick-off-with-iron-man/</guid>
      <description>EA and Marvel Unveil 3-Game Deal, to Kick Off With Iron Man Electronic Arts will launch an Iron Man game and at least two other action-adventure titles revolving around characters from the Marvel universe, under a deal announced by the video game publisher on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Donald Trump returning to Twitter? Here’s what Elon Musk has to say</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/is-donald-trump-returning-to-twitter-heres-what-elon-musk-has-to-say/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/is-donald-trump-returning-to-twitter-heres-what-elon-musk-has-to-say/</guid>
      <description>Is Donald Trump returning to Twitter? Here’s what Elon Musk has to say The big question everyone has been asking ever since Elon Musk announced that he plans to buy Twitter is if the former American President Donald Trump is coming back to the platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Workspace Individual accounts now have up to 1TB storage space</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-workspace-individual-accounts-now-have-up-to-1tb-storage-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 06:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-workspace-individual-accounts-now-have-up-to-1tb-storage-space/</guid>
      <description>Google Workspace Individual accounts now have up to 1TB storage space Google has announced that it will soon introduce more features for “Workspace Individual” users, including an increase in storage capacity and advances in email personalisation for all customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eerie image shows spectacular aftermath of a large star’s death</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/eerie-image-shows-spectacular-aftermath-of-a-large-stars-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 06:25:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/eerie-image-shows-spectacular-aftermath-of-a-large-stars-death/</guid>
      <description>Eerie image shows spectacular aftermath of a large star’s death indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will Donald Trump return to Twitter? Elon Musk says THIS</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/will-donald-trump-return-to-twitter-elon-musk-says-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 06:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/will-donald-trump-return-to-twitter-elon-musk-says-this/</guid>
      <description>Will Donald Trump return to Twitter? Elon Musk says THIS Elon Musk has fired a number of Twitter executives including CEO Parag Agrawal and Vijaya Gadde, Twitter`s longtime head of legal, policy and trust, who was in charge of significant account decisions, including suspending Trump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kodak Matrix QLED TV 50-inch review: Inexpensive, but feature-rich smart TV</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/kodak-matrix-qled-tv-50-inch-review-inexpensive-but-feature-rich-smart-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 06:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/kodak-matrix-qled-tv-50-inch-review-inexpensive-but-feature-rich-smart-tv/</guid>
      <description>Kodak Matrix QLED TV 50-inch review: Inexpensive, but feature-rich smart TV The Kodak Matrix QLED TV 50-inch goes beyond fundamentals in terms of features to look good for its price, but cheap built and unstable operating system give away its budget roots</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple TV app adds support for this video format</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-tv-app-adds-support-for-this-video-format/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 06:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-tv-app-adds-support-for-this-video-format/</guid>
      <description>Apple TV app adds support for this video format Along with HDR, content from Apple TV and iTunes movie rentals will now also support HDR10+.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp tests &#39;message yourself&#39; feature for Android, iOS: Details here</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-tests-message-yourself-feature-for-android-ios-details-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 06:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-tests-message-yourself-feature-for-android-ios-details-here/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp tests &amp;lsquo;message yourself&amp;rsquo; feature for Android, iOS: Details here This feature will help in transferring media, documents, contacts, and more from one device to the other</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MediaTek’s upcoming flagship chip to reportedly outperform Apple A16 Bionic in GPU performance</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mediateks-upcoming-flagship-chip-to-reportedly-outperform-apple-a16-bion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 06:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mediateks-upcoming-flagship-chip-to-reportedly-outperform-apple-a16-bion/</guid>
      <description>MediaTek’s upcoming flagship chip to reportedly outperform Apple A16 Bionic in GPU performance MediaTek is reportedly planning to launch its next-generation flagship chipset -- Dimensity 9200.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nokia set to launch its G60 smartphone in India; prices yet to be revealed</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nokia-set-to-launch-its-g60-smartphone-in-india-prices-yet-to-be-revealed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 01:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nokia-set-to-launch-its-g60-smartphone-in-india-prices-yet-to-be-revealed/</guid>
      <description>Nokia set to launch its G60 smartphone in India; prices yet to be revealed Nokia also announced the X30 last month alongside the G60, but it&#39;s unclear if that one will debut in India with the G60</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women and the cloud: The potential equalizer in a gender biased tech industry</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/women-and-the-cloud-the-potential-equalizer-in-a-gender-biased-tech-indust/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 01:19:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/women-and-the-cloud-the-potential-equalizer-in-a-gender-biased-tech-indust/</guid>
      <description>Women and the cloud: The potential equalizer in a gender biased tech industry The success of cloud tech in India offers a huge opportunity for Indian women in tech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Rupee trials to start from Tuesday, November 1</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/digital-rupee-trials-to-start-from-tuesday-november-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/digital-rupee-trials-to-start-from-tuesday-november-1/</guid>
      <description>Digital Rupee trials to start from Tuesday, November 1 As promised by RBI, the first pilot of the Digital currency, the Digital Rupee (e₹) will commence on November 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Ted Lasso&#39; film crew adopts Jason Sudeikis&#39;s costume for Halloween</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ted-lasso-film-crew-adopts-jason-sudeikiss-costume-for-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ted-lasso-film-crew-adopts-jason-sudeikiss-costume-for-halloween/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;Ted Lasso&amp;rsquo; film crew adopts Jason Sudeikis&amp;rsquo;s costume for Halloween Jason Sudeikis recently received a fun Halloween surprise as the film crew for &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fitbit Sense 2 at $199 makes it a compelling Pixel Watch alternative</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/fitbit-sense-2-at-199-makes-it-a-compelling-pixel-watch-alternative/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/fitbit-sense-2-at-199-makes-it-a-compelling-pixel-watch-alternative/</guid>
      <description>Fitbit Sense 2 at $199 makes it a compelling Pixel Watch alternative Google’s first true smartwatch lineup consists of three options between $230 and $350 which doesn’t leave a ton of room for each to be particularly different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instagram users are geting &#39;account suspended&#39; errors</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/instagram-users-are-geting-account-suspended-errors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/instagram-users-are-geting-account-suspended-errors/</guid>
      <description>Instagram users are geting &amp;lsquo;account suspended&amp;rsquo; errors Instagram appears to have gone down worldwide, but rather than solely being inaccessible, the fault is causing users to be told their accounts have been suspended.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T and Samsung launch Galaxy Tab A7 Lite Kids Edition with rugged design for $7/month</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/att-and-samsung-launch-galaxy-tab-a7-lite-kids-edition-with-rugged-design-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/att-and-samsung-launch-galaxy-tab-a7-lite-kids-edition-with-rugged-design-/</guid>
      <description>AT&amp;amp;T and Samsung launch Galaxy Tab A7 Lite Kids Edition with rugged design for $7/month AT&amp;T has partnered with Samsung to launch a brand new tablet option for parents to give their children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mars Express looks at mysterious Martian moon after software update</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mars-express-looks-at-mysterious-martian-moon-after-software-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 09:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mars-express-looks-at-mysterious-martian-moon-after-software-update/</guid>
      <description>Mars Express looks at mysterious Martian moon after software update indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhone 15 Pro Series Unlikely to Get 8P Camera Lens Upgrade: Ming-Chi Kuo</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/iphone-15-pro-series-unlikely-to-get-8p-camera-lens-upgrade-ming-chi-kuo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 09:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/iphone-15-pro-series-unlikely-to-get-8p-camera-lens-upgrade-ming-chi-kuo/</guid>
      <description>iPhone 15 Pro Series Unlikely to Get 8P Camera Lens Upgrade: Ming-Chi Kuo The iPhone 15 Pro series is now unlikely to get an 8P camera lens upgrade, according to analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space Calendar November 2022: Events Happening in Space</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/space-calendar-november-2022-events-happening-in-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 06:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/space-calendar-november-2022-events-happening-in-space/</guid>
      <description>Space Calendar November 2022: Events Happening in Space Know about the events happening in space this month, November 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter might start charging $20 per month for blue tick: Report</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-might-start-charging-20-per-month-for-blue-tick-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 06:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-might-start-charging-20-per-month-for-blue-tick-report/</guid>
      <description>Twitter might start charging $20 per month for blue tick: Report Twitter has planned to charge users $19.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nokia 8210 4G review: A good feature phone with mix of old and new features</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nokia-8210-4g-review-a-good-feature-phone-with-mix-of-old-and-new-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nokia-8210-4g-review-a-good-feature-phone-with-mix-of-old-and-new-features/</guid>
      <description>Nokia 8210 4G review: A good feature phone with mix of old and new features Priced at Rs 3,999, the Nokia 8210 4G is powered by 1,450 mAh battery and supports dual-SIM</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This scary Solar storm to spark Geomagnetic storm today! Danger ahead</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/this-scary-solar-storm-to-spark-geomagnetic-storm-today-danger-ahead/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 05:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/this-scary-solar-storm-to-spark-geomagnetic-storm-today-danger-ahead/</guid>
      <description>This scary Solar storm to spark Geomagnetic storm today! Danger ahead A Geomagnetic storm warning has been issued today as a solar storm races towards Earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk has quietly made a change in Twitter homepage, says report</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-has-quietly-made-a-change-in-twitter-homepage-says-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 05:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-has-quietly-made-a-change-in-twitter-homepage-says-report/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk has quietly made a change in Twitter homepage, says report According to The Verge, Musk requested that the Explore page which displays trending tweets and news stories, be redirected to the logged-out users visiting Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk considers making verification a Twitter Blue perk</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-considers-making-verification-a-twitter-blue-perk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 05:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-considers-making-verification-a-twitter-blue-perk/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk considers making verification a Twitter Blue perk With Elon Musk in charge, Twitter is planning to boost the price of its Blue subscription plan from $5 to $20 per month and make it mandatory for verified users, according to Platformer&#39;s Casey Newton and The Verge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter head Elon Musk shots down job cuts to avoid paying stock grants rumours</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-head-elon-musk-shots-down-job-cuts-to-avoid-paying-stock-grants-rum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 05:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-head-elon-musk-shots-down-job-cuts-to-avoid-paying-stock-grants-rum/</guid>
      <description>Twitter head Elon Musk shots down job cuts to avoid paying stock grants rumours Tesla, SpaceX CEO Elon Musk took over Twitter last week and the first thing that he did was to fire top executives including CEO Parag Agrawal, CFO Ned Segal, and Head of Legal Policy, Trust and Safety Vijaya Gadde.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quordle 280 answer for October 31, 2022: Know today&#39;s Quordle hints and clues here</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/quordle-280-answer-for-october-31-2022-know-todays-quordle-hints-and-clu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 01:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/quordle-280-answer-for-october-31-2022-know-todays-quordle-hints-and-clu/</guid>
      <description>Quordle 280 answer for October 31, 2022: Know today&amp;rsquo;s Quordle hints and clues here Quordle 280 answer for October 31, 2022: Finding it difficult to crack today&#39;s Quordle challenge?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wordle 499 answer for October 31: Hints and clues that will get you through quickly</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/wordle-499-answer-for-october-31-hints-and-clues-that-will-get-you-through/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 01:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/wordle-499-answer-for-october-31-hints-and-clues-that-will-get-you-through/</guid>
      <description>Wordle 499 answer for October 31: Hints and clues that will get you through quickly Wordle 499 answer for October 31: You cannot go wrong in guessing the Wordle snawer today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 trending phones of week 43</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/top-10-trending-phones-of-week-43/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 01:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/top-10-trending-phones-of-week-43/</guid>
      <description>Top 10 trending phones of week 43 It&#39;s a proper Redmi invasion in our trending chart, the newly announced 12 series occupying the first four spots and ending Google Pixel 7 Pro&#39;s three-week reign.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There’s never been a better time to buy a Chromecast with Google TV</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/theres-never-been-a-better-time-to-buy-a-chromecast-with-google-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 01:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/theres-never-been-a-better-time-to-buy-a-chromecast-with-google-tv/</guid>
      <description>There’s never been a better time to buy a Chromecast with Google TV I will be the first to admit that Google’s latest Chromecast with Google TV had me completely bewildered when it was announced just over a month ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How will metaverse change the shopping experience?</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-will-metaverse-change-the-shopping-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-will-metaverse-change-the-shopping-experience/</guid>
      <description>How will metaverse change the shopping experience? Mark Zuckerberg is doubling down on his efforts to take metaverse to the next level, despite investors&#39; pessimism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily deals Oct. 30: $240 Apple Watch SE Gen 2, $100 off Bose Frames Tempo, $200 off M1 12.9-inch iPad Pro, more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/daily-deals-oct-30-240-apple-watch-se-gen-2-100-off-bose-frames-tempo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 12:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/daily-deals-oct-30-240-apple-watch-se-gen-2-100-off-bose-frames-tempo/</guid>
      <description>Daily deals Oct. 30: $240 Apple Watch SE Gen 2, $100 off Bose Frames Tempo, $200 off M1 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BIG relief! Your Google storage plan increased to a fantastic 1TB for FREE</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/big-relief-your-google-storage-plan-increased-to-a-fantastic-1tb-for-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:53:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/big-relief-your-google-storage-plan-increased-to-a-fantastic-1tb-for-free/</guid>
      <description>BIG relief! Your Google storage plan increased to a fantastic 1TB for FREE Google announced that it is upgrading Cloud Storage from 15GB to 1TB for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install app updates on your Pixel Watch</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-install-app-updates-on-your-pixel-watch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:38:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-install-app-updates-on-your-pixel-watch/</guid>
      <description>How to install app updates on your Pixel Watch The Pixel Watch has its own set of apps that have been installed via the Play Store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crime blotter: Apple Store thefts in Maryland and Illinois</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/crime-blotter-apple-store-thefts-in-maryland-and-illinois/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:37:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/crime-blotter-apple-store-thefts-in-maryland-and-illinois/</guid>
      <description>Crime blotter: Apple Store thefts in Maryland and Illinois In the latest Apple Crime Blotter, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OMG! A dentist uses her mother&#39;s milk to make jewellery; buyers laud mementoes</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/omg-a-dentist-uses-her-mothers-milk-to-make-jewellery-buyers-laud-mement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 10:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/omg-a-dentist-uses-her-mothers-milk-to-make-jewellery-buyers-laud-mement/</guid>
      <description>OMG! A dentist uses her mother&amp;rsquo;s milk to make jewellery; buyers laud mementoes Additionally, Aditi created VT for a Canadian couple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nokia G60 5G launch in India soon; check smartphone&#39;s price, specs &amp; other details</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nokia-g60-5g-launch-in-india-soon-check-smartphones-price-specs-other-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 07:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nokia-g60-5g-launch-in-india-soon-check-smartphones-price-specs-other-/</guid>
      <description>Nokia G60 5G launch in India soon; check smartphone&amp;rsquo;s price, specs &amp;amp; other details An octa-core Qualcomm Snapdragon 695 CPU and 6GB of RAM power the 5G-capable smartphone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Injustice 2 to Marvel Snap: 6 new games to play on your iPhone</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/injustice-2-to-marvel-snap-6-new-games-to-play-on-your-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 07:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/injustice-2-to-marvel-snap-6-new-games-to-play-on-your-iphone/</guid>
      <description>Injustice 2 to Marvel Snap: 6 new games to play on your iPhone indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top smartphones to buy under Rs 20,000 in India: iQoo Z6 5G, Realme 9 5G SE and more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/top-smartphones-to-buy-under-rs-20000-in-india-iqoo-z6-5g-realme-9-5g-se/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 07:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/top-smartphones-to-buy-under-rs-20000-in-india-iqoo-z6-5g-realme-9-5g-se/</guid>
      <description>Top smartphones to buy under Rs 20,000 in India: iQoo Z6 5G, Realme 9 5G SE and more The post Top smartphones to buy under Rs 20,000 in India: iQoo Z6 5G, Realme 9 5G SE and more appeared first on BGR India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter takeover updates: Users to get downvote feature soon, know what&#39;s new about it</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-takeover-updates-users-to-get-downvote-feature-soon-know-whats-n/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 06:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-takeover-updates-users-to-get-downvote-feature-soon-know-whats-n/</guid>
      <description>Twitter takeover updates: Users to get downvote feature soon, know what&amp;rsquo;s new about it The new downvote option will soon be available to Twitter users on iOS and Android.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Total lunar eclipse on November 8</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/total-lunar-eclipse-on-november-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 06:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/total-lunar-eclipse-on-november-8/</guid>
      <description>Total lunar eclipse on November 8 Kolkata, October 30A fortnight after the partial solar eclipse, Kolkata as well as other parts of India and the globe will witness a total lunar eclipse on November 8, an eminent astrophysicist said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arm reportedly changing licensing model to prohibit custom GPUs and TPUs, could impact Google Tensor</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/arm-reportedly-changing-licensing-model-to-prohibit-custom-gpus-and-tpus-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 18:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/arm-reportedly-changing-licensing-model-to-prohibit-custom-gpus-and-tpus-c/</guid>
      <description>Arm reportedly changing licensing model to prohibit custom GPUs and TPUs, could impact Google Tensor Arm and Qualcomm are currently involved in a dispute over the latter’s acquisition of a chip company called Nuvia and subsequent work on new desktop (and server) chips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IDC: Vivo secures the top spot in Chinese smartphone market for Q3 2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/idc-vivo-secures-the-top-spot-in-chinese-smartphone-market-for-q3-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 18:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/idc-vivo-secures-the-top-spot-in-chinese-smartphone-market-for-q3-2022/</guid>
      <description>IDC: Vivo secures the top spot in Chinese smartphone market for Q3 2022 The Chinese smartphone market is the biggest one in the world and according to IDathe steady decline trend continues throughout Q3 this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review: Pixel Watch ‘Woven’ band is comfortable but has a questionable clasp and cost</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/review-pixel-watch-woven-band-is-comfortable-but-has-a-questionable-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/review-pixel-watch-woven-band-is-comfortable-but-has-a-questionable-/</guid>
      <description>Review: Pixel Watch ‘Woven’ band is comfortable but has a questionable clasp and cost Google’s Pixel Watch has a limited number of bands available, and while the one that ships out of the box is pretty good, there’s room for improvement on comfort.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ye?s Twitter Access Freeze Was Previously Lifted</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/yes-twitter-access-freeze-was-previously-lifted/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 17:34:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/yes-twitter-access-freeze-was-previously-lifted/</guid>
      <description>Ye?s Twitter Access Freeze Was Previously Lifted Rapper Ye, formerly known as Kanye West, had his access to Twitter limited only for a ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Is the Only Big Tech Consolation in Wild $477 Bn Rout</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-is-the-only-big-tech-consolation-in-wild-477-bn-rout/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 17:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-is-the-only-big-tech-consolation-in-wild-477-bn-rout/</guid>
      <description>Apple Is the Only Big Tech Consolation in Wild $477 Bn Rout In a week that has seen hundreds of billions in market value wiped out at the biggest technology firms, Apple is bucking the trend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Express VPN Aircove router review: an okay router with neat VPN tools</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/express-vpn-aircove-router-review-an-okay-router-with-neat-vpn-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 15:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/express-vpn-aircove-router-review-an-okay-router-with-neat-vpn-tools/</guid>
      <description>Express VPN Aircove router review: an okay router with neat VPN tools The Express VPN Aircove router adds VPN connectivity to the entire home network with a straightforward interface, but it lacks in some areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ChromeOS “Privacy Hub” icons on device shelf will let you toggle access to camera, mic, more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/chromeos-privacy-hub-icons-on-device-shelf-will-let-you-toggle-access/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 15:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/chromeos-privacy-hub-icons-on-device-shelf-will-let-you-toggle-access/</guid>
      <description>ChromeOS “Privacy Hub” icons on device shelf will let you toggle access to camera, mic, more Earlier this year, ChromeOS began prepping what’s known as the ‘Privacy Hub‘ – a one-stop shop for all of your device’s privacy and security options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried UE&#39;s automatic heat-to-fit earbuds and they&#39;re a revelation</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/i-tried-ues-automatic-heat-to-fit-earbuds-and-theyre-a-revelation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 10:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/i-tried-ues-automatic-heat-to-fit-earbuds-and-theyre-a-revelation/</guid>
      <description>I tried UE&amp;rsquo;s automatic heat-to-fit earbuds and they&amp;rsquo;re a revelation Ultimate Ears&#39; UE Fits are now available in the UK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple @ Work: iMessage could be a strong business communication tool if Apple expanded it to other platforms</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-work-imessage-could-be-a-strong-business-communication-tool-if-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-work-imessage-could-be-a-strong-business-communication-tool-if-app/</guid>
      <description>Apple @ Work: iMessage could be a strong business communication tool if Apple expanded it to other platforms Apple at Work is bought to you by Jamf: Get complete management and security solutions for your organization that are enterprise secure, consumer simple, and protect personal privacy with Jamf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump&#39;s fake Twitter account goes viral on internet; netizens react with funny memes</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/donald-trumps-fake-twitter-account-goes-viral-on-internet-netizens-react-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 09:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/donald-trumps-fake-twitter-account-goes-viral-on-internet-netizens-react-/</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s fake Twitter account goes viral on internet; netizens react with funny memes After a brief panic, individuals realised the tweet was not sent from Trump&#39;s account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video of two fired employees outside Headquarters; Know the fact</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/video-of-two-fired-employees-outside-headquarters-know-the-fact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 09:52:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/video-of-two-fired-employees-outside-headquarters-know-the-fact/</guid>
      <description>Video of two fired employees outside Headquarters; Know the fact Elon Musk, who is famous for his sense of humour and his mistrust of the media, also came out with a witty reaction to the entire prankster episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp coming out with blur tool to help users hide sensitive information</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-coming-out-with-blur-tool-to-help-users-hide-sensitive-information/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 02:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-coming-out-with-blur-tool-to-help-users-hide-sensitive-information/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp coming out with blur tool to help users hide sensitive information For WhatsApp web and WhatsApp desktop users, the messaging app is rolling out a blur tool to enable users to blur a part or the entire photo before sending.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xiaomi 12 Lite 5G NE, Xiaomi 13 Lite, and Xiaomi Civi 2 might all be the same device</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/xiaomi-12-lite-5g-ne-xiaomi-13-lite-and-xiaomi-civi-2-might-all-be-the-sa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 02:57:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/xiaomi-12-lite-5g-ne-xiaomi-13-lite-and-xiaomi-civi-2-might-all-be-the-sa/</guid>
      <description>Xiaomi 12 Lite 5G NE, Xiaomi 13 Lite, and Xiaomi Civi 2 might all be the same device The upcoming Xiaomi 13 Lite has been spotted in the IMEI database today, bearing the model number 2210129SG.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Q4 earnings report highlights yet another strong performance</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-q4-earnings-report-highlights-yet-another-strong-performance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 16:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-q4-earnings-report-highlights-yet-another-strong-performance/</guid>
      <description>Apple Q4 earnings report highlights yet another strong performance As expected, Apple released its Q4 earnings report for the fiscal quarter ending on September 24 and quarterly revenues sitting at an all-time high of $90.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Amazon Prime Video server packed with viewer data was exposed online</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/an-amazon-prime-video-server-packed-with-viewer-data-was-exposed-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 16:39:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/an-amazon-prime-video-server-packed-with-viewer-data-was-exposed-online/</guid>
      <description>An Amazon Prime Video server packed with viewer data was exposed online Amazon says server was quickly secured, and no login or payment details were exposed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google revives Pebble smartwatch app with support for Pixel 7 in fresh update</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-revives-pebble-smartwatch-app-with-support-for-pixel-7-in-fresh-upda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 16:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-revives-pebble-smartwatch-app-with-support-for-pixel-7-in-fresh-upda/</guid>
      <description>Google revives Pebble smartwatch app with support for Pixel 7 in fresh update It’s been almost a decade since Pebble closed its doors, but support for the brand’s smartwatches has lived on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9to5Mac Daily: October 28, 2022 – AAPL earnings, iPhone 15 rumors</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/9to5mac-daily-october-28-2022-aapl-earnings-iphone-15-rumors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 16:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/9to5mac-daily-october-28-2022-aapl-earnings-iphone-15-rumors/</guid>
      <description>9to5Mac Daily: October 28, 2022 – AAPL earnings, iPhone 15 rumors Listen to a recap of the top stories of the day from 9to5Mac.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James Webb Space Telescope captures a spooky view of the Pillars of Creation</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/james-webb-space-telescope-captures-a-spooky-view-of-the-pillars-of-creatio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 16:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/james-webb-space-telescope-captures-a-spooky-view-of-the-pillars-of-creatio/</guid>
      <description>James Webb Space Telescope captures a spooky view of the Pillars of Creation NASA has released another image that the James Webb Space Telescope has captured of the Pillars of Creation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanye West Back on Twitter as Elon Musk Takes Control of Platform</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/kanye-west-back-on-twitter-as-elon-musk-takes-control-of-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 16:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/kanye-west-back-on-twitter-as-elon-musk-takes-control-of-platform/</guid>
      <description>Kanye West Back on Twitter as Elon Musk Takes Control of Platform Rapper Kanye West&#39;s Twitter profile, which was suspended for posting anti-Semitic remarks, appeared to be back up on the platform, a day after billionaire Elon Musk took ownership of the social media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAPL up 6%, despite warning of tougher quarter ahead</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/aapl-up-6-despite-warning-of-tougher-quarter-ahead/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 14:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/aapl-up-6-despite-warning-of-tougher-quarter-ahead/</guid>
      <description>AAPL up 6%, despite warning of tougher quarter ahead Early trading today has seen AAPL up by more than 6% following yesterday’s earnings report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Apple iPad 2022 models go on first sale in India: Price, offers and other details</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-apple-ipad-2022-models-go-on-first-sale-in-india-price-offers-and-oth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 14:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-apple-ipad-2022-models-go-on-first-sale-in-india-price-offers-and-oth/</guid>
      <description>New Apple iPad 2022 models go on first sale in India: Price, offers and other details Apple unveiled the new variants of iPad -- the entry level iPad, an 11-inch iPad Pro and a 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xbox Games with Gold November lineup announced</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/xbox-games-with-gold-november-lineup-announced/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 14:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/xbox-games-with-gold-november-lineup-announced/</guid>
      <description>Xbox Games with Gold November lineup announced Here are November&#39;s Games with Gold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gotham Knights gets its first patch for PC: Aims at fixing several performance and stability issues</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gotham-knights-gets-its-first-patch-for-pc-aims-at-fixing-several-performa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 14:18:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gotham-knights-gets-its-first-patch-for-pc-aims-at-fixing-several-performa/</guid>
      <description>Gotham Knights gets its first patch for PC: Aims at fixing several performance and stability issues Gotham Knights is the latest title by WB Games Montreal and it is a hot topic for gamers right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nokia G60 5G India Launch Confirmed, Pre-Booking to Commence Soon</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nokia-g60-5g-india-launch-confirmed-pre-booking-to-commence-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 14:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nokia-g60-5g-india-launch-confirmed-pre-booking-to-commence-soon/</guid>
      <description>Nokia G60 5G India Launch Confirmed, Pre-Booking to Commence Soon Nokia G60 5G is confirmed to launch in India soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter: Influential network with a relatively limited audience</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-influential-network-with-a-relatively-limited-audience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 14:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-influential-network-with-a-relatively-limited-audience/</guid>
      <description>Twitter: Influential network with a relatively limited audience Purchased by Elon Musk for $44 billion, Twitter is popular with politicians, journalists and celebrities, but the social media giant draws a smaller user base than some competitors, including Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Would Now Hopefully Act Against Hate Speech: Rahul Gandhi</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-would-now-hopefully-act-against-hate-speech-rahul-gandhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 14:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-would-now-hopefully-act-against-hate-speech-rahul-gandhi/</guid>
      <description>Twitter Would Now Hopefully Act Against Hate Speech: Rahul Gandhi Former Congress president Rahul Gandhi hoped on Friday that Twitter would now act against hate speech, check facts more robustly and not stifle the voice of the opposition in India, soon after.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lego is discontinuing its Mindstorms robotics kits by the end of the year</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/lego-is-discontinuing-its-mindstorms-robotics-kits-by-the-end-of-the-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 10:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/lego-is-discontinuing-its-mindstorms-robotics-kits-by-the-end-of-the-year/</guid>
      <description>Lego is discontinuing its Mindstorms robotics kits by the end of the year Lego&#39;s Mindstorms robotics kits have been on the market since 1998, born from a collaboration between Lego and the Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple CEO Tim Cook addresses iPhone 14 Pro supply shortage</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-ceo-tim-cook-addresses-iphone-14-pro-supply-shortage/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 10:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-ceo-tim-cook-addresses-iphone-14-pro-supply-shortage/</guid>
      <description>Apple CEO Tim Cook addresses iPhone 14 Pro supply shortage Apple talks about iPhone 14 Pro shortage issue; CEO Tim Cook claims stock shortage should end soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple&#39;s paid subscribers doubled in three years to 900 mn, says Tim Cook</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apples-paid-subscribers-doubled-in-three-years-to-900-mn-says-tim-cook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 09:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apples-paid-subscribers-doubled-in-three-years-to-900-mn-says-tim-cook/</guid>
      <description>Apple&amp;rsquo;s paid subscribers doubled in three years to 900 mn, says Tim Cook The company said that paid accounts are growing faster than transacting accounts, so the penetration of paid accounts is increasing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk completes Twitter takeover: Here are his top 5 tweets on what’s next</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-completes-twitter-takeover-here-are-his-top-5-tweets-on-whats/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 07:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-completes-twitter-takeover-here-are-his-top-5-tweets-on-whats/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk completes Twitter takeover: Here are his top 5 tweets on what’s next indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garena Free Fire Max Redeem Codes for October 28, 2022: Grab your daily rewards and goodies here</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/garena-free-fire-max-redeem-codes-for-october-28-2022-grab-your-daily-rew/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 07:27:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/garena-free-fire-max-redeem-codes-for-october-28-2022-grab-your-daily-rew/</guid>
      <description>Garena Free Fire Max Redeem Codes for October 28, 2022: Grab your daily rewards and goodies here Players can choose their starting positions in this game, as well as collect supplies and weaponry to keep them going while on the battlefield.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No violation of net neutrality in network slicing, find Trai, DoT</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/no-violation-of-net-neutrality-in-network-slicing-find-trai-dot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 07:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/no-violation-of-net-neutrality-in-network-slicing-find-trai-dot/</guid>
      <description>No violation of net neutrality in network slicing, find Trai, DoT To make the most of 5G technology, which offers features like network slicing and giving a dedicated experience to an organisation, Jio, Airtel have urged lawmakers to review the net neutrality rules</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redmi Note 12 series finally brings 5G across the popular mid-range series</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/redmi-note-12-series-finally-brings-5g-across-the-popular-mid-range-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 07:19:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/redmi-note-12-series-finally-brings-5g-across-the-popular-mid-range-series/</guid>
      <description>Redmi Note 12 series finally brings 5G across the popular mid-range series indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Elon Musk era begins at Twitter: Expect the unexpected</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-elon-musk-era-begins-at-twitter-expect-the-unexpected/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 07:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-elon-musk-era-begins-at-twitter-expect-the-unexpected/</guid>
      <description>The Elon Musk era begins at Twitter: Expect the unexpected Elon Musk is known for his rather unconventional style of management if his track record at Tesla is anything to go by.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to watch the Charlie Brown Halloween special for free</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-watch-the-charlie-brown-halloween-special-for-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-watch-the-charlie-brown-halloween-special-for-free/</guid>
      <description>How to watch the Charlie Brown Halloween special for free Happy Halloween!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global smartphone shipments decline due to poor demand, only Apple sees growth: Canalys</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/global-smartphone-shipments-decline-due-to-poor-demand-only-apple-sees-gro/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/global-smartphone-shipments-decline-due-to-poor-demand-only-apple-sees-gro/</guid>
      <description>Global smartphone shipments decline due to poor demand, only Apple sees growth: Canalys indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota and DC sue Target-owned Shipt delivery service for worker misclassification</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/minnesota-and-dc-sue-target-owned-shipt-delivery-service-for-worker-misclas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/minnesota-and-dc-sue-target-owned-shipt-delivery-service-for-worker-misclas/</guid>
      <description>Minnesota and DC sue Target-owned Shipt delivery service for worker misclassification The Minnesota and District of Columbia attorneys general are suing Target-owned Shipt delivery service over worker misclassification, CBS News has reported.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple sets new revenue record in India, logs double-digit growth in Q3&#39;2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-sets-new-revenue-record-in-india-logs-double-digit-growth-in-q32022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-sets-new-revenue-record-in-india-logs-double-digit-growth-in-q32022/</guid>
      <description>Apple sets new revenue record in India, logs double-digit growth in Q3&#39;2022 Apple posted a September quarter record revenue of $90.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube introduces @ Handle feature: Know what is it, how it works and more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/youtube-introduces-handle-feature-know-what-is-it-how-it-works-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/youtube-introduces-handle-feature-know-what-is-it-how-it-works-and-more/</guid>
      <description>YouTube introduces @ Handle feature: Know what is it, how it works and more YouTube says its Handle feature would enable new way for users to find and connect with creators</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Buds 2 Pro review: Best earbuds for Samsung users</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-galaxy-buds-2-pro-review-best-earbuds-for-samsung-users/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 03:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-galaxy-buds-2-pro-review-best-earbuds-for-samsung-users/</guid>
      <description>Samsung Galaxy Buds 2 Pro review: Best earbuds for Samsung users Every smartphone brand is trying to do what Apple did years ago and proudly continues to do: create a mobile ecosystem in the most convenient way that compels the user not to leave it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk officially takes over as Twitter CEO and fires company executives</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-officially-takes-over-as-twitter-ceo-and-fires-company-executives/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 01:25:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-officially-takes-over-as-twitter-ceo-and-fires-company-executives/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk officially takes over as Twitter CEO and fires company executives The first chapter of the saga between Twitter and Elon Musk has come to an end, but there’s much more to come.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk has begun his takeover of Twitter</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-has-begun-his-takeover-of-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 01:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-has-begun-his-takeover-of-twitter/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk has begun his takeover of Twitter After months of legal drama, Elon Musk has begun his takeover of Twitter, according to The Wall Street Journal and The Washington Post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Check out all 48 Yuppie Psycho: Executive Edition Xbox achievements</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/check-out-all-48-yuppie-psycho-executive-edition-xbox-achievements/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:19:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/check-out-all-48-yuppie-psycho-executive-edition-xbox-achievements/</guid>
      <description>Check out all 48 Yuppie Psycho: Executive Edition Xbox achievements 48 achievements for 1,000 Gamerscore</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google and Coinbase join forces for the future of Web3</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-and-coinbase-join-forces-for-the-future-of-web3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:03:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-and-coinbase-join-forces-for-the-future-of-web3/</guid>
      <description>Google and Coinbase join forces for the future of Web3 Cryptocurrency as a means of decentralized money may be volatile and uncertain but building the future of the web on decentralized blockchain technologies is an explosively emerging market and many tech giants are jumping into the Web3 arena feet first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s every sensor on the Pixel Watch and what each one does</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/heres-every-sensor-on-the-pixel-watch-and-what-each-one-does/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/heres-every-sensor-on-the-pixel-watch-and-what-each-one-does/</guid>
      <description>Here’s every sensor on the Pixel Watch and what each one does Google’s Pixel Watch is a smartwatch that houses a slew of health features powered by Fitbit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scary sound of Earth&#39;s magnetic field is shocking; just LISTEN now</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/scary-sound-of-earths-magnetic-field-is-shocking-just-listen-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 16:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/scary-sound-of-earths-magnetic-field-is-shocking-just-listen-now/</guid>
      <description>Scary sound of Earth&amp;rsquo;s magnetic field is shocking; just LISTEN now Scientists have collaborated with artists and musicians to bring the spooky sound of Earth&#39;s magnetic field to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Music removes Kanye West playlist after controversy</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-music-removes-kanye-west-playlist-after-controversy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 16:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-music-removes-kanye-west-playlist-after-controversy/</guid>
      <description>Apple Music removes Kanye West playlist after controversy Following other companies, Apple has removed a Kanye West playlist from Apple Music after the singer make antisemitic remarks on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyundai supplier to open EV battery module plant in Alabama</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hyundai-supplier-to-open-ev-battery-module-plant-in-alabama/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 16:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hyundai-supplier-to-open-ev-battery-module-plant-in-alabama/</guid>
      <description>Hyundai supplier to open EV battery module plant in Alabama A Korean automotive parts company plans to open a $205 million factory that will supply 200,000 battery modules annually for electric vehicles produced in Alabama and Georgia, officials said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honeybee behavior informs efficiency of wind farms</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/honeybee-behavior-informs-efficiency-of-wind-farms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 16:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/honeybee-behavior-informs-efficiency-of-wind-farms/</guid>
      <description>Honeybee behavior informs efficiency of wind farms An algorithm based on the altruistic behavior of honeybees could help those designing wind farms know exactly where to plant each turbine in the array to maximize efficiency and energy output from the wind farm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two years into COVID-19, the city that never sleeps returns to waking up early</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/two-years-into-covid-19-the-city-that-never-sleeps-returns-to-waking-up-ea/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 16:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/two-years-into-covid-19-the-city-that-never-sleeps-returns-to-waking-up-ea/</guid>
      <description>Two years into COVID-19, the city that never sleeps returns to waking up early In 2020, our study showed that lockdowns from COVID-19 significantly increased electricity use in New York City apartments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Converting biowastes into a sustainable material for sound absorption</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/converting-biowastes-into-a-sustainable-material-for-sound-absorption/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 16:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/converting-biowastes-into-a-sustainable-material-for-sound-absorption/</guid>
      <description>Converting biowastes into a sustainable material for sound absorption Researchers at Aalto University are developing a way to convert biowaste into a new, sustainable sound-absorbing material.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching AI to accurately colorize marine plankton images</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/teaching-ai-to-accurately-colorize-marine-plankton-images/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 16:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/teaching-ai-to-accurately-colorize-marine-plankton-images/</guid>
      <description>Teaching AI to accurately colorize marine plankton images Plankton are fundamental to the marine ecosystem and an indispensable means of modern marine ecological management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New method to determine the dimensionality of complex networks through hyperbolic geometry</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-method-to-determine-the-dimensionality-of-complex-networks-through-hype/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 16:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-method-to-determine-the-dimensionality-of-complex-networks-through-hype/</guid>
      <description>New method to determine the dimensionality of complex networks through hyperbolic geometry Reducing redundant information to find simplifying patterns in data sets and complex networks is a scientific challenge in many fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s an alternative to Belkin’s awkward Continuity Camera mount for iPhone</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/heres-an-alternative-to-belkins-awkward-continuity-camera-mount-for-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 16:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/heres-an-alternative-to-belkins-awkward-continuity-camera-mount-for-i/</guid>
      <description>Here’s an alternative to Belkin’s awkward Continuity Camera mount for iPhone Apple’s Continuity Camera feature has landed with macOS Ventura and iOS 16 that lets you use your great iPhone camera as your Mac’s webcam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FCC proposes rules to prevent fake emergency alerts</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/fcc-proposes-rules-to-prevent-fake-emergency-alerts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 16:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/fcc-proposes-rules-to-prevent-fake-emergency-alerts/</guid>
      <description>FCC proposes rules to prevent fake emergency alerts The Federal Communications Commission is well aware of the potential damage from fake emergency alerts, and it&#39;s hoping to minimize the threat with policy changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google giving some Nest Wifi owners a 30% Nest Wifi Pro discount</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-giving-some-nest-wifi-owners-a-30-nest-wifi-pro-discount/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-giving-some-nest-wifi-owners-a-30-nest-wifi-pro-discount/</guid>
      <description>Google giving some Nest Wifi owners a 30% Nest Wifi Pro discount The Nest Wifi Pro officially launches today, and Google is giving some Nest Wifi owners a 30% discount to encourage upgrades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New York Post is the latest news outlet to get hacked</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-new-york-post-is-the-latest-news-outlet-to-get-hacked/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 15:22:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-new-york-post-is-the-latest-news-outlet-to-get-hacked/</guid>
      <description>The New York Post is the latest news outlet to get hacked Fast Company isn&#39;t the only news outlet to suffer a recent, high-profile security breach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Xiaomi Redmi Note 12 Explorer sets a new benchmark for fast charging - 210W</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-xiaomi-redmi-note-12-explorer-sets-a-new-benchmark-for-fast-charging-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 15:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-xiaomi-redmi-note-12-explorer-sets-a-new-benchmark-for-fast-charging-/</guid>
      <description>The Xiaomi Redmi Note 12 Explorer sets a new benchmark for fast charging - 210W When the USB-IF announced plans for adding a Power Delivery profile for 240W charging we thought it was something for the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp: How to use the image blurring tool on desktop</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-how-to-use-the-image-blurring-tool-on-desktop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 15:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-how-to-use-the-image-blurring-tool-on-desktop/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp: How to use the image blurring tool on desktop WhatsApp recently rolled out the blur tool for some of its users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy M23 5G, Galaxy A04, Galaxy A04e to launch in India soon as support pages go live</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-galaxy-m23-5g-galaxy-a04-galaxy-a04e-to-launch-in-india-soon-as-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 15:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-galaxy-m23-5g-galaxy-a04-galaxy-a04e-to-launch-in-india-soon-as-s/</guid>
      <description>Samsung Galaxy M23 5G, Galaxy A04, Galaxy A04e to launch in India soon as support pages go live Samsung is gearing to launch a bunch of new M-series and A-series smartphones in India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A hackable, multi-functional, and modular extrusion 3D printer for soft materials</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/a-hackable-multi-functional-and-modular-extrusion-3d-printer-for-soft-mat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 15:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/a-hackable-multi-functional-and-modular-extrusion-3d-printer-for-soft-mat/</guid>
      <description>A hackable, multi-functional, and modular extrusion 3D printer for soft materials Researchers have developed a hackable and multi-functional 3D printer for soft materials that is affordable and open design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haryana Police Identifies 28,000 Phone Numbers Being Used for Cybercrimes</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/haryana-police-identifies-28000-phone-numbers-being-used-for-cybercrimes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 15:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/haryana-police-identifies-28000-phone-numbers-being-used-for-cybercrimes/</guid>
      <description>Haryana Police Identifies 28,000 Phone Numbers Being Used for Cybercrimes About 28,000 mobile phone numbers being misused for committing cybercrimes have been identified and they will be blocked soon, a senior Haryana Police officer said on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>‘Star Trek: Lower Decks’ finds riches in its own margins</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/star-trek-lower-decks-finds-riches-in-its-own-margins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 15:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/star-trek-lower-decks-finds-riches-in-its-own-margins/</guid>
      <description>‘Star Trek: Lower Decks’ finds riches in its own margins It’s been a long road, getting from Lower Decks’ slightly rough-around-the-edges first episode to here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Researchers design next-generation electrolytes for lithium metal batteries</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/researchers-design-next-generation-electrolytes-for-lithium-metal-batteries/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 15:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/researchers-design-next-generation-electrolytes-for-lithium-metal-batteries/</guid>
      <description>Researchers design next-generation electrolytes for lithium metal batteries A team of researchers has discovered a new mechanism to stabilize the lithium metal electrode and electrolyte in lithium metal batteries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OnePlus offers up a vague schedule for when to expect the Android 13 beta on Nord devices</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oneplus-offers-up-a-vague-schedule-for-when-to-expect-the-android-13-beta-o/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 14:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oneplus-offers-up-a-vague-schedule-for-when-to-expect-the-android-13-beta-o/</guid>
      <description>OnePlus offers up a vague schedule for when to expect the Android 13 beta on Nord devices Android 13 is starting to expand past the beta stage on devices from Samsung, Vivo, and more after launching on Pixels earlier this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xbox Insiders will help shape the new dashboard</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/xbox-insiders-will-help-shape-the-new-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 14:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/xbox-insiders-will-help-shape-the-new-dashboard/</guid>
      <description>Xbox Insiders will help shape the new dashboard The Xbox team is asking for Xbox Insider feedback on new preview updates</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp submits report to IT Ministry on Tuesday&#39;s service outage</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-submits-report-to-it-ministry-on-tuesdays-service-outage/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-submits-report-to-it-ministry-on-tuesdays-service-outage/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp submits report to IT Ministry on Tuesday&amp;rsquo;s service outage Messaging platform WhatsApp has submitted its report to the IT ministry on the service outage that happened on Tuesday, according to government sources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung reports record revenue but 24% decline in profit in Q3</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-reports-record-revenue-but-24-decline-in-profit-in-q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:22:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-reports-record-revenue-but-24-decline-in-profit-in-q3/</guid>
      <description>Samsung reports record revenue but 24% decline in profit in Q3 Samsung posted its Q3 earnings report today, and the numbers revealed the most revenue ever recorded for this three-month period.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily deals Oct. 27: $800 off Samsung OLED TVs, $200 off M1 12.9-inch iPad Pro, Hover-1 Blast scooter for $90, more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/daily-deals-oct-27-800-off-samsung-oled-tvs-200-off-m1-129-inch-ipad-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/daily-deals-oct-27-800-off-samsung-oled-tvs-200-off-m1-129-inch-ipad-/</guid>
      <description>Daily deals Oct. 27: $800 off Samsung OLED TVs, $200 off M1 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Webb captures ‘unprecedented’ image of galaxies merging near supermassive black hole</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/webb-captures-unprecedented-image-of-galaxies-merging-near-supermassi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/webb-captures-unprecedented-image-of-galaxies-merging-near-supermassi/</guid>
      <description>Webb captures ‘unprecedented’ image of galaxies merging near supermassive black hole indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TikTok gaming push will be an ’enormous’ one, launch expected on Nov 2</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tiktok-gaming-push-will-be-an-enormous-one-launch-expected-on-nov-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:06:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tiktok-gaming-push-will-be-an-enormous-one-launch-expected-on-nov-2/</guid>
      <description>TikTok gaming push will be an ’enormous’ one, launch expected on Nov 2 TikTok gaming has so far been a very small part of the streaming video app, but the company is said to be just days away from announcing an “enormous” push into the games market … more… The post TikTok gaming push will be an ’enormous’ one, launch expected on Nov 2 appeared first on 9to5Mac.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Ear (stick) not for you? These 5 premium earbuds may fit the bill</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nothing-ear-stick-not-for-you-these-5-premium-earbuds-may-fit-the-bill/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nothing-ear-stick-not-for-you-these-5-premium-earbuds-may-fit-the-bill/</guid>
      <description>Nothing Ear (stick) not for you? These 5 premium earbuds may fit the bill indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forget iPhone 14, world&#39;s fastest phone coming; Check out this mind-blowing tech</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/forget-iphone-14-worlds-fastest-phone-coming-check-out-this-mind-blowing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 09:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/forget-iphone-14-worlds-fastest-phone-coming-check-out-this-mind-blowing/</guid>
      <description>Forget iPhone 14, world&amp;rsquo;s fastest phone coming; Check out this mind-blowing tech The iPhone 14 series is one of the fastest smartphones on the planet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devtron announces $12 million investment from Insight Partners</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/devtron-announces-12-million-investment-from-insight-partners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 09:37:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/devtron-announces-12-million-investment-from-insight-partners/</guid>
      <description>Devtron announces $12 million investment from Insight Partners The cloud-native space has seen the introduction of a wide array of open-source DevOps tools built for solving very specific use cases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NothingOS 1.1.6 for Phone (1) brings camera improvements, bug fixes &amp; more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nothingos-116-for-phone-1-brings-camera-improvements-bug-fixes-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nothingos-116-for-phone-1-brings-camera-improvements-bug-fixes-more/</guid>
      <description>NothingOS 1.1.6 for Phone (1) brings camera improvements, bug fixes &amp;amp; more The NothingOS 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Byju’s allegedly shuts Kerala office, forces employees to resign</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/byjus-allegedly-shuts-kerala-office-forces-employees-to-resign/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 09:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/byjus-allegedly-shuts-kerala-office-forces-employees-to-resign/</guid>
      <description>Byju’s allegedly shuts Kerala office, forces employees to resign Byju’s, the world’s most valued edtech firm backed by Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg’s Chan Zuckerberg Initiative, may have shut its office in Technopark, Thiruvananthapuram, Kerala and asked employees working there to resign.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U&amp;i launches 35W fast charger, 24W 4-in-1 powerbank: Details inside</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ui-launches-35w-fast-charger-24w-4-in-1-powerbank-details-inside/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 09:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ui-launches-35w-fast-charger-24w-4-in-1-powerbank-details-inside/</guid>
      <description>U&amp;amp;i launches 35W fast charger, 24W 4-in-1 powerbank: Details inside The powerbank comes equipped with a 10,000mAh battery capacity and claims to recharge your smartphone and TWS earphones as well as headphones multiple times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sundar Pichai received an early warning of an earthquake hitting San Jose</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sundar-pichai-received-an-early-warning-of-an-earthquake-hitting-san-jose/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 09:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sundar-pichai-received-an-early-warning-of-an-earthquake-hitting-san-jose/</guid>
      <description>Sundar Pichai received an early warning of an earthquake hitting San Jose You receive alerts about heart rate, blood pressure and even car accident on your smartphone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook selects 15 Indian online communities for accelerator programme</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/facebook-selects-15-indian-online-communities-for-accelerator-programme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 09:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/facebook-selects-15-indian-online-communities-for-accelerator-programme/</guid>
      <description>Facebook selects 15 Indian online communities for accelerator programme These community leaders will also get an opportunity to collaborate with advocates and other leaders in the community-building ecosystem to bring their ideas to life</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pokemon Go to roll out new updates to map</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/pokemon-go-to-roll-out-new-updates-to-map/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 09:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/pokemon-go-to-roll-out-new-updates-to-map/</guid>
      <description>Pokemon Go to roll out new updates to map After three years, Pokemon GO is releasing upgrades to keep offering an experience that unites trainers&#39; global adventure, the company said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Pass adds three new Xbox games today</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/game-pass-adds-three-new-xbox-games-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 06:59:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/game-pass-adds-three-new-xbox-games-today/</guid>
      <description>Game Pass adds three new Xbox games today Gunfire Reborn, Signalis, and Frog Detective: The Entire Mystery join Game Pass today</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ford disbands Argo AI autonomous vehicle unit, posts loss</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ford-disbands-argo-ai-autonomous-vehicle-unit-posts-loss/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 06:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ford-disbands-argo-ai-autonomous-vehicle-unit-posts-loss/</guid>
      <description>Ford disbands Argo AI autonomous vehicle unit, posts loss Ford said Wednesday that it is disbanding Argo AI, an autonomous vehicle company that it co-owns with Volkswagen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk updates his Twitter bio to &#34;Chief Twit&#34;</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-updates-his-twitter-bio-to-chief-twit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 06:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-updates-his-twitter-bio-to-chief-twit/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk updates his Twitter bio to &amp;ldquo;Chief Twit&amp;rdquo; Elon Musk has updated his Twitter bio to &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JioMart on WhatsApp a big opportunity for Meta, says Mark Zuckerberg</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/jiomart-on-whatsapp-a-big-opportunity-for-meta-says-mark-zuckerberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 06:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/jiomart-on-whatsapp-a-big-opportunity-for-meta-says-mark-zuckerberg/</guid>
      <description>JioMart on WhatsApp a big opportunity for Meta, says Mark Zuckerberg As Meta doubles down on its monetisation drive across its family of apps, its Founder and CEO Mark Zuckerberg has said that JioMart on WhatsApp in India will be a big opportunity for the paid messaging market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp may finally let you forward media with text captions</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-may-finally-let-you-forward-media-with-text-captions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 06:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-may-finally-let-you-forward-media-with-text-captions/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp may finally let you forward media with text captions indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple may release 16-inch iPad next year, foldable iPad in 2024: Reports</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-may-release-16-inch-ipad-next-year-foldable-ipad-in-2024-reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 06:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-may-release-16-inch-ipad-next-year-foldable-ipad-in-2024-reports/</guid>
      <description>Apple may release 16-inch iPad next year, foldable iPad in 2024: Reports The company&#39;s largest iPad Pro model right now is of 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JioMart on WhatsApp a big opportunity for us: Zuckerberg</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/jiomart-on-whatsapp-a-big-opportunity-for-us-zuckerberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 06:19:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/jiomart-on-whatsapp-a-big-opportunity-for-us-zuckerberg/</guid>
      <description>JioMart on WhatsApp a big opportunity for us: Zuckerberg New Delhi: As Meta doubles down on its monetisation drive across its family of apps, its Founder and CEO Mark Zuckerberg has said that JioMart on WhatsApp in India is going to be a big opportunity for the paid messaging market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Realme 10 series design teased ahead of launch, tipped to launch in November</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/realme-10-series-design-teased-ahead-of-launch-tipped-to-launch-in-novembe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 06:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/realme-10-series-design-teased-ahead-of-launch-tipped-to-launch-in-novembe/</guid>
      <description>Realme 10 series design teased ahead of launch, tipped to launch in November Realme is heading towards the launch of its upcoming smartphone series– Realme 10 series–in China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple&#39;s lack of care with gambling app ads is a symptom of a bigger problem</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apples-lack-of-care-with-gambling-app-ads-is-a-symptom-of-a-bigger-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apples-lack-of-care-with-gambling-app-ads-is-a-symptom-of-a-bigger-problem/</guid>
      <description>Apple&amp;rsquo;s lack of care with gambling app ads is a symptom of a bigger problem Apple can argue about privacy, it can claim to put users before anything else, but when its business runs on gambling ads, it&#39;s moving yet further away from its stated principles and becoming a gambling company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy S22 gets astrophotography and multiple exposure mode in latest camera updates</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-galaxy-s22-gets-astrophotography-and-multiple-exposure-mode-in-late/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-galaxy-s22-gets-astrophotography-and-multiple-exposure-mode-in-late/</guid>
      <description>Samsung Galaxy S22 gets astrophotography and multiple exposure mode in latest camera updates A lot of Android devices now rely heavily on software to make cameras capable of much more than normally possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rocksteady co-founders leave studio, Suicide Squad &#34;nearly finished&#34;</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rocksteady-co-founders-leave-studio-suicide-squad-nearly-finished/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rocksteady-co-founders-leave-studio-suicide-squad-nearly-finished/</guid>
      <description>Rocksteady co-founders leave studio, Suicide Squad &amp;ldquo;nearly finished&amp;rdquo; Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League is in &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube for Android adds a navigation drawer in latest Explore revamp</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/youtube-for-android-adds-a-navigation-drawer-in-latest-explore-revamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/youtube-for-android-adds-a-navigation-drawer-in-latest-explore-revamp/</guid>
      <description>YouTube for Android adds a navigation drawer in latest Explore revamp While Google apps have generally removed the navigation drawer in recent years, some have brought them back with YouTube for Android and iOS being the latest example of that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding COVID-19 fake news with a computer chatbot</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/finding-covid-19-fake-news-with-a-computer-chatbot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/finding-covid-19-fake-news-with-a-computer-chatbot/</guid>
      <description>Finding COVID-19 fake news with a computer chatbot The COVID-19 pandemic has been marked by ever-present fake news surrounding the behavior and effects of the coronavirus, the impact of social distancing, lockdowns, and quarantine, and the medical response in terms of vaccinations and pharmaceuticals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The popularity of the Korean foreign influencer is on the rise, but it comes with a dark side</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-popularity-of-the-korean-foreign-influencer-is-on-the-rise-but-it-come/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-popularity-of-the-korean-foreign-influencer-is-on-the-rise-but-it-come/</guid>
      <description>The popularity of the Korean foreign influencer is on the rise, but it comes with a dark side If you&#39;ve been scrolling through YouTube, TikTok or Instagram it would be no surprise to chance upon calming minimalist aesthetics of Korean cafe decor; pilgrimages to the locations of popular K-dramas; and even the polite decorum of Korean public transport commuters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>16-inch iPad could arrive in late 2023</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/16-inch-ipad-could-arrive-in-late-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:18:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/16-inch-ipad-could-arrive-in-late-2023/</guid>
      <description>16-inch iPad could arrive in late 2023 A rumor claims that Apple is preparing to reveal a 16-inch iPad in the fourth quarter of 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peloton app is now available on Wear OS</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/peloton-app-is-now-available-on-wear-os/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/peloton-app-is-now-available-on-wear-os/</guid>
      <description>Peloton app is now available on Wear OS As new hardware continues to bolster the Wear OS ecosystem, Peloton has just launched an official Wear OS app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deals: Samsung Galaxy S22 now $100 off, Galaxy Tab S6 Lite hits $230, Anker gear, more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/deals-samsung-galaxy-s22-now-100-off-galaxy-tab-s6-lite-hits-230-anker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/deals-samsung-galaxy-s22-now-100-off-galaxy-tab-s6-lite-hits-230-anker/</guid>
      <description>Deals: Samsung Galaxy S22 now $100 off, Galaxy Tab S6 Lite hits $230, Anker gear, more All of today’s best deals include a $100 discount on the Samsung Galaxy S22 that now comes joined by its refreshed Galaxy Tab S6 Lite hitting $230.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You can buy the new iPad and iPad Pro, starting today</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/you-can-buy-the-new-ipad-and-ipad-pro-starting-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/you-can-buy-the-new-ipad-and-ipad-pro-starting-today/</guid>
      <description>You can buy the new iPad and iPad Pro, starting today The iPad 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vivo X90 to have Dimensity 9200 chipset and 120W fast charging</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/vivo-x90-to-have-dimensity-9200-chipset-and-120w-fast-charging/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:44:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/vivo-x90-to-have-dimensity-9200-chipset-and-120w-fast-charging/</guid>
      <description>vivo X90 to have Dimensity 9200 chipset and 120W fast charging The vivo X90 series will arrive in December, and the X90 Pro+ flagship will have a Snapdragon 8 Gen 2 chipset and a top-notch camera.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nxtdigital launches broadband-over-satellite solution ‘NXTSkyFi’</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nxtdigital-launches-broadband-over-satellite-solution-nxtskyfi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nxtdigital-launches-broadband-over-satellite-solution-nxtskyfi/</guid>
      <description>Nxtdigital launches broadband-over-satellite solution ‘NXTSkyFi’ Nxtdigital Ltd has announced the launch of “NXTSkyFi” which is a broadband-over-satellite (BOS) solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One of the world&#39;s biggest ticket websites suffered a multi-year data breach</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/one-of-the-worlds-biggest-ticket-websites-suffered-a-multi-year-data-breac/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/one-of-the-worlds-biggest-ticket-websites-suffered-a-multi-year-data-breac/</guid>
      <description>One of the world&amp;rsquo;s biggest ticket websites suffered a multi-year data breach See Tickets website had a skimmer gathering sensitive user payment data for more than two years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia RTX 4090 cable controversy rolls on as PSU maker looks to help owners</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nvidia-rtx-4090-cable-controversy-rolls-on-as-psu-maker-looks-to-help-owner/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nvidia-rtx-4090-cable-controversy-rolls-on-as-psu-maker-looks-to-help-owner/</guid>
      <description>Nvidia RTX 4090 cable controversy rolls on as PSU maker looks to help owners More reports of the cable melting on Nvidia’s flagship graphics card are rolling in, unfortunately for those owners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Store extends boosted trade-ins for Pixel 7 through November</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-store-extends-boosted-trade-ins-for-pixel-7-through-november/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:24:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-store-extends-boosted-trade-ins-for-pixel-7-through-november/</guid>
      <description>Google Store extends boosted trade-ins for Pixel 7 through November If you’ve been hoping to pick up a Pixel 7 and Pixel 7 Pro, the Google Store has yet again boosted trade-in values for a limited time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final season of Apple TV&#43; thriller &#39;Servant&#39; premieres January 13</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/final-season-of-apple-tv-thriller-servant-premieres-january-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/final-season-of-apple-tv-thriller-servant-premieres-january-13/</guid>
      <description>Final season of Apple TV+ thriller &amp;lsquo;Servant&amp;rsquo; premieres January 13 M.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sony&#39;s high-resolution A7R V mirrorless camera now shoots 8K video</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sonys-high-resolution-a7r-v-mirrorless-camera-now-shoots-8k-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sonys-high-resolution-a7r-v-mirrorless-camera-now-shoots-8k-video/</guid>
      <description>Sony&amp;rsquo;s high-resolution A7R V mirrorless camera now shoots 8K video Sony has launched the $3,900 A7R V, its latest mirrorless camera designed to shoot portraits, landscapes and other subjects that require as much resolution as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Six affordable 5G smartphones to buy under Rs 15,000</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/six-affordable-5g-smartphones-to-buy-under-rs-15000/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 12:34:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/six-affordable-5g-smartphones-to-buy-under-rs-15000/</guid>
      <description>Six affordable 5G smartphones to buy under Rs 15,000 indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You can now use Nintendo’s SNES gamepads with your iPhone, iPad, Mac and Apple TV</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/you-can-now-use-nintendos-snes-gamepads-with-your-iphone-ipad-mac-and-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 12:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/you-can-now-use-nintendos-snes-gamepads-with-your-iphone-ipad-mac-and-/</guid>
      <description>You can now use Nintendo’s SNES gamepads with your iPhone, iPad, Mac and Apple TV With iOS 16.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use Apple Pencil&#39;s new Hover Mode with M2 iPad Pro</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-use-apple-pencils-new-hover-mode-with-m2-ipad-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 12:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-use-apple-pencils-new-hover-mode-with-m2-ipad-pro/</guid>
      <description>How to use Apple Pencil&amp;rsquo;s new Hover Mode with M2 iPad Pro The new Hover Mode is either a gimmick you&#39;ll never use, or part of making Apple Pencil feel ever more like a natural part of your workflow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp reportedly rolls out image blur tool for desktop beta users</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-reportedly-rolls-out-image-blur-tool-for-desktop-beta-users/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 12:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-reportedly-rolls-out-image-blur-tool-for-desktop-beta-users/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp reportedly rolls out image blur tool for desktop beta users Popular messaging app WhatsApp is reportedly rolling out a new image blurring feature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moto Razr 2022 foldable smartphone with Snapdragon 8 Gen 1&#43; SoC, fast charging support launched globally</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/moto-razr-2022-foldable-smartphone-with-snapdragon-8-gen-1-soc-fast-charg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 12:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/moto-razr-2022-foldable-smartphone-with-snapdragon-8-gen-1-soc-fast-charg/</guid>
      <description>Moto Razr 2022 foldable smartphone with Snapdragon 8 Gen 1+ SoC, fast charging support launched globally Moto Razr 2022 is now official.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Watch saves doctor&#39;s life who took a hard fall</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-watch-saves-doctors-life-who-took-a-hard-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 10:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-watch-saves-doctors-life-who-took-a-hard-fall/</guid>
      <description>Apple Watch saves doctor&amp;rsquo;s life who took a hard fall Earlier this month, Apple Watch detected the pregnancy of a 34-year-old woman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Pass launch title Wo Long: Fallen Dynasty confirms release date</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/game-pass-launch-title-wo-long-fallen-dynasty-confirms-release-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 10:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/game-pass-launch-title-wo-long-fallen-dynasty-confirms-release-date/</guid>
      <description>Game Pass launch title Wo Long: Fallen Dynasty confirms release date We&#39;ll be playing the action-RPG in March 2023</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google is reportedly working on the “Pixel G10” that has the same specs as the Pixel 7 Pro</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-is-reportedly-working-on-the-pixel-g10-that-has-the-same-specs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 10:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-is-reportedly-working-on-the-pixel-g10-that-has-the-same-specs/</guid>
      <description>Google is reportedly working on the “Pixel G10” that has the same specs as the Pixel 7 Pro Google recently launched the Pixel 7 series in India including the Pixel 7 and Pixel 7 Pro smartphones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iMessage for Android would have stifled innovation, says Craig Federighi</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/imessage-for-android-would-have-stifled-innovation-says-craig-federighi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 10:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/imessage-for-android-would-have-stifled-innovation-says-craig-federighi/</guid>
      <description>iMessage for Android would have stifled innovation, says Craig Federighi Craig Federighi defended the decision to not develop Messages for Android, saying it would never get a mass audience, and had Apple done it, it would have hampered innovation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meta slams Apple for ‘undercutting others’ with ad policy</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/meta-slams-apple-for-undercutting-others-with-ad-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 10:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/meta-slams-apple-for-undercutting-others-with-ad-policy/</guid>
      <description>Meta slams Apple for ‘undercutting others’ with ad policy indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PlayStation 5 DualSense Edge controller: Release date, features, and everything you need to know</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/playstation-5-dualsense-edge-controller-release-date-features-and-everyt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 09:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/playstation-5-dualsense-edge-controller-release-date-features-and-everyt/</guid>
      <description>PlayStation 5 DualSense Edge controller: Release date, features, and everything you need to know indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ancient bacteria could still be beneath Martian surface</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ancient-bacteria-could-still-be-beneath-martian-surface/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 09:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ancient-bacteria-could-still-be-beneath-martian-surface/</guid>
      <description>Ancient bacteria could still be beneath Martian surface indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung October 2022 update rolling out for these Galaxy devices</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-october-2022-update-rolling-out-for-these-galaxy-devices/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-october-2022-update-rolling-out-for-these-galaxy-devices/</guid>
      <description>Samsung October 2022 update rolling out for these Galaxy devices Samsung is on a roll as of late with device updates for a number of handsets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Home app is getting these new features after promised update</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-home-app-is-getting-these-new-features-after-promised-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 08:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-home-app-is-getting-these-new-features-after-promised-update/</guid>
      <description>Google Home app is getting these new features after promised update The company has also added some design elements to the Routines page in the app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LinkedIn: How to spot fake profiles on the platform</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/linkedin-how-to-spot-fake-profiles-on-the-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 08:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/linkedin-how-to-spot-fake-profiles-on-the-platform/</guid>
      <description>LinkedIn: How to spot fake profiles on the platform LinkedIn has introduced new features to allow users to spot fake profiles and remove them from the platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You can now tell YouTube to prioritise new features</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/you-can-now-tell-youtube-to-prioritise-new-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 08:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/you-can-now-tell-youtube-to-prioritise-new-features/</guid>
      <description>You can now tell YouTube to prioritise new features Apart from voting for the features, YouTube users can also make requests for new features which will be added to the page every quarter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snap?s Evan Spiegel Slams the Metaverse, Touts Own AR Vision</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/snaps-evan-spiegel-slams-the-metaverse-touts-own-ar-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 08:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/snaps-evan-spiegel-slams-the-metaverse-touts-own-ar-vision/</guid>
      <description>Snap?s Evan Spiegel Slams the Metaverse, Touts Own AR Vision Snap founder Evan Spiegel rubbished the idea that future computing will migrate into a virtual world dubbed the metaverse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>As Nothing Ear (stick) TWS launches today, here are 5 other devices with translucent design language</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/as-nothing-ear-stick-tws-launches-today-here-are-5-other-devices-with-tr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 08:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/as-nothing-ear-stick-tws-launches-today-here-are-5-other-devices-with-tr/</guid>
      <description>As Nothing Ear (stick) TWS launches today, here are 5 other devices with translucent design language indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OM System unveils the OM-5, its first camera without the Olympus name</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/om-system-unveils-the-om-5-its-first-camera-without-the-olympus-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 08:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/om-system-unveils-the-om-5-its-first-camera-without-the-olympus-name/</guid>
      <description>OM System unveils the OM-5, its first camera without the Olympus name OM System has launched its first camera that doesn&#39;t carry the Olympus name, the $1,200 OM-5 — and it looks a lot like the Olympus OM-D E-M5 Mark III, other than a few tweaks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft launches developer-focused Mac mini-like PC with ARM processor</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/microsoft-launches-developer-focused-mac-mini-like-pc-with-arm-processor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 08:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/microsoft-launches-developer-focused-mac-mini-like-pc-with-arm-processor/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft launches developer-focused Mac mini-like PC with ARM processor indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk plans to wind up Twitter buyout deal by Friday: Report</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-plans-to-wind-up-twitter-buyout-deal-by-friday-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 08:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-plans-to-wind-up-twitter-buyout-deal-by-friday-report/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk plans to wind up Twitter buyout deal by Friday: Report Musk pledged to close the deal on a video conference call on Monday with bankers who are helping fund the deal, according to the report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhones will get USB-C charging to comply with EU law, Apple SVP confirms</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/iphones-will-get-usb-c-charging-to-comply-with-eu-law-apple-svp-confirms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 07:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/iphones-will-get-usb-c-charging-to-comply-with-eu-law-apple-svp-confirms/</guid>
      <description>iPhones will get USB-C charging to comply with EU law, Apple SVP confirms When the European Parliament voted in favor of making USB-C the common charging standard in the region, it was pretty obvious which company was going to be the most affected by the mandate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One UI 5.0 update roll out scheduled released for a host of Samsung devices</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/one-ui-50-update-roll-out-scheduled-released-for-a-host-of-samsung-devices/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 07:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/one-ui-50-update-roll-out-scheduled-released-for-a-host-of-samsung-devices/</guid>
      <description>One UI 5.0 update roll out scheduled released for a host of Samsung devices Samsung has announced the One UI 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google lists screen protectors ‘certified’ to work with Pixel 6 and 7 fingerprint sensor</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-lists-screen-protectors-certified-to-work-with-pixel-6-and-7-f/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 07:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-lists-screen-protectors-certified-to-work-with-pixel-6-and-7-f/</guid>
      <description>Google lists screen protectors ‘certified’ to work with Pixel 6 and 7 fingerprint sensor With the Pixel 6 now just over a week old for most owners, the under-display fingerprint sensor has emerged as one of the bigger points of contention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX usurps Boeing to become NASA’s largest for-profit vendor</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/spacex-usurps-boeing-to-become-nasas-largest-for-profit-vendor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 06:34:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/spacex-usurps-boeing-to-become-nasas-largest-for-profit-vendor/</guid>
      <description>SpaceX usurps Boeing to become NASA’s largest for-profit vendor Fourteen years after winning its first major NASA contract, data shared by Aviation Week reporter Irene Klotz shows that SpaceX has usurped every other major aerospace company in the US to become the space agency’s largest for-profit vendor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sennheiser Momentum 4 review: Pure music</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sennheiser-momentum-4-review-pure-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 06:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sennheiser-momentum-4-review-pure-music/</guid>
      <description>Sennheiser Momentum 4 review: Pure music indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp down for hours yesterday! Here is the &#34;reason&#34; why</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-down-for-hours-yesterday-here-is-the-reason-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 06:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-down-for-hours-yesterday-here-is-the-reason-why/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp down for hours yesterday! Here is the &amp;ldquo;reason&amp;rdquo; why WhatsApp down was the horror cry from millions of users yesterday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Obviously we’ll have to comply&#39;: Apple on bringing USB-C to iPhones</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/obviously-well-have-to-comply-apple-on-bringing-usb-c-to-iphones/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 06:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/obviously-well-have-to-comply-apple-on-bringing-usb-c-to-iphones/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;Obviously we’ll have to comply&amp;rsquo;: Apple on bringing USB-C to iPhones Greg Joswiak, Senior Vice President, worldwide marketing at Apple told The Wall Street Journal at their WSJ Tech Live event that “obviously we’ll [Apple] have to comply, we have no choice” in bringing an iPhone with a USB-C connector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motorola Moto Razr 2022 with Snapdragon 8 Plus Gen 1 makes global debut</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/motorola-moto-razr-2022-with-snapdragon-8-plus-gen-1-makes-global-debut/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 02:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/motorola-moto-razr-2022-with-snapdragon-8-plus-gen-1-makes-global-debut/</guid>
      <description>Motorola Moto Razr 2022 with Snapdragon 8 Plus Gen 1 makes global debut The Motorola Moto Razr 2022 is set to release in select European markets almost three months after its China debut.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New App Store ad slots heavily promote gambling apps</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-app-store-ad-slots-heavily-promote-gambling-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 01:55:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-app-store-ad-slots-heavily-promote-gambling-apps/</guid>
      <description>New App Store ad slots heavily promote gambling apps App developers have taken to Twitter to voice concerns that Apple&#39;s new App Store ad slots regularly feature gambling apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deals: get 2 lifetime licenses to Microsoft Office for Mac Home &amp; Business 2021 for just $79.99</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/deals-get-2-lifetime-licenses-to-microsoft-office-for-mac-home-business-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 01:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/deals-get-2-lifetime-licenses-to-microsoft-office-for-mac-home-business-/</guid>
      <description>Deals: get 2 lifetime licenses to Microsoft Office for Mac Home &amp;amp; Business 2021 for just $79.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How WhatsApp is turning into a spammer&#39;s paradise?</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-whatsapp-is-turning-into-a-spammers-paradise/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-whatsapp-is-turning-into-a-spammers-paradise/</guid>
      <description>How WhatsApp is turning into a spammer&amp;rsquo;s paradise? WhatsApp was hit with a major outage recently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How this Star Wars actor is helping Ukraine fight the “evil empire”</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-this-star-wars-actor-is-helping-ukraine-fight-the-evil-empire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 01:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-this-star-wars-actor-is-helping-ukraine-fight-the-evil-empire/</guid>
      <description>How this Star Wars actor is helping Ukraine fight the “evil empire” Mark Hamill, who plays Luke Skywalker in the Star Wars film franchise, has helped send at least 500 drones to Ukraine to help the country in its fight against Russia, the actor revealed in a radio interview with Bloomberg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lenovo Duet 3 Chromebook tablet is on sale again</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-lenovo-duet-3-chromebook-tablet-is-on-sale-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:53:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-lenovo-duet-3-chromebook-tablet-is-on-sale-again/</guid>
      <description>The Lenovo Duet 3 Chromebook tablet is on sale again Without a doubt, Lenovo’s OLED-toting Duet 5 Chromebook is the best ChromeOS tablet on the market but the smaller Duet 3 is still the more desirable device for those wanting something a little more portable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple issues first developer beta for iOS 16.2, iPadOS 16.2, watchOS 9.2</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-issues-first-developer-beta-for-ios-162-ipados-162-watchos-92/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-issues-first-developer-beta-for-ios-162-ipados-162-watchos-92/</guid>
      <description>Apple issues first developer beta for iOS 16.2, iPadOS 16.2, watchOS 9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improving the interfacial binding in flexible electronics is crucial for commercialization</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/improving-the-interfacial-binding-in-flexible-electronics-is-crucial-for-co/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/improving-the-interfacial-binding-in-flexible-electronics-is-crucial-for-co/</guid>
      <description>Improving the interfacial binding in flexible electronics is crucial for commercialization Stretchable electronic devices are promising candidates for personalized health care systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lyft&#39;s re-launched Pink subscription starts at $10 per month</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/lyfts-re-launched-pink-subscription-starts-at-10-per-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:45:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/lyfts-re-launched-pink-subscription-starts-at-10-per-month/</guid>
      <description>Lyft&amp;rsquo;s re-launched Pink subscription starts at $10 per month Lyft is once again rethinking its monthly subscription plan, and this time the cost might be easier to justify.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;I could have died&#39; says Apple Watch-wearing doctor who took a hard fall</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/i-could-have-died-says-apple-watch-wearing-doctor-who-took-a-hard-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/i-could-have-died-says-apple-watch-wearing-doctor-who-took-a-hard-fall/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;I could have died&amp;rsquo; says Apple Watch-wearing doctor who took a hard fall Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple releases first betas of iOS 16.2, iPadOS 16.2, macOS 13.1, and watchOS 9.2</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-releases-first-betas-of-ios-162-ipados-162-macos-131-and-watcho/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-releases-first-betas-of-ios-162-ipados-162-macos-131-and-watcho/</guid>
      <description>Apple releases first betas of iOS 16.2, iPadOS 16.2, macOS 13.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sony LinkBuds earbuds to receive multipoint pairing, LinkBuds S gets ‘Earth Blue’ colorway</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sony-linkbuds-earbuds-to-receive-multipoint-pairing-linkbuds-s-gets-ear/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sony-linkbuds-earbuds-to-receive-multipoint-pairing-linkbuds-s-gets-ear/</guid>
      <description>Sony LinkBuds earbuds to receive multipoint pairing, LinkBuds S gets ‘Earth Blue’ colorway Sony’s LinkBuds and LinkBuds S are set to get a brand-new software update in the coming weeks, bringing along multipoint pairing functionality to the wireless earbuds as well as a new “Earth Blue” color to the LinkBuds S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple seeds first developer beta of macOS Ventura 13.1</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-seeds-first-developer-beta-of-macos-ventura-131/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:38:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-seeds-first-developer-beta-of-macos-ventura-131/</guid>
      <description>Apple seeds first developer beta of macOS Ventura 13.1 Fresh from ending the betas of the milestone release, Apple is now working on the first post-release update for macOS Ventura, with developers getting the first beta build of macOS Ventura 13.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s dual pane Google Keep on Chromebooks, but it’s hard to find on tablets &amp; foldables</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/heres-dual-pane-google-keep-on-chromebooks-but-its-hard-to-find-on-t/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:35:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/heres-dual-pane-google-keep-on-chromebooks-but-its-hard-to-find-on-t/</guid>
      <description>Here’s dual pane Google Keep on Chromebooks, but it’s hard to find on tablets &amp;amp; foldables At the start of last month, Google announced that Keep was getting a dual-pane view on large-screen devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Businesses waste a full-time working week setting up video calls</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/businesses-waste-a-full-time-working-week-setting-up-video-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:28:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/businesses-waste-a-full-time-working-week-setting-up-video-calls/</guid>
      <description>Businesses waste a full-time working week setting up video calls AV technologies need to be swift and easy to use to make hybrid working effective</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple raising prices of Apple Music, Apple One and Apple TV&#43;</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-raising-prices-of-apple-music-apple-one-and-apple-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:12:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-raising-prices-of-apple-music-apple-one-and-apple-tv/</guid>
      <description>Apple raising prices of Apple Music, Apple One and Apple TV+ Streaming budgets are taking another hit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developing the world&#39;s first elephant trunk-mimetic robot hand, capable of gripping even fine needles</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/developing-the-worlds-first-elephant-trunk-mimetic-robot-hand-capable-of-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/developing-the-worlds-first-elephant-trunk-mimetic-robot-hand-capable-of-/</guid>
      <description>Developing the world&amp;rsquo;s first elephant trunk-mimetic robot hand, capable of gripping even fine needles A gripper robot has been developed that can grasp all types of objects, from very fine or thin objects such as acupuncture needles and sewing needles to large objects such as boxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Age of Empires IV Anniversary Update achievements now live</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/age-of-empires-iv-anniversary-update-achievements-now-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/age-of-empires-iv-anniversary-update-achievements-now-live/</guid>
      <description>Age of Empires IV Anniversary Update achievements now live 20 achievements for 310 Gamerscore</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A new kind of wood-based plastic could enable circular home furnishings and building materials</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/a-new-kind-of-wood-based-plastic-could-enable-circular-home-furnishings-and/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 16:55:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/a-new-kind-of-wood-based-plastic-could-enable-circular-home-furnishings-and/</guid>
      <description>A new kind of wood-based plastic could enable circular home furnishings and building materials Plastics used in home furnishings and constructions materials could be replaced with a new kind of wood-based degradable plastic with semi-structural strength.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Studio is getting a brand-new logo</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/android-studio-is-getting-a-brand-new-logo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 16:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/android-studio-is-getting-a-brand-new-logo/</guid>
      <description>Android Studio is getting a brand-new logo Google hosted the Android Developer Summit this week to unveil the latest tools for Android app developers and, quietly, the company also unveiled a new logo for Android Studio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSA: It’s not just you, iMessage is currently down [U]</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/psa-its-not-just-you-imessage-is-currently-down-u/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 16:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/psa-its-not-just-you-imessage-is-currently-down-u/</guid>
      <description>PSA: It’s not just you, iMessage is currently down [U] Update: This outage appears to have been a brief one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guided Frame on the Pixel 7: Who it’s for and how to use it</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/guided-frame-on-the-pixel-7-who-its-for-and-how-to-use-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/guided-frame-on-the-pixel-7-who-its-for-and-how-to-use-it/</guid>
      <description>Guided Frame on the Pixel 7: Who it’s for and how to use it The Pixel 7 brought us an abundance of new camera-focused features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The unlocked Pixel 6a drops to crazy-low price of $299 (33% off) in the wake of Pixel 7</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-unlocked-pixel-6a-drops-to-crazy-low-price-of-299-33-off-in-the-wak/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:42:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-unlocked-pixel-6a-drops-to-crazy-low-price-of-299-33-off-in-the-wak/</guid>
      <description>The unlocked Pixel 6a drops to crazy-low price of $299 (33% off) in the wake of Pixel 7 As we move into the holiday buying season, deals are everywhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Offshore wind power gains international momentum</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/offshore-wind-power-gains-international-momentum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:36:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/offshore-wind-power-gains-international-momentum/</guid>
      <description>Offshore wind power gains international momentum &#34;We can&#39;t just wait for the technology to improve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alphabet to Meta, UK Consumers At Risk From ?Predatory? Big Tech Firms, Report Warns</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/alphabet-to-meta-uk-consumers-at-risk-from-predatory-big-tech-firms-rep/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/alphabet-to-meta-uk-consumers-at-risk-from-predatory-big-tech-firms-rep/</guid>
      <description>Alphabet to Meta, UK Consumers At Risk From ?Predatory? Big Tech Firms, Report Warns UK consumers could be at risk from the ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptoverse: British pound fiasco boosts Bitcoin&#39;s hedge appeal</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cryptoverse-british-pound-fiasco-boosts-bitcoins-hedge-appeal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cryptoverse-british-pound-fiasco-boosts-bitcoins-hedge-appeal/</guid>
      <description>Cryptoverse: British pound fiasco boosts Bitcoin&amp;rsquo;s hedge appeal As a developed nation, you know your currency&#39;s in a spot of bother when investors start to hedge with bitcoin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partial solar eclipse started in Iceland and headed to India</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/partial-solar-eclipse-started-in-iceland-and-headed-to-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/partial-solar-eclipse-started-in-iceland-and-headed-to-india/</guid>
      <description>Partial solar eclipse started in Iceland and headed to India A partial solar eclipse began over Iceland on Tuesday as the rare celestial spectacle started to make its way east across a swathe of the Northern Hemisphere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Webex gains Continuity Camera support in macOS Ventura</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cisco-webex-gains-continuity-camera-support-in-macos-ventura/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cisco-webex-gains-continuity-camera-support-in-macos-ventura/</guid>
      <description>Cisco Webex gains Continuity Camera support in macOS Ventura Apple and Cisco have partnered to help enhance hybrid work on the Mac, with Cisco Webex adding support for Continuity Camera and mobile sharing features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redfall shows off some of its &#34;creepiest bloodsuckers&#34;</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/redfall-shows-off-some-of-its-creepiest-bloodsuckers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/redfall-shows-off-some-of-its-creepiest-bloodsuckers/</guid>
      <description>Redfall shows off some of its &amp;ldquo;creepiest bloodsuckers&amp;rdquo; The co-op action-RPG just debuted a new trailer</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NothingOS 1.1.6 update brings support for Google AR core, fixes max HDR brightness and more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nothingos-116-update-brings-support-for-google-ar-core-fixes-max-hdr-bri/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nothingos-116-update-brings-support-for-google-ar-core-fixes-max-hdr-bri/</guid>
      <description>NothingOS 1.1.6 update brings support for Google AR core, fixes max HDR brightness and more indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung rolls out One UI 5 ‘Maintenance Mode’ to keep your data safe during repair</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-rolls-out-one-ui-5-maintenance-mode-to-keep-your-data-safe-du/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-rolls-out-one-ui-5-maintenance-mode-to-keep-your-data-safe-du/</guid>
      <description>Samsung rolls out One UI 5 ‘Maintenance Mode’ to keep your data safe during repair Handing your phone off to be repaired can be a little anxiety-inducing, given that it contains your valuable info.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study finds Apple Watch blood oxygen sensor is as reliable as ‘medical-grade device’</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/study-finds-apple-watch-blood-oxygen-sensor-is-as-reliable-as-medical-gr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:23:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/study-finds-apple-watch-blood-oxygen-sensor-is-as-reliable-as-medical-gr/</guid>
      <description>Study finds Apple Watch blood oxygen sensor is as reliable as ‘medical-grade device’ A new validation study published this month puts the blood oxygen feature of the Apple Watch to the test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After Massive WhatsApp Outage, Meta Apologizes For Any ?Inconvenience?</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/after-massive-whatsapp-outage-meta-apologizes-for-any-inconvenience/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:23:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/after-massive-whatsapp-outage-meta-apologizes-for-any-inconvenience/</guid>
      <description>After Massive WhatsApp Outage, Meta Apologizes For Any ?Inconvenience? WhatsApp, the instant messaging service owned by Meta Platforms said it fixed an issue that caused a widespread outage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Israeli TikTok star Hadar Muchtar hopes to get out the youth vote</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/israeli-tiktok-star-hadar-muchtar-hopes-to-get-out-the-youth-vote/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/israeli-tiktok-star-hadar-muchtar-hopes-to-get-out-the-youth-vote/</guid>
      <description>Israeli TikTok star Hadar Muchtar hopes to get out the youth vote Ahead of Israel&#39;s elections, a 21-year-old TikTok star has tapped into the economic frustrations of the country&#39;s disaffected youth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>macOS and iOS now support Nintendo&#39;s classic controllers</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/macos-and-ios-now-support-nintendos-classic-controllers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/macos-and-ios-now-support-nintendos-classic-controllers/</guid>
      <description>macOS and iOS now support Nintendo&amp;rsquo;s classic controllers Apple added a surprise for gamers in the tvOS, macOS, iOS, and iPadOS updates, with them all now supporting a pair of nostalgic Nintendo controllers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JD listing reveals Xiaomi Book Air specs - 13&#34; OLED screen in tow</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/jd-listing-reveals-xiaomi-book-air-specs-13-oled-screen-in-tow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/jd-listing-reveals-xiaomi-book-air-specs-13-oled-screen-in-tow/</guid>
      <description>JD listing reveals Xiaomi Book Air specs - 13&amp;quot; OLED screen in tow Earlier today, Xiaomi confirmed its plans to launch a new Windows ultrabook at its Redmi Note 12 series launch event on October 27 and now Chinese online retailer JD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A store that sells Nothing will open in London this year</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/a-store-that-sells-nothing-will-open-in-london-this-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/a-store-that-sells-nothing-will-open-in-london-this-year/</guid>
      <description>A store that sells Nothing will open in London this year Nothing only just released its first phone months ago, but that isn&#39;t stopping the company from establishing a physical retail presence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Six games already confirmed for Game Pass next month</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/six-games-already-confirmed-for-game-pass-next-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/six-games-already-confirmed-for-game-pass-next-month/</guid>
      <description>Six games already confirmed for Game Pass next month With more likely to follow, too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Chrome ditching support for Windows 7 and Windows 8.1 in early 2023</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-chrome-ditching-support-for-windows-7-and-windows-81-in-early-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-chrome-ditching-support-for-windows-7-and-windows-81-in-early-2023/</guid>
      <description>Google Chrome ditching support for Windows 7 and Windows 8.1 in early 2023 If you’re still on an older Windows PC running Windows 7 or Windows 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial intelligence is used for predictive policing in the US and UK—South Africa should embrace it, too</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/artificial-intelligence-is-used-for-predictive-policing-in-the-us-and-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/artificial-intelligence-is-used-for-predictive-policing-in-the-us-and-uk/</guid>
      <description>Artificial intelligence is used for predictive policing in the US and UK—South Africa should embrace it, too In the 2002 movie Minority Report (based on a short story by Philip K Dick), director Steven Spielberg imagined a future in which three psychics can &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How much money you save with Apple One bundles in Fall 2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-much-money-you-save-with-apple-one-bundles-in-fall-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:03:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-much-money-you-save-with-apple-one-bundles-in-fall-2022/</guid>
      <description>How much money you save with Apple One bundles in Fall 2022 With Apple raising the price of most of its subscription services, the new cost of the Apple One bundle can still make it a bargain, in the right circumstances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team develops new method to determine lifespan of lithium-ion batteries</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/team-develops-new-method-to-determine-lifespan-of-lithium-ion-batteries/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/team-develops-new-method-to-determine-lifespan-of-lithium-ion-batteries/</guid>
      <description>Team develops new method to determine lifespan of lithium-ion batteries A University of Missouri engineering team has devised a new way to determine how many times you can recharge a lithium-ion battery before it needs to be replaced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future ‘Doctor Who’ seasons will air on Disney&#43;</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/future-doctor-who-seasons-will-air-on-disney/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/future-doctor-who-seasons-will-air-on-disney/</guid>
      <description>Future ‘Doctor Who’ seasons will air on Disney+ The BBC and Disney have announced future seasons of Doctor Who will stream on Disney+ outside the UK and Ireland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motorola Moto Razr 2022 flip phone arrives in Europe, India launch likely</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/motorola-moto-razr-2022-flip-phone-arrives-in-europe-india-launch-likely/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 14:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/motorola-moto-razr-2022-flip-phone-arrives-in-europe-india-launch-likely/</guid>
      <description>Motorola Moto Razr 2022 flip phone arrives in Europe, India launch likely Motorola has announced the international release of its next-generation flagship foldable smartphone Moto Razr 2022, which comes with Qualcomms’ latest chipset, Snapdragon 8 Plus Gen 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple supplier warns of major drop in smartphone sales ahead of holiday season</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-supplier-warns-of-major-drop-in-smartphone-sales-ahead-of-holiday-sea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 14:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-supplier-warns-of-major-drop-in-smartphone-sales-ahead-of-holiday-sea/</guid>
      <description>Apple supplier warns of major drop in smartphone sales ahead of holiday season An Apple supplier is warning of a significant decline in smartphone demand as we head into the holiday shopping season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google to stop updating Chrome browser on these Windows PCs from 2023</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-to-stop-updating-chrome-browser-on-these-windows-pcs-from-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 14:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-to-stop-updating-chrome-browser-on-these-windows-pcs-from-2023/</guid>
      <description>Google to stop updating Chrome browser on these Windows PCs from 2023 Google’s decision to end support for Windows 7 and Windows 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine learning and signal processing design for edge acoustic applications</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/machine-learning-and-signal-processing-design-for-edge-acoustic-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 14:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/machine-learning-and-signal-processing-design-for-edge-acoustic-application/</guid>
      <description>Machine learning and signal processing design for edge acoustic applications Edge computing is an architecture in which data and processing are placed as close as possible to end users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Nest deals are poppin’</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/these-nest-deals-are-poppin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 14:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/these-nest-deals-are-poppin/</guid>
      <description>These Nest deals are poppin’ Google continues to expand further and further into the hardware space and rumor has it that some new audio devices could be on the horizon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The future of cloud gaming is more than the sum of its parts, but it’s still made up of parts</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-future-of-cloud-gaming-is-more-than-the-sum-of-its-parts-but-its-st/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 14:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-future-of-cloud-gaming-is-more-than-the-sum-of-its-parts-but-its-st/</guid>
      <description>The future of cloud gaming is more than the sum of its parts, but it’s still made up of parts You may be asking yourself why I’m writing about Google Stadia again after the tech giant announced that it would be dead and gone by the new year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GM sidesteps economic headwinds; Q3 profit jumps nearly 37%</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gm-sidesteps-economic-headwinds-q3-profit-jumps-nearly-37/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 14:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gm-sidesteps-economic-headwinds-q3-profit-jumps-nearly-37/</guid>
      <description>GM sidesteps economic headwinds; Q3 profit jumps nearly 37% General Motors&#39; third-quarter net profit rose 36.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung will update these Galaxy devices to Android 13</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-will-update-these-galaxy-devices-to-android-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 14:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-will-update-these-galaxy-devices-to-android-13/</guid>
      <description>Samsung will update these Galaxy devices to Android 13 After launching on Pixel phones earlier this year, Android 13 is now headed to Samsung Galaxy devices outside of a beta program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India fines Google $113 million for abusing the Play Store&#39;s dominance</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-fines-google-113-million-for-abusing-the-play-stores-dominance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 14:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-fines-google-113-million-for-abusing-the-play-stores-dominance/</guid>
      <description>India fines Google $113 million for abusing the Play Store&amp;rsquo;s dominance Google is on the hook for another nine-figure fine after India’s antitrust agency said the company abused the dominant position of the Play Store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Filtration methods remove harmful &#39;forever chemicals&#39; from drinking water</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/filtration-methods-remove-harmful-forever-chemicals-from-drinking-water/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 14:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/filtration-methods-remove-harmful-forever-chemicals-from-drinking-water/</guid>
      <description>Filtration methods remove harmful &amp;lsquo;forever chemicals&amp;rsquo; from drinking water A team of Johns Hopkins engineers has discovered a method to filter out a class of harmful industrial &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Former NFT Marketplace Worker Must Face Insider Trading Charges</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/former-nft-marketplace-worker-must-face-insider-trading-charges/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:25:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/former-nft-marketplace-worker-must-face-insider-trading-charges/</guid>
      <description>Former NFT Marketplace Worker Must Face Insider Trading Charges A former employee of OpenSea, the world?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube introduces precise seeking, pinch to zoom and other improvements</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/youtube-introduces-precise-seeking-pinch-to-zoom-and-other-improvements/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:23:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/youtube-introduces-precise-seeking-pinch-to-zoom-and-other-improvements/</guid>
      <description>YouTube introduces precise seeking, pinch to zoom and other improvements The hours you spend watching YouTube videos are about to get a little more pleasant with the latest user interface improvements that are coming to mobile, desktop and TV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#shotoniphone: Apple CEO Cook extends Diwali wishes; gives shoutout to Indian photographer</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/shotoniphone-apple-ceo-cook-extends-diwali-wishes-gives-shoutout-to-indi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:22:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/shotoniphone-apple-ceo-cook-extends-diwali-wishes-gives-shoutout-to-indi/</guid>
      <description>#shotoniphone: Apple CEO Cook extends Diwali wishes; gives shoutout to Indian photographer Apple CEO Tim Cook attached a photo clicked by a Mumbai-based photographer Apeksha Maker to his Diwali greetings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft starts rolling out Android 12L for Surface Duo, Duo 2: Reports</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/microsoft-starts-rolling-out-android-12l-for-surface-duo-duo-2-reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/microsoft-starts-rolling-out-android-12l-for-surface-duo-duo-2-reports/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft starts rolling out Android 12L for Surface Duo, Duo 2: Reports With Android 12L, users can customise their experience with colour palettes applied across the system, based on their chosen wallpaper</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple releases watchOS 9.1 with battery life improvements, Apple Music upgrades</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-releases-watchos-91-with-battery-life-improvements-apple-music-upgr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-releases-watchos-91-with-battery-life-improvements-apple-music-upgr/</guid>
      <description>Apple releases watchOS 9.1 with battery life improvements, Apple Music upgrades indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Mukesh Ambani Will Use Finance to Tighten DNA Loop: Andy Mukherjee</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-mukesh-ambani-will-use-finance-to-tighten-dna-loop-andy-mukherjee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-mukesh-ambani-will-use-finance-to-tighten-dna-loop-andy-mukherjee/</guid>
      <description>How Mukesh Ambani Will Use Finance to Tighten DNA Loop: Andy Mukherjee Consumers&#39; digital footprints could help the Mukesh Ambani&#39;s financial services ambition and unlock shareholder value, says Andy Mukherjee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp down for hours: 5 alternative messaging apps you can use</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-down-for-hours-5-alternative-messaging-apps-you-can-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-down-for-hours-5-alternative-messaging-apps-you-can-use/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp down for hours: 5 alternative messaging apps you can use The popular Meta-owned instant messaging service is showing a connection error for several users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last partial solar eclipse of 2022 will be visible TODAY in India; know all about the surya grahan</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/last-partial-solar-eclipse-of-2022-will-be-visible-today-in-india-know-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/last-partial-solar-eclipse-of-2022-will-be-visible-today-in-india-know-all/</guid>
      <description>Last partial solar eclipse of 2022 will be visible TODAY in India; know all about the surya grahan Surya grahan 2022: Today, October 25, the last partial solar eclipse of the year will be seen from India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple likely to kill 6.1-inch base iPhone model from next year</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-likely-to-kill-61-inch-base-iphone-model-from-next-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-likely-to-kill-61-inch-base-iphone-model-from-next-year/</guid>
      <description>Apple likely to kill 6.1-inch base iPhone model from next year The rumour had sparked a backlash from many, who took to Twitter to voice out their disapproval of the iPhone 15 Ultra model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Realme 10 Series Specifications Surface Again, Tipped to Launch in November</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/realme-10-series-specifications-surface-again-tipped-to-launch-in-november/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/realme-10-series-specifications-surface-again-tipped-to-launch-in-november/</guid>
      <description>Realme 10 Series Specifications Surface Again, Tipped to Launch in November The TENAA listings of the Realme 10 5G and Realme 10 Pro+ 5G have been updated to reveal the specifications of the two smartphones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Windows 11 bug puts your USB drive at risk!</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/this-windows-11-bug-puts-your-usb-drive-at-risk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/this-windows-11-bug-puts-your-usb-drive-at-risk/</guid>
      <description>This Windows 11 bug puts your USB drive at risk! Windows 11 users have been complaining about a new bug plaguing their systems after the 22H2 update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobileye IPO to be Market Entry for Self-Driving Tech Firm, Intel CEO Says</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mobileye-ipo-to-be-market-entry-for-self-driving-tech-firm-intel-ceo-says/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mobileye-ipo-to-be-market-entry-for-self-driving-tech-firm-intel-ceo-says/</guid>
      <description>Mobileye IPO to be Market Entry for Self-Driving Tech Firm, Intel CEO Says Intel&#39;s initial public offering of its self-driving tech company Mobileye was not a capital raise but part of the company&#39;s efforts to make an entry into the market, CEO Pat Gelsinger said on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp down: Hilarious memes flood Twitter, here are some of the most viral tweets</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-down-hilarious-memes-flood-twitter-here-are-some-of-the-most-vir/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-down-hilarious-memes-flood-twitter-here-are-some-of-the-most-vir/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp down: Hilarious memes flood Twitter, here are some of the most viral tweets WhatsApp, the Meta-owned instant messaging platform is down for several users across India and several parts of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA names 16-person panel tasked with investigating UFOs</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nasa-names-16-person-panel-tasked-with-investigating-ufos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nasa-names-16-person-panel-tasked-with-investigating-ufos/</guid>
      <description>NASA names 16-person panel tasked with investigating UFOs Last June, NASA announced that it would convene a panel to study &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp says working to restore services after users report disruption</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-says-working-to-restore-services-after-users-report-disruption/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-says-working-to-restore-services-after-users-report-disruption/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp says working to restore services after users report disruption New Delhi, October 25 Popular messaging app WhatsApp stopped working for many users across the world, including in India as sending or receiving text and videos snagged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhone photos tips: Get Instagram worthy photos on iPhone in low light with these apps</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/iphone-photos-tips-get-instagram-worthy-photos-on-iphone-in-low-light-with/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/iphone-photos-tips-get-instagram-worthy-photos-on-iphone-in-low-light-with/</guid>
      <description>iPhone photos tips: Get Instagram worthy photos on iPhone in low light with these apps Know simple and easy iPhone photos tips to improve your low-light photography.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whatsapp resumes service after facing global outage</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-resumes-service-after-facing-global-outage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-resumes-service-after-facing-global-outage/</guid>
      <description>Whatsapp resumes service after facing global outage New Delhi, October 25 Popular messaging app WhatsApp faced a global outage from the UK to India, with users being not able to send and receive text and video messages for more than an hour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple&#39;s App Store Said to Start Displaying More Ads From Today: Report</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apples-app-store-said-to-start-displaying-more-ads-from-today-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apples-app-store-said-to-start-displaying-more-ads-from-today-report/</guid>
      <description>Apple&amp;rsquo;s App Store Said to Start Displaying More Ads From Today: Report While ads were previously visible in the App Store, the new ads appearing in the Today tab, will allow better visibility for advertisers, according to a report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Updates App Store Guidelines for NFT Sales: Details</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-updates-app-store-guidelines-for-nft-sales-details/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-updates-app-store-guidelines-for-nft-sales-details/</guid>
      <description>Apple Updates App Store Guidelines for NFT Sales: Details In an update, Apple has restricted apps from using NFTs to encourage consumers to do business outside the company&#39;s purview, potentially circumventing the company&#39;s ability to charge up to 30.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp down today, users rush to Twitter to vent fury</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-down-today-users-rush-to-twitter-to-vent-fury/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:37:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-down-today-users-rush-to-twitter-to-vent-fury/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp down today, users rush to Twitter to vent fury WhatsApp down today messages have flooded social media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redmi Note 12 Pro&#43; 5G camera specifications confirmed ahead of launch</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/redmi-note-12-pro-5g-camera-specifications-confirmed-ahead-of-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/redmi-note-12-pro-5g-camera-specifications-confirmed-ahead-of-launch/</guid>
      <description>Redmi Note 12 Pro+ 5G camera specifications confirmed ahead of launch Redmi Note 12 series is arriving on October 27 and the brand is building hype around it before the launch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Users report problems sending, receiving WhatsApp messages</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/users-report-problems-sending-receiving-whatsapp-messages/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:29:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/users-report-problems-sending-receiving-whatsapp-messages/</guid>
      <description>Users report problems sending, receiving WhatsApp messages People around the world are reporting problems sending and receiving messages on the popular chat app WhatsApp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singapore targets net zero by 2050, eyes hydrogen power</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/singapore-targets-net-zero-by-2050-eyes-hydrogen-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:28:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/singapore-targets-net-zero-by-2050-eyes-hydrogen-power/</guid>
      <description>Singapore targets net zero by 2050, eyes hydrogen power Singapore announced Tuesday it aims to achieve carbon neutrality by 2050, giving a firm date for the first time, and will look at using hydrogen as a major power source.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OnePlus Nord N300 5G with MediaTek processor, 5000mAh battery launched</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oneplus-nord-n300-5g-with-mediatek-processor-5000mah-battery-launched/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oneplus-nord-n300-5g-with-mediatek-processor-5000mah-battery-launched/</guid>
      <description>OnePlus Nord N300 5G with MediaTek processor, 5000mAh battery launched OnePlus Nord N300 5G smartphone is now official.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp outage across India, user unable to send and receive messages</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-outage-across-india-user-unable-to-send-and-receive-messages/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-outage-across-india-user-unable-to-send-and-receive-messages/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp outage across India, user unable to send and receive messages People around the world are reporting problems sending and receiving messages on the popular chat app WhatsApp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp not working: Meta speaks out, this is the latest update</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-not-working-meta-speaks-out-this-is-the-latest-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-not-working-meta-speaks-out-this-is-the-latest-update/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp not working: Meta speaks out, this is the latest update WhatsApp not working: Meta has released a statement on the outage of WhatsApp across the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp is down and messages won&#39;t send - here&#39;s what we know</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-is-down-and-messages-wont-send-heres-what-we-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-is-down-and-messages-wont-send-heres-what-we-know/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp is down and messages won&amp;rsquo;t send - here&amp;rsquo;s what we know WhatsApp appears to be down, with messages not sending.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xiaomi Redmi Note 12 Pro Plus will debut ISOCELL HPX 200MP camera</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/xiaomi-redmi-note-12-pro-plus-will-debut-isocell-hpx-200mp-camera/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/xiaomi-redmi-note-12-pro-plus-will-debut-isocell-hpx-200mp-camera/</guid>
      <description>Xiaomi Redmi Note 12 Pro Plus will debut ISOCELL HPX 200MP camera Yesterday Xiaomi confirmed its plans to launch the Redmi Note 12 series on October 27 and we now get more details about two of the three expected phones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy S22 Series gets Android 13-based One UI 5 update: Check its top features here</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-galaxy-s22-series-gets-android-13-based-one-ui-5-update-check-its-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-galaxy-s22-series-gets-android-13-based-one-ui-5-update-check-its-/</guid>
      <description>Samsung Galaxy S22 Series gets Android 13-based One UI 5 update: Check its top features here Samsung has finally started rolling out Android 13-based One UI 5 update to its Galaxy S22 series smartphones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft updates Surface Duo devices with Android 12L: New features, changes and more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/microsoft-updates-surface-duo-devices-with-android-12l-new-features-chang/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/microsoft-updates-surface-duo-devices-with-android-12l-new-features-chang/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft updates Surface Duo devices with Android 12L: New features, changes and more Android 10 and 11 on Surface Duo devices offered an experience that was very close to the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good news for OnePlus users! OnePlus 10T now supports 5G service, details here</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/good-news-for-oneplus-users-oneplus-10t-now-supports-5g-service-details-h/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/good-news-for-oneplus-users-oneplus-10t-now-supports-5g-service-details-h/</guid>
      <description>Good news for OnePlus users! OnePlus 10T now supports 5G service, details here This OTA will be incremental as usual.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5G service revenue to reach $315 bn globally in 2023</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/5g-service-revenue-to-reach-315-bn-globally-in-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 02:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/5g-service-revenue-to-reach-315-bn-globally-in-2023/</guid>
      <description>5G service revenue to reach $315 bn globally in 2023 This represents growth of over 60 per cent in a single year for operator-billed 5G service revenue, according to Juniper Research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Music, Apple TV&#43;, and Apple One all got more expensive today</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-music-apple-tv-and-apple-one-all-got-more-expensive-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 01:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-music-apple-tv-and-apple-one-all-got-more-expensive-today/</guid>
      <description>Apple Music, Apple TV+, and Apple One all got more expensive today Apple is definitely not fighting against inflation today by raising the prices for three of its services, thus creating some inflation of its own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Third-party MagSafe accessories are about to look a lot nicer</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/third-party-magsafe-accessories-are-about-to-look-a-lot-nicer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/third-party-magsafe-accessories-are-about-to-look-a-lot-nicer/</guid>
      <description>Third-party MagSafe accessories are about to look a lot nicer Third-party MagSafe chargers are about to become much more varied, as Apple is now offering an updated MagSafe module to manufacturers that isn&#39;t the bright white circle that has been standard since launch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Check out the first iPhone apps that support Live Activities and Dynamic Island with iOS 16.1</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/check-out-the-first-iphone-apps-that-support-live-activities-and-dynamic-is/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/check-out-the-first-iphone-apps-that-support-live-activities-and-dynamic-is/</guid>
      <description>Check out the first iPhone apps that support Live Activities and Dynamic Island with iOS 16.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Android tablet &amp; foldable apps would like in Google’s perfect world [Gallery]</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/what-android-tablet-foldable-apps-would-like-in-googles-perfect-world-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/what-android-tablet-foldable-apps-would-like-in-googles-perfect-world-/</guid>
      <description>What Android tablet &amp;amp; foldable apps would like in Google’s perfect world [Gallery] At the Android Developer Summit 2022, Google shared a “Large Screen Gallery” that provides layout guidance for tablet and foldables apps by category: Social media &amp; communication, Media, Productivity, Shopping, and Reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fitbit set for legal faceoff with Australian watchdog over refund and replacement policy</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/fitbit-set-for-legal-faceoff-with-australian-watchdog-over-refund-and-repla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:26:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/fitbit-set-for-legal-faceoff-with-australian-watchdog-over-refund-and-repla/</guid>
      <description>Fitbit set for legal faceoff with Australian watchdog over refund and replacement policy Fitbit has been taken to task by Australia’s competition watchdog for allegedly misleading consumers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xbox sale round-up October 25th, 2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/xbox-sale-round-up-october-25th-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:08:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/xbox-sale-round-up-october-25th-2022/</guid>
      <description>Xbox sale round-up October 25th, 2022 The latest games, bundles And downloadable content sales from Xbox Live</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early Black Friday Samsung TV deals: save up to $3,000 on The Frame, Neo 4K, 8K, OLED TVs</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/early-black-friday-samsung-tv-deals-save-up-to-3000-on-the-frame-neo-4k/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 23:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/early-black-friday-samsung-tv-deals-save-up-to-3000-on-the-frame-neo-4k/</guid>
      <description>Early Black Friday Samsung TV deals: save up to $3,000 on The Frame, Neo 4K, 8K, OLED TVs Samsung has launched Black Friday savings on its TV line, with discounts of up to $3,000 off Neo QLED 4K and 8K panels, as well as The Frame and OLED sets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9to5MacDaily: October 24, 2022 – Apple Music and TV&#43; price increases</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/9to5macdaily-october-24-2022-apple-music-and-tv-price-increases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 23:29:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/9to5macdaily-october-24-2022-apple-music-and-tv-price-increases/</guid>
      <description>9to5MacDaily: October 24, 2022 – Apple Music and TV+ price increases Listen to a recap of the top stories of the day from 9to5Mac.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Majority of people don&#39;t want use of their personal data to result in harm or corporate profit</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/majority-of-people-dont-want-use-of-their-personal-data-to-result-in-harm-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 23:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/majority-of-people-dont-want-use-of-their-personal-data-to-result-in-harm-/</guid>
      <description>Majority of people don&amp;rsquo;t want use of their personal data to result in harm or corporate profit Clear communication about how people&#39;s data is used won&#39;t necessarily alleviate their concerns about it, new research from the University of Sheffield has found.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Children’s hospitals fill up amid up early surge in respiratory infections</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/childrens-hospitals-fill-up-amid-up-early-surge-in-respiratory-infection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 22:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/childrens-hospitals-fill-up-amid-up-early-surge-in-respiratory-infection/</guid>
      <description>Children’s hospitals fill up amid up early surge in respiratory infections Now is the time to get flu shots as well as COVID boosters, experts advise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter employees warn Musk mass layoffs would be &#39;reckless&#39;</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-employees-warn-musk-mass-layoffs-would-be-reckless/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 22:39:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-employees-warn-musk-mass-layoffs-would-be-reckless/</guid>
      <description>Twitter employees warn Musk mass layoffs would be &amp;lsquo;reckless&amp;rsquo; Days before Elon Musk’s deal to acquire Twitter could finally close, workers at the social company are warning that staff cuts would be “reckless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Messages tests new design for delivered and read indicators</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-messages-tests-new-design-for-delivered-and-read-indicators/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 22:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-messages-tests-new-design-for-delivered-and-read-indicators/</guid>
      <description>Google Messages tests new design for delivered and read indicators After rolling out a new icon and previewing several upcoming features last week, Google Messages is now testing new delivered and read status indicators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple finally releases iPadOS 16 alongside iOS 16.1, watchOS 9.1, and tvOS 16.1 - GSMArena.com news - GSMArena.com</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-finally-releases-ipados-16-alongside-ios-161-watchos-91-and-tvos-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 22:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-finally-releases-ipados-16-alongside-ios-161-watchos-91-and-tvos-/</guid>
      <description>Apple finally releases iPadOS 16 alongside iOS 16.1, watchOS 9.1, and tvOS 16.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;ll be paying more for Apple Music, Apple TV&#43;, Apple One subs soon</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/youll-be-paying-more-for-apple-music-apple-tv-apple-one-subs-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 16:52:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/youll-be-paying-more-for-apple-music-apple-tv-apple-one-subs-soon/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ll be paying more for Apple Music, Apple TV+, Apple One subs soon The price of Apple&#39;s main subscription services including Apple Music, is rising by between $1 and $3 per month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Molecular cage protects precious metals in catalytic converters</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/molecular-cage-protects-precious-metals-in-catalytic-converters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 16:48:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/molecular-cage-protects-precious-metals-in-catalytic-converters/</guid>
      <description>Molecular cage protects precious metals in catalytic converters Sometimes, solutions to environmental problems can have environmentally unfriendly side effects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Seen At $25000! Crypto Gets More Attractive as SEC Gets Aggressive, Investors Say</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bitcoin-seen-at-25000-crypto-gets-more-attractive-as-sec-gets-aggressive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 16:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bitcoin-seen-at-25000-crypto-gets-more-attractive-as-sec-gets-aggressive/</guid>
      <description>Bitcoin Seen At $25000! Crypto Gets More Attractive as SEC Gets Aggressive, Investors Say Bitcoin will trade between $17600 and $25000 until the end of this year, survey of market participants shows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sony Xperia Ace IV rumored to feature SD 4 Gen 1 chip and 5.5&#34; FHD&#43; OLED display</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sony-xperia-ace-iv-rumored-to-feature-sd-4-gen-1-chip-and-55-fhd-oled-di/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 16:44:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sony-xperia-ace-iv-rumored-to-feature-sd-4-gen-1-chip-and-55-fhd-oled-di/</guid>
      <description>Sony Xperia Ace IV rumored to feature SD 4 Gen 1 chip and 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climate Change Tops Insurers? Worries With War Close Behind</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/climate-change-tops-insurers-worries-with-war-close-behind/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 16:43:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/climate-change-tops-insurers-worries-with-war-close-behind/</guid>
      <description>Climate Change Tops Insurers? Worries With War Close Behind Climate change remains at the top of insurance companies?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You might think solar panels have been perfected—but we can still make them even better and cheaper</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/you-might-think-solar-panels-have-been-perfectedbut-we-can-still-make-th/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 16:36:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/you-might-think-solar-panels-have-been-perfectedbut-we-can-still-make-th/</guid>
      <description>You might think solar panels have been perfected—but we can still make them even better and cheaper The cost of turning sunlight into electricity has fallen more than 90% over the last decade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPadOS 16.1 review: imperfect preview of what&#39;s next</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ipados-161-review-imperfect-preview-of-whats-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 15:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ipados-161-review-imperfect-preview-of-whats-next/</guid>
      <description>iPadOS 16.1 review: imperfect preview of what&amp;rsquo;s next Apple&#39;s first release of iPadOS 16, iPadOS 16.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PayPal adds passkey support in the US for easier logins and check outs</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/paypal-adds-passkey-support-in-the-us-for-easier-logins-and-check-outs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 15:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/paypal-adds-passkey-support-in-the-us-for-easier-logins-and-check-outs/</guid>
      <description>PayPal adds passkey support in the US for easier logins and check outs PayPal has started rolling out passkeys for users in the US, on the same day Apple is bringing the technology to its computers and tablets with macOS Ventura and iPadOS16.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Buy beats Apple to &#39;MacBook as a subscription service&#39; program</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/best-buy-beats-apple-to-macbook-as-a-subscription-service-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/best-buy-beats-apple-to-macbook-as-a-subscription-service-program/</guid>
      <description>Best Buy beats Apple to &amp;lsquo;MacBook as a subscription service&amp;rsquo; program Electronics retailer Best Buy has launched a Mac equivalent of Apple&#39;s iPhone upgrade program, letting users lease a laptop over a three-year period.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resident Evil Code: Veronica remake not planned but could happen</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/resident-evil-code-veronica-remake-not-planned-but-could-happen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:58:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/resident-evil-code-veronica-remake-not-planned-but-could-happen/</guid>
      <description>Resident Evil Code: Veronica remake not planned but could happen It&#39;s not planned, but if the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>?It is teamwork&#39;, Vikram Sarabhai Space Centre Director after launch of Mark 3 satellite</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/it-is-teamwork-vikram-sarabhai-space-centre-director-after-launch-of-mar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/it-is-teamwork-vikram-sarabhai-space-centre-director-after-launch-of-mar/</guid>
      <description>?It is teamwork&#39;, Vikram Sarabhai Space Centre Director after launch of Mark 3 satellite ISRO team that worked behind Mark 3 satellite mission has reached Thiruvananthapuram.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vivo details X90 series camera upgrades, shares camera samples</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/vivo-details-x90-series-camera-upgrades-shares-camera-samples/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:44:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/vivo-details-x90-series-camera-upgrades-shares-camera-samples/</guid>
      <description>vivo details X90 series camera upgrades, shares camera samples vivo and Zeiss have been hard at work developing the camera technology for the upcoming X90 series of flagships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahsa Amini death protests: Cyber attackers hack into Iran&#39;s atomic energy agency</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mahsa-amini-death-protests-cyber-attackers-hack-into-irans-atomic-energy-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mahsa-amini-death-protests-cyber-attackers-hack-into-irans-atomic-energy-/</guid>
      <description>Mahsa Amini death protests: Cyber attackers hack into Iran&amp;rsquo;s atomic energy agency Built using Russian technology in 2011, Bushehr is Iran&#39;s first nuclear power plant situated along the Persian Gulf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philips CEO Starts Tenure By Cutting 4,000 Jobs Amid Recall Woes</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/philips-ceo-starts-tenure-by-cutting-4000-jobs-amid-recall-woes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/philips-ceo-starts-tenure-by-cutting-4000-jobs-amid-recall-woes/</guid>
      <description>Philips CEO Starts Tenure By Cutting 4,000 Jobs Amid Recall Woes The cuts amount to about 5% of Philips?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>macOS Ventura review: Great features &amp; promise, but not all here yet</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/macos-ventura-review-great-features-promise-but-not-all-here-yet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/macos-ventura-review-great-features-promise-but-not-all-here-yet/</guid>
      <description>macOS Ventura review: Great features &amp;amp; promise, but not all here yet There is much to like in macOS Ventura and many reasons to upgrade, but there are still some oddly rough edges and not all of the new features live up to promises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China&#39;s biggest shopping event: Setback for Alibaba as Singles Day left without superhosts</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/chinas-biggest-shopping-event-setback-for-alibaba-as-singles-day-left-wit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:36:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/chinas-biggest-shopping-event-setback-for-alibaba-as-singles-day-left-wit/</guid>
      <description>China&amp;rsquo;s biggest shopping event: Setback for Alibaba as Singles Day left without superhosts When Alibaba kicks off its Singles Day extravaganza, it will for the first time in years, not be headlined by its two mega sales stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to avoid Nvidia RTX 4090 scams when shopping online during Black Friday</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-avoid-nvidia-rtx-4090-scams-when-shopping-online-during-black-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-avoid-nvidia-rtx-4090-scams-when-shopping-online-during-black-friday/</guid>
      <description>How to avoid Nvidia RTX 4090 scams when shopping online during Black Friday Here&#39;s how you can avoid Nvidia RTX 4090 and other gadget scams when shopping for Black Friday deals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M2 iPad Pro reviews: Much like the M1 model, only a handful of people need it</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/m2-ipad-pro-reviews-much-like-the-m1-model-only-a-handful-of-people-need-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/m2-ipad-pro-reviews-much-like-the-m1-model-only-a-handful-of-people-need-/</guid>
      <description>M2 iPad Pro reviews: Much like the M1 model, only a handful of people need it Alongside reviews of the new 10th-generation entry-level iPad, M2 iPad Pro reviews are also out – and here reviewers speak with one voice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Exchange FTX to Provide $6 Million Phishing Compensation</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/crypto-exchange-ftx-to-provide-6-million-phishing-compensation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/crypto-exchange-ftx-to-provide-6-million-phishing-compensation/</guid>
      <description>Crypto Exchange FTX to Provide $6 Million Phishing Compensation Bankman-Fried proposed in a blog post what he called a ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Level Lock&#43; review, new Apple TV 4K, &amp; Netatmo drops HSV support</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/level-lock-review-new-apple-tv-4k-netatmo-drops-hsv-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/level-lock-review-new-apple-tv-4k-netatmo-drops-hsv-support/</guid>
      <description>Level Lock+ review, new Apple TV 4K, &amp;amp; Netatmo drops HSV support With another week comes another jam-packed episode of Homekit Insider where your hosts review the new Level Lock+, talk about the updated Apple TV 4K, and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube adds pinch-to-zoom on mobile as part of its latest redesign</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/youtube-adds-pinch-to-zoom-on-mobile-as-part-of-its-latest-redesign/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/youtube-adds-pinch-to-zoom-on-mobile-as-part-of-its-latest-redesign/</guid>
      <description>YouTube adds pinch-to-zoom on mobile as part of its latest redesign YouTube is getting a fresh look and some extra features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A strategy to fabricate kesterite solar cells with a 13% efficiency</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/a-strategy-to-fabricate-kesterite-solar-cells-with-a-13-efficiency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/a-strategy-to-fabricate-kesterite-solar-cells-with-a-13-efficiency/</guid>
      <description>A strategy to fabricate kesterite solar cells with a 13% efficiency Kesterite (Cu2ZnSnS4, CZTS) is a sulfide mineral with a unique lattice structure that can be considered as derived from chalcopyrite CuInSe2 (CIS) by substituting two atoms of In3+ in the chalcopyrite by one atom of Zn2+ and one atom of Sn4+.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use third-party 20mm bands with the Google Pixel Watch</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-use-third-party-20mm-bands-with-the-google-pixel-watch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-use-third-party-20mm-bands-with-the-google-pixel-watch/</guid>
      <description>How to use third-party 20mm bands with the Google Pixel Watch One of the biggest complaints with the Pixel Watch is that Google is using a proprietary band system that limits choices drastically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use Continuity Camera in iOS 16 and macOS Ventura</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-use-continuity-camera-in-ios-16-and-macos-ventura/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 11:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-use-continuity-camera-in-ios-16-and-macos-ventura/</guid>
      <description>How to use Continuity Camera in iOS 16 and macOS Ventura Continuity Camera allows you to use your iPhone&#39;s camera to insert photos or documents in your Mac and use it as a FaceTime camera as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Masimo “Apple Watch clone” was based on access to confidential info and source code</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/masimo-apple-watch-clone-was-based-on-access-to-confidential-info-and/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 11:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/masimo-apple-watch-clone-was-based-on-access-to-confidential-info-and/</guid>
      <description>Masimo “Apple Watch clone” was based on access to confidential info and source code Update: Apple has now filed a second lawsuit, this one revealing that Masimo was given access to confidential information and source code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Morning After: Bono finally apologizes for that free iTunes U2 album</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-morning-after-bono-finally-apologizes-for-that-free-itunes-u2-album/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 11:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-morning-after-bono-finally-apologizes-for-that-free-itunes-u2-album/</guid>
      <description>The Morning After: Bono finally apologizes for that free iTunes U2 album Once upon a time, back in 2014, U2 gave away an album&#39;s worth of songs to every iTunes user in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Windows 11 feature will make file sharing easier; Update now</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/this-windows-11-feature-will-make-file-sharing-easier-update-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 11:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/this-windows-11-feature-will-make-file-sharing-easier-update-now/</guid>
      <description>This Windows 11 feature will make file sharing easier; Update now Windows 11 users just got a new update that will make file sharing and photos management easier than before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bono memoir reveals the story behind the free U2 album debacle (and U2 iPod)</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bono-memoir-reveals-the-story-behind-the-free-u2-album-debacle-and-u2-ipod/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 11:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bono-memoir-reveals-the-story-behind-the-free-u2-album-debacle-and-u2-ipod/</guid>
      <description>Bono memoir reveals the story behind the free U2 album debacle (and U2 iPod) A memoir by Irish singer-songwriter Bono reveals the story behind the free U2 album debacle, which saw both Apple and the band become the butt of jokes on social media, as well as the subject of considerable anger toward both parties … more… The post Bono memoir reveals the story behind the free U2 album debacle (and U2 iPod) appeared first on 9to5Mac.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily deals Oct. 24: $99 Apple TV 4K 32GB, $90 Beats Studio Buds, $50 Amazon Echo, more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/daily-deals-oct-24-99-apple-tv-4k-32gb-90-beats-studio-buds-50-amazo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 11:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/daily-deals-oct-24-99-apple-tv-4k-32gb-90-beats-studio-buds-50-amazo/</guid>
      <description>Daily deals Oct. 24: $99 Apple TV 4K 32GB, $90 Beats Studio Buds, $50 Amazon Echo, more Monday&#39;s best deals include an $89 Apple Pencil Gen 2, $80 off a Dell 27-inch UltraSharp monitor, $100 off Beats Powerbeats Pro, and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use the Clock app in macOS Ventura</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-use-the-clock-app-in-macos-ventura/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 11:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-use-the-clock-app-in-macos-ventura/</guid>
      <description>How to use the Clock app in macOS Ventura Apple has finally migrated the Clock app to the Mac with the arrival of macOS Ventura.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Pass Soulslike Lies of P length and DLC plans detailed</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/game-pass-soulslike-lies-of-p-length-and-dlc-plans-detailed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 11:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/game-pass-soulslike-lies-of-p-length-and-dlc-plans-detailed/</guid>
      <description>Game Pass Soulslike Lies of P length and DLC plans detailed Director Choi Ji-Won has revealed how long it will take to beat Lies of P</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSA: Yes, you can charge your Pixel Buds with the Pixel Watch charger</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/psa-yes-you-can-charge-your-pixel-buds-with-the-pixel-watch-charger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 11:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/psa-yes-you-can-charge-your-pixel-buds-with-the-pixel-watch-charger/</guid>
      <description>PSA: Yes, you can charge your Pixel Buds with the Pixel Watch charger Annoyingly you can’t charge the Pixel Watch using your phone or another Qi charger, but we have some good news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The iPhone 14 Pro Review: The Best iPhone Humankind Can Get, Yet!</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-iphone-14-pro-review-the-best-iphone-humankind-can-get-yet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 10:48:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-iphone-14-pro-review-the-best-iphone-humankind-can-get-yet/</guid>
      <description>The iPhone 14 Pro Review: The Best iPhone Humankind Can Get, Yet!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk visits Monterrey, Nuevo León, Mexico &amp; chats with officials</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-visits-monterrey-nuevo-len-mexico-chats-with-officials/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 21:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-visits-monterrey-nuevo-len-mexico-chats-with-officials/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk visits Monterrey, Nuevo León, Mexico &amp;amp; chats with officials Tesla CEO Elon Musk took a trip to Nuevo León, Mexico, this weekend, where he was spotted talking with a state official and the wife of Governor Samuel García Sepulveda, Mariana Rodríguez.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wordle 492 answer for today: Here is the Wordle answer for October 24</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/wordle-492-answer-for-today-here-is-the-wordle-answer-for-october-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 18:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/wordle-492-answer-for-today-here-is-the-wordle-answer-for-october-24/</guid>
      <description>Wordle 492 answer for today: Here is the Wordle answer for October 24 To help you out, here is the Wordle 492 answer for October 24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Doodle celebrates the life of country singer Slim Dusty</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-doodle-celebrates-the-life-of-country-singer-slim-dusty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 17:42:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-doodle-celebrates-the-life-of-country-singer-slim-dusty/</guid>
      <description>Google Doodle celebrates the life of country singer Slim Dusty Today’s limited Google Doodle celebrates the late great Australian country singer Slim Dusty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bitcoin Futures ETF at 1: $1.8 Billion Lured, Over Half Lost</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-bitcoin-futures-etf-at-1-18-billion-lured-over-half-lost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 17:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-bitcoin-futures-etf-at-1-18-billion-lured-over-half-lost/</guid>
      <description>The Bitcoin Futures ETF at 1: $1.8 Billion Lured, Over Half Lost A year on from its blistering debut, America?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moonlighting unacceptable: Happiest Minds</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/moonlighting-unacceptable-happiest-minds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 17:36:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/moonlighting-unacceptable-happiest-minds/</guid>
      <description>Moonlighting unacceptable: Happiest Minds Happiest Minds had about 4,581 employees as of September 30, 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple iPhone owners report Face ID issues after iOS update, know more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-iphone-owners-report-face-id-issues-after-ios-update-know-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 17:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/apple-iphone-owners-report-face-id-issues-after-ios-update-know-more/</guid>
      <description>Apple iPhone owners report Face ID issues after iOS update, know more MacRumours claims that there were issues with resetting Face ID on Apple devices with iOS 15.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly poll: will you buy an iPad Pro (2022)? How about a vanilla iPad (2022)?</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/weekly-poll-will-you-buy-an-ipad-pro-2022-how-about-a-vanilla-ipad-202/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 17:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/weekly-poll-will-you-buy-an-ipad-pro-2022-how-about-a-vanilla-ipad-202/</guid>
      <description>Weekly poll: will you buy an iPad Pro (2022)? How about a vanilla iPad (2022)?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to manage and maintain your Google Passwords like a pro</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-manage-and-maintain-your-google-passwords-like-a-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 17:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-manage-and-maintain-your-google-passwords-like-a-pro/</guid>
      <description>How to manage and maintain your Google Passwords like a pro Despite the fact that most people (yes, even you and I) completely disregard the health and wellness of our digital footprint, it doesn’t mean it’s not important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flipkart Big Diwali Sale: Ordered gaming laptop from Flipkart received a giant stone and e-waste</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/flipkart-big-diwali-sale-ordered-gaming-laptop-from-flipkart-received-a-gi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 13:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/flipkart-big-diwali-sale-ordered-gaming-laptop-from-flipkart-received-a-gi/</guid>
      <description>Flipkart Big Diwali Sale: Ordered gaming laptop from Flipkart received a giant stone and e-waste Chinmaya Ramana of Mangalore, Karnataka ordered a gaming laptop on Flipkart in the Big Diwali Sale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp to soon bring customised &#39;Avatars&#39; for beta testers</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-to-soon-bring-customised-avatars-for-beta-testers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 09:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-to-soon-bring-customised-avatars-for-beta-testers/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp to soon bring customised &amp;lsquo;Avatars&amp;rsquo; for beta testers WhatsApp to soon launch personalised &#39;Avatars&#39; for some beta users.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
