<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Editor&#39;s picks on TechnoStreet</title>
    <link>https://technostreet.github.io/tags/editors-picks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Editor&#39;s picks on TechnoStreet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 04:05:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://technostreet.github.io/tags/editors-picks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Amazon begins layoffs in India, informs affected employees over email and promises them 5 months of severance pay</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/amazon-begins-layoffs-in-india-informs-affected-employees-over-email-and-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 04:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/amazon-begins-layoffs-in-india-informs-affected-employees-over-email-and-p/</guid>
      <description>Amazon begins layoffs in India, informs affected employees over email and promises them 5 months of severance pay Amazon CEO Andy Jassy had earlier announced that the e-commerce giant will lay off over 18,000 employees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead body of a girl found on the Eastern Peripheral Highway in Greater Noida, her head crushed, probe initiated</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dead-body-of-a-girl-found-on-the-eastern-peripheral-highway-in-greater-noid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 05:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dead-body-of-a-girl-found-on-the-eastern-peripheral-highway-in-greater-noid/</guid>
      <description>Dead body of a girl found on the Eastern Peripheral Highway in Greater Noida, her head crushed, probe initiated Initial probe suggests that the girl&#39;s head was smashed to conceal her identity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>As global media reports ring alarm over rising Covid cases in China, Global Times, the CCP mouthpiece says ‘all is well’</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/as-global-media-reports-ring-alarm-over-rising-covid-cases-in-china-global/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 06:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/as-global-media-reports-ring-alarm-over-rising-covid-cases-in-china-global/</guid>
      <description>As global media reports ring alarm over rising Covid cases in China, Global Times, the CCP mouthpiece says ‘all is well’ The World Health Organisation (WHO) on December 22 expressed concerns over the unprecedented wave of Covid cases in China and asked it to accelerate vaccination of the most vulnerable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New CCTV footage from Tihar shows Satyendar Jain having lavish meal, fresh-cut salad, fruits; jail authorities say he has gained 8 kgs weight</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-cctv-footage-from-tihar-shows-satyendar-jain-having-lavish-meal-fresh-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 05:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-cctv-footage-from-tihar-shows-satyendar-jain-having-lavish-meal-fresh-/</guid>
      <description>New CCTV footage from Tihar shows Satyendar Jain having lavish meal, fresh-cut salad, fruits; jail authorities say he has gained 8 kgs weight Earlier it was revealed that the person giving massage to Jain in leaked video was child rape accused.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After attacking Adani and Ambani ad nauseam, Alt News’ out-on-bail Mohammed Zubair begs Elon Musk to invest in Indian media</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/after-attacking-adani-and-ambani-ad-nauseam-alt-news-out-on-bail-mohamm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 11:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/after-attacking-adani-and-ambani-ad-nauseam-alt-news-out-on-bail-mohamm/</guid>
      <description>After attacking Adani and Ambani ad nauseam, Alt News’ out-on-bail Mohammed Zubair begs Elon Musk to invest in Indian media Alt News co-founder Mohammed Zubair recently asked Twitter CEO Elon Musk to invest in Indian media.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
