<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>health on TechnoStreet</title>
    <link>https://technostreet.github.io/categories/health/</link>
    <description>Recent content in health on TechnoStreet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 05:02:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://technostreet.github.io/categories/health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>आयुर्वेद डॉ का दावा- सिर्फ 3 हफ्ते में इन 5 टिप्स से कम होने लगेगा बॉडी में जमा फैट</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-3-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 05:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-3-/</guid>
      <description>आयुर्वेद डॉ का दावा- सिर्फ 3 हफ्ते में इन 5 टिप्स से कम होने लगेगा बॉडी में जमा फैट मोटापा (Obesity) खराब जीवनशैली से संबंधित स्थिति है। यह कुछ मामलों में किसी बीमारी के कारण भी हो सकती है। इसे समय रहते कम नहीं किया जाए तो यह कोलेस्ट्रॉल, हाई बीपी, स्ट्रोक और हार्ट अटैक जैसी जानलेवा बीमारियों का कारण भी बन सकती है। लेकिन वेट लॉस करने की मुश्किलों को देखते हुए कई लोग मोटापे को गंभीरता से नहीं लेते हैं। आपको बता दें वजन कम करना इतना भी मुश्किल नहीं है, जितना इसे फिल्मों और विज्ञापनों में बताया जाता है। यदि आप सही विकल्पों को चुनते हैं, तो आपकी वेट लॉस जर्नी (Weight Loss Journey) बिना खान-पान से परहेज किए और जिम में घंटों पसीना बहाए बिना ही पूरी हो सकती है। आयुर्वेद विशेषज्ञ डॉक्टर दीक्षा भावसार ने हाल ही में ठंड में वेट लॉस (Weight Loss Winter Tips) के लिए आसान और असरदार कुछ उपायों को अपने इंस्टाग्राम पर शेयर किया है। इन आयुर्वेदिक वेट लॉस टिप्स के बारे में उनका दावा है कि इसे नियमित फॉलो करके सिर्फ 3 हफ्ते में वजन कम किया जा सकता है।</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rahul Gandhi braves Delhi temperatures in just a T-shirt: The science of people feeling cold</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rahul-gandhi-braves-delhi-temperatures-in-just-a-t-shirt-the-science-of-pe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 07:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rahul-gandhi-braves-delhi-temperatures-in-just-a-t-shirt-the-science-of-pe/</guid>
      <description>Rahul Gandhi braves Delhi temperatures in just a T-shirt: The science of people feeling cold Rahul Gandhi braves Delhi temperatures in just a T-shirt: The science of people feeling cold</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breakfast Recipe: सर्दियों में नाश्ते में बनाएं गाजर का पराठा, हर कोई खा जाएगा 4-5, यहां जानें इसकी क्विक रेसिपी</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/breakfast-recipe-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 02:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/breakfast-recipe-/</guid>
      <description>Breakfast Recipe: सर्दियों में नाश्ते में बनाएं गाजर का पराठा, हर कोई खा जाएगा 4-5, यहां जानें इसकी क्विक रेसिपी Gajar Paratha Recipe: सर्दियों में नाश्ते में आलू पराठा, मूली का पराठा खाकर बोर हो गए हैं तो अब बनाएं गाजर का पराठा.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bahubali Thali: एक थाली में 25 आइटम, कीमत इतनी कि कार की आधी टंकी भर जाएगी</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bahubali-thali-25-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 07:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bahubali-thali-25-/</guid>
      <description>Bahubali Thali: एक थाली में 25 आइटम, कीमत इतनी कि कार की आधी टंकी भर जाएगी बाहुबली ढाबे की बाहुबली थाली की बात की जाए तो इस थाली में करीब 25 से अधिक व्यंजन परोसे जाते हैं.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Street Food: मुंगेर की यह सीजनल मिठाई है बेहद लजीज़, मिठास के शौकीनों की है पहली पसंद</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/street-food-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 07:37:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/street-food-/</guid>
      <description>Street Food: मुंगेर की यह सीजनल मिठाई है बेहद लजीज़, मिठास के शौकीनों की है पहली पसंद मुंगेर के हवेली खड़गपुर प्रखंड के मुजफ्फरगंज गांव को स्पेशल खोवा के लाय से भी पहचाना जाता है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas 2022: ये हैं दिल्ली के वे 7 होटल-रेस्त्रां, जहां आप जमकर एंजॉय कर सकते हैं क्रिसमस</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/christmas-2022-7-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 07:02:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/christmas-2022-7-/</guid>
      <description>Christmas 2022: ये हैं दिल्ली के वे 7 होटल-रेस्त्रां, जहां आप जमकर एंजॉय कर सकते हैं क्रिसमस Christmas 2022: क्रिसमस (christmas) का त्योहार नजदीक आ चुका है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stroke And Diabetes: डायबिटीज के रोगियों को स्ट्रोक का रहता है ज्यादा खतरा, जानें इसका कारण</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/stroke-and-diabetes-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 10:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/stroke-and-diabetes-/</guid>
      <description>Stroke And Diabetes: डायबिटीज के रोगियों को स्ट्रोक का रहता है ज्यादा खतरा, जानें इसका कारण Stroke And Diabetes: स्ट्रोक एक गंभीर मेडिकल कंडीशन है अगर इस पर समय रहते ध्यान नहीं दिया गया तो यह मरीज के लिए जानलेवा साबित हो सकता है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Fishing Trips To Take This Summer</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-best-fishing-trips-to-take-this-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 05:12:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-best-fishing-trips-to-take-this-summer/</guid>
      <description>The Best Fishing Trips To Take This Summer Summer is a time for vacations, pool days, and of course, fishing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>महिलाएं Winter Blues से इस तरह खुद को उबारें, निराशा और उदासी से मिलेगी निजात</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-winter-blues-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 02:39:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-winter-blues-/</guid>
      <description>महिलाएं Winter Blues से इस तरह खुद को उबारें, निराशा और उदासी से मिलेगी निजात सर्दी आते ही दिन छोटे हो जाते हैं और रोशनी की कमी हो जाती है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diabetes control: टाइप 1 डायबिटीज को जड़ से खत्म करने की दवा तैयार, अमेरिका में मिली इस्तेमाल की मंजूरी</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/diabetes-control-1-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 15:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/diabetes-control-1-/</guid>
      <description>Diabetes control: टाइप 1 डायबिटीज को जड़ से खत्म करने की दवा तैयार, अमेरिका में मिली इस्तेमाल की मंजूरी Type 1 diabetes treatment: टाइप 1 डायबिटीज बच्चों और किशोरों में होने वाली गंभीर बीमारी है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More babies, lower risk of endometrial cancer</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/more-babies-lower-risk-of-endometrial-cancer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 03:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/more-babies-lower-risk-of-endometrial-cancer/</guid>
      <description>More babies, lower risk of endometrial cancer While many highly industrialized and developed countries report falling or negative population growth rates due to a rapid decrease in the number of babies born each year, a new report adds more strength to the evidence that bearing a baby has a protective effect on the endometrium, the lining of the womb, reducing the risk of endometrial cancer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food sustainability incorporated in only 20% of European food-based dietary guidelines</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/food-sustainability-incorporated-in-only-20-of-european-food-based-dietary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 03:50:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/food-sustainability-incorporated-in-only-20-of-european-food-based-dietary/</guid>
      <description>Food sustainability incorporated in only 20% of European food-based dietary guidelines The health of the planet and that of humankind are profoundly interconnected: the way we feed ourselves has a significant impact upon both our own health and that of the environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chromosomal microarray analysis could help identify the cause of SIDS or SUDC in older children</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/chromosomal-microarray-analysis-could-help-identify-the-cause-of-sids-or-su/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 16:55:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/chromosomal-microarray-analysis-could-help-identify-the-cause-of-sids-or-su/</guid>
      <description>Chromosomal microarray analysis could help identify the cause of SIDS or SUDC in older children A genetic test known as chromosomal microarray analysis (CMA) could help identify the cause of sudden infant death syndrome (SIDS) or its counterpart in older children, known as sudden unexplained death in childhood (SUDC), finds a study led by Boston Children&#39;s Hospital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beer hop compounds could serve as the basis for nutraceuticals to combat Alzheimer’s disease</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/beer-hop-compounds-could-serve-as-the-basis-for-nutraceuticals-to-combat-al/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 16:44:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/beer-hop-compounds-could-serve-as-the-basis-for-nutraceuticals-to-combat-al/</guid>
      <description>Beer hop compounds could serve as the basis for nutraceuticals to combat Alzheimer’s disease Beer is one of the oldest and most popular beverages in the world, with some people loving and others hating the distinct, bitter taste of the hops used to flavor its many varieties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EKF to showcase POCT connectivity solutions at MEDICA 2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ekf-to-showcase-poct-connectivity-solutions-at-medica-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 16:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ekf-to-showcase-poct-connectivity-solutions-at-medica-2022/</guid>
      <description>EKF to showcase POCT connectivity solutions at MEDICA 2022 EKF Diagnostics, a global diagnostics company, will be introducing its latest product developments and offerings at MEDICA 2022, Düsseldorf, Germany, 14-17 November.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Psilocybin could be a promising therapeutic strategy for people with treatment-resistant depression</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/psilocybin-could-be-a-promising-therapeutic-strategy-for-people-with-treatm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 16:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/psilocybin-could-be-a-promising-therapeutic-strategy-for-people-with-treatm/</guid>
      <description>Psilocybin could be a promising therapeutic strategy for people with treatment-resistant depression Researchers at Trinity College Dublin have participated in the largest and most rigorous clinical trial to date of psilocybin (a psychoactive ingredient in magic mushrooms), pointing to the possibility that COMP360 psilocybin with psychological support could be a beneficial therapeutic strategy for people with treatment-resistant depression (TRD).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planning on sleeping in? Your productivity can get affected</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/planning-on-sleeping-in-your-productivity-can-get-affected/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 07:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/planning-on-sleeping-in-your-productivity-can-get-affected/</guid>
      <description>Planning on sleeping in? Your productivity can get affected By observing biological rhythms and everyday preferences, Fogel`s team was able to determine a person`s chronotype--their morning or evening proclivities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>स्वस्थ बालों के लिए 5 आवश्यक पोषक तत्व, इन फूड्स से करें इनकी कमी दूर</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-5-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 05:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-5-/</guid>
      <description>स्वस्थ बालों के लिए 5 आवश्यक पोषक तत्व, इन फूड्स से करें इनकी कमी दूर कुछ स्थितियां हमारी स्कैल्प और बालों के स्वास्थ्य पर प्रभाव डाल सकती हैं, इसलिए यदि आपके बाल अचानक झड़ने लगें, तो इसके मुख्य कारणों को जानने के लिए हेयर स्पेशलिस्ट या डॉक्टर की सलाह लेना बहुत ज़रूरी है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Vestibular Hypofunction disorder? All about the disease, Varun Dhawan is diagnosed with</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/what-is-vestibular-hypofunction-disorder-all-about-the-disease-varun-dhaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 04:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/what-is-vestibular-hypofunction-disorder-all-about-the-disease-varun-dhaw/</guid>
      <description>What is Vestibular Hypofunction disorder? All about the disease, Varun Dhawan is diagnosed with Actor Varun Dhawan recently shared his health update and his diagnosis of Vestibular Hypofunction disorder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>H pylori eradication protects against aspirin-associated peptic ulcer bleeding</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/h-pylori-eradication-protects-against-aspirin-associated-peptic-ulcer-bleed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 07:29:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/h-pylori-eradication-protects-against-aspirin-associated-peptic-ulcer-bleed/</guid>
      <description>H pylori eradication protects against aspirin-associated peptic ulcer bleeding A new study, led by experts at the University of Nottingham found that the risk of stomach bleeding caused by using aspirin long-term, can be reduced with a short course of antibiotics, potentially improving the safety of aspirin when used to prevent heart attacks, strokes and possibly some cancers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast Weight Loss: वेट लॉस की तैयारी कर रहे लोगों को जरूर फॉलो करने चाहिए ये 5 स्टेप्स</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/fast-weight-loss-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 04:28:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/fast-weight-loss-/</guid>
      <description>Fast Weight Loss: वेट लॉस की तैयारी कर रहे लोगों को जरूर फॉलो करने चाहिए ये 5 स्टेप्स Weight Loss Tips: बढ़ते वजन की समस्या हमेशा से ही उन लोगों के लिए परेशानी खड़ी करती है, जिन्हें फिट रहना पसंद है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australian Digital Health Agency and CSIRO collaborate to improve the connectedness of Australia’s healthcare system</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/australian-digital-health-agency-and-csiro-collaborate-to-improve-the-conne/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 13:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/australian-digital-health-agency-and-csiro-collaborate-to-improve-the-conne/</guid>
      <description>Australian Digital Health Agency and CSIRO collaborate to improve the connectedness of Australia’s healthcare system The Australian Digital Health Agency and Australia’s national science agency, CSIRO’s Australian e-Health Research Centre (AEHRC) have launched a new collaboration combining their skills and expertise to deliver a centre of excellence for connectivity across the Australian healthcare system, through the National Clinical Terminology Service (NCTS).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investigating the role of the gut-to-brain axis in defensive responses</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/investigating-the-role-of-the-gut-to-brain-axis-in-defensive-responses/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 13:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/investigating-the-role-of-the-gut-to-brain-axis-in-defensive-responses/</guid>
      <description>Investigating the role of the gut-to-brain axis in defensive responses In a new study, researchers investigated the function of the gut-to-brain axis in defensive responses induced by toxins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cedars-Sinai experts to present innovative heart research data during AHA Scientific Sessions 2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cedars-sinai-experts-to-present-innovative-heart-research-data-during-aha-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cedars-sinai-experts-to-present-innovative-heart-research-data-during-aha-s/</guid>
      <description>Cedars-Sinai experts to present innovative heart research data during AHA Scientific Sessions 2022 During American Heart Association Scientific Sessions 2022, Prominent Cedars-Sinai Cardiologists, Cardiothoracic Surgeons and Interventionalists Available for Interviews</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research reveals how whole-genome sequencing may enhance detection of fetal CNS anomalies</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/research-reveals-how-whole-genome-sequencing-may-enhance-detection-of-fetal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/research-reveals-how-whole-genome-sequencing-may-enhance-detection-of-fetal/</guid>
      <description>Research reveals how whole-genome sequencing may enhance detection of fetal CNS anomalies BGI-Research and the Maternal and Child Health Hospital of Hubei Province (MCHH) published whole-genome sequencing research results in npj Genomic Medicine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study highlights the benefits of eccentric-focused training</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/study-highlights-the-benefits-of-eccentric-focused-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 06:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/study-highlights-the-benefits-of-eccentric-focused-training/</guid>
      <description>Study highlights the benefits of eccentric-focused training Good news for those who struggle to fit a gym workout into their day: you may be able to cut your weights routine in half and still see the same results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New method to estimate the contribution of each amino acid residue</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-method-to-estimate-the-contribution-of-each-amino-acid-residue/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 05:55:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-method-to-estimate-the-contribution-of-each-amino-acid-residue/</guid>
      <description>New method to estimate the contribution of each amino acid residue You can&#39;t expect a pharmaceutical scientist to switch labs to the facilities available in a television studio and expect the same research output.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effect of marital stress on heart attack recovery is detrimental</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/effect-of-marital-stress-on-heart-attack-recovery-is-detrimental/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 02:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/effect-of-marital-stress-on-heart-attack-recovery-is-detrimental/</guid>
      <description>Effect of marital stress on heart attack recovery is detrimental In a recent study soon to be presented at the American Heart Association (AHA) Scientific Sessions 2022*, researchers examined the adverse effects of marital stress (MS) on recovery from acute myocardial infarction (AMI).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personalized approach to kidney disease screening for T1D patients could enable earlier disease detection</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/personalized-approach-to-kidney-disease-screening-for-t1d-patients-could-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 16:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/personalized-approach-to-kidney-disease-screening-for-t1d-patients-could-en/</guid>
      <description>Personalized approach to kidney disease screening for T1D patients could enable earlier disease detection Taking a personalized approach to kidney disease screening for people with type 1 diabetes (T1D) may reduce the time that chronic kidney disease goes undetected, according to a new analysis performed by the Epidemiology of Diabetes Interventions and Complications study group, which is funded by the National Institute of Diabetes and Digestive and Kidney Diseases, part of the National Institutes of Health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 takeaways from our daily meeting: Stocks await Fed decision, Club earnings recap</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/2-takeaways-from-our-daily-meeting-stocks-await-fed-decision-club-earning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 16:09:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/2-takeaways-from-our-daily-meeting-stocks-await-fed-decision-club-earning/</guid>
      <description>2 takeaways from our daily meeting: Stocks await Fed decision, Club earnings recap The Investing Club holds its &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An optimal approach to treat femoropopliteal lesions</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/an-optimal-approach-to-treat-femoropopliteal-lesions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 07:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/an-optimal-approach-to-treat-femoropopliteal-lesions/</guid>
      <description>An optimal approach to treat femoropopliteal lesions New research published in the Journal of the American College of Cardiology shows the use of drug-coated balloons is an optimal approach compared to bare metal stents in treating femoropopliteal lesions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nutrition-related content on TikTok may contribute to disordered eating behaviors</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nutrition-related-content-on-tiktok-may-contribute-to-disordered-eating-beh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 07:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nutrition-related-content-on-tiktok-may-contribute-to-disordered-eating-beh/</guid>
      <description>Nutrition-related content on TikTok may contribute to disordered eating behaviors New research from the University of Vermont finds the most viewed content on TikTok relating to food, nutrition and weight perpetuates a toxic diet culture among teens and young adults and that expert voices are largely missing from the conversation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 steps to reduce stress for a better sex life - check here</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/7-steps-to-reduce-stress-for-a-better-sex-life-check-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 07:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/7-steps-to-reduce-stress-for-a-better-sex-life-check-here/</guid>
      <description>7 steps to reduce stress for a better sex life - check here Stress plays a role in both sexual performance and sperm health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vaginal progesterone may not be effective for preventing preterm births</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/vaginal-progesterone-may-not-be-effective-for-preventing-preterm-births/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 03:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/vaginal-progesterone-may-not-be-effective-for-preventing-preterm-births/</guid>
      <description>Vaginal progesterone may not be effective for preventing preterm births Vaginal progesterone, a hormone treatment considered the standard of care for preventing preterm birth in at-risk pregnant women, may not be effective, according to UT Southwestern Medical Center researchers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleep Research Society&#39;s new position statement advocates the elimination of daylight saving time</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sleep-research-societys-new-position-statement-advocates-the-elimination-o/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 17:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sleep-research-societys-new-position-statement-advocates-the-elimination-o/</guid>
      <description>Sleep Research Society&amp;rsquo;s new position statement advocates the elimination of daylight saving time With the annual change from daylight saving time to standard time approaching on Sunday, Nov.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dietary components do not have impact on RMD outcomes</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dietary-components-do-not-have-impact-on-rmd-outcomes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 17:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dietary-components-do-not-have-impact-on-rmd-outcomes/</guid>
      <description>Dietary components do not have impact on RMD outcomes In 2022, EULAR - the European Alliance of Rheumatology Associations - published new recommendations regarding lifestyle behaviors and work participation to prevent progression of rheumatic and musculoskeletal diseases (RMDs).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Novel troponin test may help improve the treatment of heart attack patients</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/novel-troponin-test-may-help-improve-the-treatment-of-heart-attack-patients/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/novel-troponin-test-may-help-improve-the-treatment-of-heart-attack-patients/</guid>
      <description>Novel troponin test may help improve the treatment of heart attack patients A new test has been developed in Turku, Finland, that helps in separating heart attack patients from those whose cardiac troponin values are elevated due to renal insufficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the safety and immunogenicity of KD-414, a novel SARS-CoV-2 vaccine</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/exploring-the-safety-and-immunogenicity-of-kd-414-a-novel-sars-cov-2-vacci/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/exploring-the-safety-and-immunogenicity-of-kd-414-a-novel-sars-cov-2-vacci/</guid>
      <description>Exploring the safety and immunogenicity of KD-414, a novel SARS-CoV-2 vaccine In a new study, researchers assessed the immunogenicity and safety of KD-414, an inactivated severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2) vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High incidence of CKD in the United States persists, study says</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/high-incidence-of-ckd-in-the-united-states-persists-study-says/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 06:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/high-incidence-of-ckd-in-the-united-states-persists-study-says/</guid>
      <description>High incidence of CKD in the United States persists, study says New onset chronic kidney disease (CKD) in people with diabetes is highest among racial and ethnic minority groups compared with white persons, a UCLA-Providence study finds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High-throughput sequencing reveals structured olfactory neuron projections</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/high-throughput-sequencing-reveals-structured-olfactory-neuron-projections/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 06:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/high-throughput-sequencing-reveals-structured-olfactory-neuron-projections/</guid>
      <description>High-throughput sequencing reveals structured olfactory neuron projections Our sense of smell has a powerful effect on our behavior and emotions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breastfeeding support extends breastfeeding duration and exclusivity</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/breastfeeding-support-extends-breastfeeding-duration-and-exclusivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 01:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/breastfeeding-support-extends-breastfeeding-duration-and-exclusivity/</guid>
      <description>Breastfeeding support extends breastfeeding duration and exclusivity Researchers determine the impact of different support on the duration and exclusivity of mothers breastfeeding healthy term babies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SARS-CoV-2 Omicron BA.2 less severe than Delta and original Omicron</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sars-cov-2-omicron-ba2-less-severe-than-delta-and-original-omicron/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sars-cov-2-omicron-ba2-less-severe-than-delta-and-original-omicron/</guid>
      <description>SARS-CoV-2 Omicron BA.2 less severe than Delta and original Omicron Researchers estimate the severity of infection with the SARS-CoV-2 Omicron BA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infants&#39; innateness for tuning in to musical rhythms is intertwined with early social engagement</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/infants-innateness-for-tuning-in-to-musical-rhythms-is-intertwined-with-ea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:47:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/infants-innateness-for-tuning-in-to-musical-rhythms-is-intertwined-with-ea/</guid>
      <description>Infants&#39; innateness for tuning in to musical rhythms is intertwined with early social engagement Engaging infants with a song provides a readymade means for supporting social development and interaction, according to a study published by the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Increasing Awareness Surrounding Ataxia</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/increasing-awareness-surrounding-ataxia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/increasing-awareness-surrounding-ataxia/</guid>
      <description>Increasing Awareness Surrounding Ataxia In this interview, we speak to Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most adults seeking to lose weight overestimate the healthiness of their diet</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/most-adults-seeking-to-lose-weight-overestimate-the-healthiness-of-their-di/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/most-adults-seeking-to-lose-weight-overestimate-the-healthiness-of-their-di/</guid>
      <description>Most adults seeking to lose weight overestimate the healthiness of their diet In a small study, most adults seeking to lose weight overestimated the healthiness of their diet, according to preliminary research to be presented at the American Heart Association&#39;s Scientific Sessions 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SpyCatcher-SpyTag technology used to develop recombinant protein-based intranasal vaccine against SARS-CoV-2</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/spycatcher-spytag-technology-used-to-develop-recombinant-protein-based-intr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 09:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/spycatcher-spytag-technology-used-to-develop-recombinant-protein-based-intr/</guid>
      <description>SpyCatcher-SpyTag technology used to develop recombinant protein-based intranasal vaccine against SARS-CoV-2 The findings of a new study showed that the intranasal SpyCage vaccine platform can be protective against SARS-CoV-2 and may prove to be a versatile and adaptable modality for the formulation of intranasal vaccines that target respiratory pathogens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 appetite suppressant walmart [#Exposed] 2022 Updated - Deccan Herald</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/7-appetite-suppressant-walmart-exposed-2022-updated-deccan-herald/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 09:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/7-appetite-suppressant-walmart-exposed-2022-updated-deccan-herald/</guid>
      <description>7 appetite suppressant walmart [#Exposed] 2022 Updated - Deccan Herald 7 appetite suppressant walmart [#Exposed] 2022 Updated Deccan Herald</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curia celebrates ground-breaking ceremony in Albuquerque</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/curia-celebrates-ground-breaking-ceremony-in-albuquerque/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 09:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/curia-celebrates-ground-breaking-ceremony-in-albuquerque/</guid>
      <description>Curia celebrates ground-breaking ceremony in Albuquerque Curia today hosted a ground-breaking ceremony to mark the beginning of construction of its expanded campus in Albuquerque, New Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diabetics, manage your sugar cravings and blood glucose level with these effective tips</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/diabetics-manage-your-sugar-cravings-and-blood-glucose-level-with-these-ef/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 05:20:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/diabetics-manage-your-sugar-cravings-and-blood-glucose-level-with-these-ef/</guid>
      <description>Diabetics, manage your sugar cravings and blood glucose level with these effective tips indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An estimated 15% of U.S. adults have long-COVID</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/an-estimated-15-of-us-adults-have-long-covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 01:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/an-estimated-15-of-us-adults-have-long-covid/</guid>
      <description>An estimated 15% of U.S. adults have long-COVID In a recent study published in the journal JAMA Network Open, researchers in the United States estimated the sociodemographic factors associated with and prevalence of post-acute coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) symptom sequelae (PASC) or long COVID (LCOVID).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intermittent fasting can affect female hormones: Study - Sentinelassam - The Sentinel Assam</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/intermittent-fasting-can-affect-female-hormones-study-sentinelassam-th/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 01:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/intermittent-fasting-can-affect-female-hormones-study-sentinelassam-th/</guid>
      <description>Intermittent fasting can affect female hormones: Study - Sentinelassam - The Sentinel Assam Intermittent fasting can affect female hormones: Study - Sentinelassam The Sentinel AssamIntermittent fasting can affect female hormones: Research Hindustan TimesIs intermittent fasting a good practice?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An evaluation of the response to nationwide COVID-19 testing in England</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/an-evaluation-of-the-response-to-nationwide-covid-19-testing-in-england/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 01:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/an-evaluation-of-the-response-to-nationwide-covid-19-testing-in-england/</guid>
      <description>An evaluation of the response to nationwide COVID-19 testing in England Researchers in the Netherlands and the United Kingdom formulated recommendations for future pandemics using lessons learned from the testing programs implemented in the United Kingdom (UK) during the ongoing coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is India well past the major threat of severe impact of Covid-19? Here&#39;s what experts feel</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/is-india-well-past-the-major-threat-of-severe-impact-of-covid-19-heres-wh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 07:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/is-india-well-past-the-major-threat-of-severe-impact-of-covid-19-heres-wh/</guid>
      <description>Is India well past the major threat of severe impact of Covid-19?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Stroke Day 2022: Know everything from risk factors to improving strength after stroke - The Indian Express</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/world-stroke-day-2022-know-everything-from-risk-factors-to-improving-stren/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 09:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/world-stroke-day-2022-know-everything-from-risk-factors-to-improving-stren/</guid>
      <description>World Stroke Day 2022: Know everything from risk factors to improving strength after stroke - The Indian Express World Stroke Day 2022: Know everything from risk factors to improving strength after stroke The Indian ExpressMore Than 85% Of Stroke Patients Unaware Of Symptoms: Survey NDTVWorld Stroke Day | High time India had a national-level stroke registry MoneycontrolWorld Stroke Day: Here’s How You Can Prevent Stroke With Lifestyle Changes News18World Stroke Day: All you need to know about symptoms, prevention and treatment CNBCTV18View Full coverage on Google News</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standarized PedMSUS courses to help evaluate children with arthritis</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/standarized-pedmsus-courses-to-help-evaluate-children-with-arthritis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 02:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/standarized-pedmsus-courses-to-help-evaluate-children-with-arthritis/</guid>
      <description>Standarized PedMSUS courses to help evaluate children with arthritis Pediatric musculoskeletal ultrasound (PedMSUS) has great potential in the evaluation of children with arthritis, and since 2012 several PedMSUS courses have been endorsed by EULAR - The European Alliance of Rheumatology Associations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First guidance to optimize the use of PROMs for young people with inflammatory arthritis</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/first-guidance-to-optimize-the-use-of-proms-for-young-people-with-inflammat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 02:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/first-guidance-to-optimize-the-use-of-proms-for-young-people-with-inflammat/</guid>
      <description>First guidance to optimize the use of PROMs for young people with inflammatory arthritis PROMs aim to collect information on how a disease impacts key areas of a person&#39;s life, such as their quality of life, ability to do everyday activities, and their social or sexual health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Stroke Day 2022 exclusive: BEWARE of warning signs! Make THESE lifestyle changes to avoid a stroke</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/world-stroke-day-2022-exclusive-beware-of-warning-signs-make-these-lifest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 02:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/world-stroke-day-2022-exclusive-beware-of-warning-signs-make-these-lifest/</guid>
      <description>World Stroke Day 2022 exclusive: BEWARE of warning signs! Make THESE lifestyle changes to avoid a stroke When the blood supply to part of the brain is cut off, a stroke happens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reward for cooperative behavior</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/reward-for-cooperative-behavior/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 02:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/reward-for-cooperative-behavior/</guid>
      <description>Reward for cooperative behavior Researchers at the Max Planck Institute in Plön show that reputation plays a key role in determining which rewarding policies people adopt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study reveals the molecular mechanisms of dynamic activation of DNMT1 by H3Ub2</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/study-reveals-the-molecular-mechanisms-of-dynamic-activation-of-dnmt1-by-h3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 02:39:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/study-reveals-the-molecular-mechanisms-of-dynamic-activation-of-dnmt1-by-h3/</guid>
      <description>Study reveals the molecular mechanisms of dynamic activation of DNMT1 by H3Ub2 This study is led by Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Piceatannol and mTOR inhibitor combination proves be an attractive therapeutic strategy for gastric cancer</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/piceatannol-and-mtor-inhibitor-combination-proves-be-an-attractive-therapeu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 02:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/piceatannol-and-mtor-inhibitor-combination-proves-be-an-attractive-therapeu/</guid>
      <description>Piceatannol and mTOR inhibitor combination proves be an attractive therapeutic strategy for gastric cancer This study is led by Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update: Vaccination in children with AIIRD</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/update-vaccination-in-children-with-aiird/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 02:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/update-vaccination-in-children-with-aiird/</guid>
      <description>Update: Vaccination in children with AIIRD People with autoimmune or auto-inflammatory rheumatic diseases have an increased risk of infections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New developments in dementia research presented at Appel Alzheimer&#39;s Disease Research Institute Symposium</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-developments-in-dementia-research-presented-at-appel-alzheimers-diseas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 02:24:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-developments-in-dementia-research-presented-at-appel-alzheimers-diseas/</guid>
      <description>New developments in dementia research presented at Appel Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s Disease Research Institute Symposium The 10th annual Appel Alzheimer&#39;s Disease Research Institute Symposium brought fascinating reports of progress in understanding Alzheimer&#39;s and related neurodegenerative diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defect in gene caused massive obesity in mice despite normal food intake</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/defect-in-gene-caused-massive-obesity-in-mice-despite-normal-food-intake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 02:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/defect-in-gene-caused-massive-obesity-in-mice-despite-normal-food-intake/</guid>
      <description>Defect in gene caused massive obesity in mice despite normal food intake A faulty gene, rather than a faulty diet, may explain why some people gain excessive weight even when they don&#39;t eat more than others, UT Southwestern researchers at the Center for the Genetics of Host Defense have discovered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study: Vacant lot greening can reduce community crime, violence</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/study-vacant-lot-greening-can-reduce-community-crime-violence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 02:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/study-vacant-lot-greening-can-reduce-community-crime-violence/</guid>
      <description>Study: Vacant lot greening can reduce community crime, violence Communities that are engaged in cleaning, mowing and repurposing vacant spaces are likely to experience greater reductions in violence and crime than neighborhoods that do not participate in these activities, according to new research led by the University of Michigan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New insights on antibody responses to omicron variants</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-insights-on-antibody-responses-to-omicron-variants/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 02:19:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-insights-on-antibody-responses-to-omicron-variants/</guid>
      <description>New insights on antibody responses to omicron variants Knowing how well vaccination against one SARS-CoV-2 strain (with or without previous infection) counteracts infection with a different strain is a critical research question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developing game-based tech to detect and intervene against stress and anxiety</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/developing-game-based-tech-to-detect-and-intervene-against-stress-and-anxie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 02:18:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/developing-game-based-tech-to-detect-and-intervene-against-stress-and-anxie/</guid>
      <description>Developing game-based tech to detect and intervene against stress and anxiety A high-tech startup that uses game-based interventions to help users identify stress- and anxiety-related events in real time and receive a personalized intervention has been awarded a federal grant to partially develop its technology through research at Purdue University&#39;s College of Engineering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New vaccine approach can help jumpstart immune response to COVID-19</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-vaccine-approach-can-help-jumpstart-immune-response-to-covid-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 16:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-vaccine-approach-can-help-jumpstart-immune-response-to-covid-19/</guid>
      <description>New vaccine approach can help jumpstart immune response to COVID-19 A Yale-designed nasal vaccine can help bolster immune responses to COVID-19 in previously vaccinated animals and reduce viral transmission, Yale researchers report Oct.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multiple revenue misses in one of our winners convinced us to take profits and get out</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/multiple-revenue-misses-in-one-of-our-winners-convinced-us-to-take-profits-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 16:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/multiple-revenue-misses-in-one-of-our-winners-convinced-us-to-take-profits-/</guid>
      <description>Multiple revenue misses in one of our winners convinced us to take profits and get out We never like to sell on a down day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CU Anschutz study details the mechanisms behind the link between shingles and strokes</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cu-anschutz-study-details-the-mechanisms-behind-the-link-between-shingles-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 14:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cu-anschutz-study-details-the-mechanisms-behind-the-link-between-shingles-a/</guid>
      <description>CU Anschutz study details the mechanisms behind the link between shingles and strokes Scientists investigating why people who have had shingles are at a higher risk of stroke, now believe the answer lies within lipid vesicles called exosomes that shuttle proteins and genetic information between cells, according to new research from the University of Colorado Anschutz Medical Campus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Large listeriosis outbreak in Spain caused by contaminated stuffed pork</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/large-listeriosis-outbreak-in-spain-caused-by-contaminated-stuffed-pork/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 14:14:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/large-listeriosis-outbreak-in-spain-caused-by-contaminated-stuffed-pork/</guid>
      <description>Large listeriosis outbreak in Spain caused by contaminated stuffed pork Listeria bacteria are ubiquitous in the environment and consumption of food contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes is one of the main routes for food-borne outbreaks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The impact of seasonal coronavirus immunity on susceptibility to SARS-CoV-2 infection and COVID-19 vaccination</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-impact-of-seasonal-coronavirus-immunity-on-susceptibility-to-sars-cov-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 14:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-impact-of-seasonal-coronavirus-immunity-on-susceptibility-to-sars-cov-2/</guid>
      <description>The impact of seasonal coronavirus immunity on susceptibility to SARS-CoV-2 infection and COVID-19 vaccination Researchers investigated whether immunity against seasonal human coronavirus spike proteins of HKU1, OC43, NL63, or 229E could protect against SARS-CoV-2 in vitro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When monkeypox reaches rural communities, it collides with strained public health systems</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/when-monkeypox-reaches-rural-communities-it-collides-with-strained-public-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 10:07:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/when-monkeypox-reaches-rural-communities-it-collides-with-strained-public-/</guid>
      <description>When monkeypox reaches rural communities, it collides with strained public health systems When a case of monkeypox was reported in Nevada&#39;s Humboldt County in August, it was the state&#39;s first detected occurrence of the virus in a rural area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuck in a ‘trigger-stress-eating-temporary-relief’ cycle? Here’s how you can break the chain</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/stuck-in-a-trigger-stress-eating-temporary-relief-cycle-heres-how/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/stuck-in-a-trigger-stress-eating-temporary-relief-cycle-heres-how/</guid>
      <description>Stuck in a ‘trigger-stress-eating-temporary-relief’ cycle? Here’s how you can break the chain indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proof-of-principle study: Novel tool advances potential way to deliver gene therapy</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/proof-of-principle-study-novel-tool-advances-potential-way-to-deliver-gene/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/proof-of-principle-study-novel-tool-advances-potential-way-to-deliver-gene/</guid>
      <description>Proof-of-principle study: Novel tool advances potential way to deliver gene therapy Johns Hopkins Medicine researchers say they have successfully used a cell&#39;s natural process for making proteins to &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Researchers unravel the precise mechanism of nuclear envelope repair in human and mouse cells</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/researchers-unravel-the-precise-mechanism-of-nuclear-envelope-repair-in-hum/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/researchers-unravel-the-precise-mechanism-of-nuclear-envelope-repair-in-hum/</guid>
      <description>Researchers unravel the precise mechanism of nuclear envelope repair in human and mouse cells All living cells harbor nuclei-;key biological structures that play an important role in information storage, retrieval, and duplication of genetic information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Low-density granulocytes are phenotypically altered in people with long-COVID</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/low-density-granulocytes-are-phenotypically-altered-in-people-with-long-cov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/low-density-granulocytes-are-phenotypically-altered-in-people-with-long-cov/</guid>
      <description>Low-density granulocytes are phenotypically altered in people with long-COVID In a recent study posted to the bioRxiv* preprint server, researchers characterized low-density granulocyte (LDG) neutrophil (NP) proportion among individuals up to 14 months post-SARS-CoV-2 (severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2) infection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An unprecedented list of health-threatening fungi released by the WHO</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/an-unprecedented-list-of-health-threatening-fungi-released-by-the-who/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 01:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/an-unprecedented-list-of-health-threatening-fungi-released-by-the-who/</guid>
      <description>An unprecedented list of health-threatening fungi released by the WHO The WHO fungal priority pathogens list ranks pathogens that pose a serious risk of morbidity and mortality in humans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New report highlights the health impacts of air pollution in Africa</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-report-highlights-the-health-impacts-of-air-pollution-in-africa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 01:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-report-highlights-the-health-impacts-of-air-pollution-in-africa/</guid>
      <description>New report highlights the health impacts of air pollution in Africa Nearly all the African continent faces some of the most severe health impacts in the world caused by air pollution, with several countries experiencing some of the highest levels of air pollution in the world, according to a new report published by the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New initiative to improve post-acute stroke care across Montana, Nebraska and North Dakota</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-initiative-to-improve-post-acute-stroke-care-across-montana-nebraska-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-initiative-to-improve-post-acute-stroke-care-across-montana-nebraska-a/</guid>
      <description>New initiative to improve post-acute stroke care across Montana, Nebraska and North Dakota The American Heart Association, the world&#39;s leading voluntary organization focused on heart and brain health for all, is launching a two-year initiative to expand and enhance post-acute stroke care across Montana, Nebraska and North Dakota, giving all patients the best chance at independent life after stroke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RNA-sensing platform could help detect and selectively kill tumors, or edit the genome in specific cells</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rna-sensing-platform-could-help-detect-and-selectively-kill-tumors-or-edit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:54:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rna-sensing-platform-could-help-detect-and-selectively-kill-tumors-or-edit/</guid>
      <description>RNA-sensing platform could help detect and selectively kill tumors, or edit the genome in specific cells Researchers at the Broad Institute of MIT and Harvard and the McGovern Institute for Brain Research at MIT have developed a system that can detect a particular RNA sequence in live cells and produce a protein of interest in response.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study sheds light on why some patients respond better than others to immunotherapy</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/study-sheds-light-on-why-some-patients-respond-better-than-others-to-immuno/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:47:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/study-sheds-light-on-why-some-patients-respond-better-than-others-to-immuno/</guid>
      <description>Study sheds light on why some patients respond better than others to immunotherapy Immunotherapy, a biotherapy that boosts the ability of the immune system to recognize and attack mutant tumor cells, has transformed the treatment landscape for patients battling cancer, which emerges from the progressive accumulation of DNA mutations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Immune checkpoint therapy may be beneficial in certain cases of severe COVID-19</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/immune-checkpoint-therapy-may-be-beneficial-in-certain-cases-of-severe-covi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:42:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/immune-checkpoint-therapy-may-be-beneficial-in-certain-cases-of-severe-covi/</guid>
      <description>Immune checkpoint therapy may be beneficial in certain cases of severe COVID-19 An article published in Science Advances suggests that a type of cancer treatment known as immune checkpoint blockade may be beneficial in certain cases of severe COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UC San Diego participates in national trial to assess potential treatment for human monkeypox</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/uc-san-diego-participates-in-national-trial-to-assess-potential-treatment-f/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/uc-san-diego-participates-in-national-trial-to-assess-potential-treatment-f/</guid>
      <description>UC San Diego participates in national trial to assess potential treatment for human monkeypox The University of California San Diego will be one of multiple sites assessing the safety and efficacy of tecovirimat as a potential treatment for human monkeypox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does maternal insulin tolerance during pregnancy influence child adiposity?</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/does-maternal-insulin-tolerance-during-pregnancy-influence-child-adiposity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/does-maternal-insulin-tolerance-during-pregnancy-influence-child-adiposity/</guid>
      <description>Does maternal insulin tolerance during pregnancy influence child adiposity? Researchers explore the association between maternal insulin resistance with fetal fat deposition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unprecedented COVID spikes could overwhelm local jurisdictions, mathematical model suggests</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/unprecedented-covid-spikes-could-overwhelm-local-jurisdictions-mathematica/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/unprecedented-covid-spikes-could-overwhelm-local-jurisdictions-mathematica/</guid>
      <description>Unprecedented COVID spikes could overwhelm local jurisdictions, mathematical model suggests America was unprepared for the magnitude of the pandemic, which overwhelmed many counties and filled some hospitals to capacity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New study pinpoints neurons that slow us down during sickness</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-study-pinpoints-neurons-that-slow-us-down-during-sickness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-study-pinpoints-neurons-that-slow-us-down-during-sickness/</guid>
      <description>New study pinpoints neurons that slow us down during sickness We tend to eat, drink, and move less when we&#39;re feeling under the weather.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long COVID, a new clinical entity constantly evolving</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/long-covid-a-new-clinical-entity-constantly-evolving/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/long-covid-a-new-clinical-entity-constantly-evolving/</guid>
      <description>Long COVID, a new clinical entity constantly evolving Researchers discuss the epidemiology, diagnosis, pathogenesis, and treatment of long COVID.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study sheds new light on the risk of rare blood-clotting condition after covid-19 vaccination</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/study-sheds-new-light-on-the-risk-of-rare-blood-clotting-condition-after-co/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/study-sheds-new-light-on-the-risk-of-rare-blood-clotting-condition-after-co/</guid>
      <description>Study sheds new light on the risk of rare blood-clotting condition after covid-19 vaccination A study published by The BMJ today sheds further light on the risk of developing a very rare blood-clotting condition known as thrombosis with thrombocytopenia syndrome (TTS) after vaccination against the covid-19 virus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seeing or hearing birds linked with an improvement in mental wellbeing</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/seeing-or-hearing-birds-linked-with-an-improvement-in-mental-wellbeing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/seeing-or-hearing-birds-linked-with-an-improvement-in-mental-wellbeing/</guid>
      <description>Seeing or hearing birds linked with an improvement in mental wellbeing New research from King&#39;s College London has found that seeing or hearing birds is associated with an improvement in mental wellbeing that can last up to eight hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In mild cases of COVID, blood clot risk is higher</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/in-mild-cases-of-covid-blood-clot-risk-is-higher/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/in-mild-cases-of-covid-blood-clot-risk-is-higher/</guid>
      <description>In mild cases of COVID, blood clot risk is higher Researchers examine the association between COVID-19 and increased cardiovascular outcomes and mortality sequelae.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using stem cell cloning to identify the origin of lethal stomach and esophageal cancers</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/using-stem-cell-cloning-to-identify-the-origin-of-lethal-stomach-and-esopha/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/using-stem-cell-cloning-to-identify-the-origin-of-lethal-stomach-and-esopha/</guid>
      <description>Using stem cell cloning to identify the origin of lethal stomach and esophageal cancers The University of Houston is leading a team of cancer researchers and experts in stem cell cloning to identify the origin of two very lethal cancers of the stomach and esophagus - esophageal adenocarcinoma (EAC) and intestinal gastric cancer (iGC).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OSU researchers take major step toward improving, lengthening the lives of cystic fibrosis patients</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/osu-researchers-take-major-step-toward-improving-lengthening-the-lives-of-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/osu-researchers-take-major-step-toward-improving-lengthening-the-lives-of-/</guid>
      <description>OSU researchers take major step toward improving, lengthening the lives of cystic fibrosis patients Researchers at Oregon State University and Oregon Health &amp; Science University have taken a key step toward improving and lengthening the lives of cystic fibrosis patients, who experience chronically clogged airways and a dramatically shortened life expectancy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Researchers find a switch to regulate the diabetes-causing gene</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/researchers-find-a-switch-to-regulate-the-diabetes-causing-gene/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/researchers-find-a-switch-to-regulate-the-diabetes-causing-gene/</guid>
      <description>Researchers find a switch to regulate the diabetes-causing gene Researchers at the Centre for Genomic Regulation and Imperial College London have found a switch that regulates the activity of a gene that causes diabetes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Tuberculosis Report 2022 - World Health Organization</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/global-tuberculosis-report-2022-world-health-organization/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 16:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/global-tuberculosis-report-2022-world-health-organization/</guid>
      <description>Global Tuberculosis Report 2022 - World Health Organization Global Tuberculosis Report 2022 World Health OrganizationView Full coverage on Google News</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research opens up new avenues for overcoming treatment resistance in colorectal cancer</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/research-opens-up-new-avenues-for-overcoming-treatment-resistance-in-colore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 16:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/research-opens-up-new-avenues-for-overcoming-treatment-resistance-in-colore/</guid>
      <description>Research opens up new avenues for overcoming treatment resistance in colorectal cancer Colorectal cancer is one of the most common cancers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down with viral infections? Try these home remedies</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/down-with-viral-infections-try-these-home-remedies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 15:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/down-with-viral-infections-try-these-home-remedies/</guid>
      <description>Down with viral infections? Try these home remedies People, these days, have now forgotten the importance of Ayurvedic Nuskha.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rare variants of type I IFN immunity genes could underlie life-threatening COVID-19</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rare-variants-of-type-i-ifn-immunity-genes-could-underlie-life-threatening-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rare-variants-of-type-i-ifn-immunity-genes-could-underlie-life-threatening-/</guid>
      <description>Rare variants of type I IFN immunity genes could underlie life-threatening COVID-19 Researchers assessed whether loss-of-function variants of type I interferon immunity genes are associated with life-threatening COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>As Mohanlal enjoys red meat for lunch, his nutritionist shares a trick to make it ‘gut-friendly’</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/as-mohanlal-enjoys-red-meat-for-lunch-his-nutritionist-shares-a-trick-to-m/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 09:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/as-mohanlal-enjoys-red-meat-for-lunch-his-nutritionist-shares-a-trick-to-m/</guid>
      <description>As Mohanlal enjoys red meat for lunch, his nutritionist shares a trick to make it ‘gut-friendly’ indianexpress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unique gut bacteria could be responsible for triggering rheumatoid arthritis in at-risk people</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/unique-gut-bacteria-could-be-responsible-for-triggering-rheumatoid-arthriti/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 02:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/unique-gut-bacteria-could-be-responsible-for-triggering-rheumatoid-arthriti/</guid>
      <description>Unique gut bacteria could be responsible for triggering rheumatoid arthritis in at-risk people Researchers at the University of Colorado School of Medicine have discovered that a unique bacteria found in the gut could be responsible for triggering rheumatoid arthritis (RA) in people already at risk for the autoimmune disease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>$3 million grant to support the expansion of Midwest AIDS Training and Education Center at UIC</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/3-million-grant-to-support-the-expansion-of-midwest-aids-training-and-educ/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:36:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/3-million-grant-to-support-the-expansion-of-midwest-aids-training-and-educ/</guid>
      <description>$3 million grant to support the expansion of Midwest AIDS Training and Education Center at UIC The Midwest AIDS Training and Education Center at the University of Illinois Chicago will expand its services nationwide with the help of a new $3 million grant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unilever recalls select dry shampoo products with high benzene levels; find out how it harms your health</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/unilever-recalls-select-dry-shampoo-products-with-high-benzene-levels-find/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/unilever-recalls-select-dry-shampoo-products-with-high-benzene-levels-find/</guid>
      <description>Unilever recalls select dry shampoo products with high benzene levels; find out how it harms your health Just how harmful is benzene?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Treatment for complicated urinary tract infections is possible; suggests study</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/treatment-for-complicated-urinary-tract-infections-is-possible-suggests-st/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 12:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/treatment-for-complicated-urinary-tract-infections-is-possible-suggests-st/</guid>
      <description>Treatment for complicated urinary tract infections is possible; suggests study Some 79 percent of the patients receiving the new combination of cefepime and enmetazobactam were successfully treated for their illness, as opposed to 58.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is the association of self-reported post-vaccination symptoms with anti–SARS-CoV-2 antibody response?</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/what-is-the-association-of-self-reported-post-vaccination-symptoms-with-ant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 12:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/what-is-the-association-of-self-reported-post-vaccination-symptoms-with-ant/</guid>
      <description>What is the association of self-reported post-vaccination symptoms with anti–SARS-CoV-2 antibody response?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Put a Full Stop to Child Sexual Abuse</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/put-a-full-stop-to-child-sexual-abuse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 11:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/put-a-full-stop-to-child-sexual-abuse/</guid>
      <description>Put a Full Stop to Child Sexual Abuse We believe that we live in a safe society but very often this is a myth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All about new Frontiers in Dentistry</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/all-about-new-frontiers-in-dentistry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 10:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/all-about-new-frontiers-in-dentistry/</guid>
      <description>All about new Frontiers in Dentistry Dr Mitali Bora, Principal of Regional Dental College, Guwahati shares a detailed and comprehensive overview with MELANGE</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 and the gut</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/covid-19-and-the-gut/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/covid-19-and-the-gut/</guid>
      <description>COVID-19 and the gut Researchers summarize current knowledge about underlying mechanisms and potential therapeutic approaches for the effects of COVID-19 on the gut.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dangers of recreational/medical cannabis use</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dangers-of-recreationalmedical-cannabis-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 08:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dangers-of-recreationalmedical-cannabis-use/</guid>
      <description>Dangers of recreational/medical cannabis use Researchers describe the wide range of neurological effects associated with cannabis use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DNA damage in older age increases expression of ACE2 and SARS-CoV-2 infection risk</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dna-damage-in-older-age-increases-expression-of-ace2-and-sars-cov-2-infecti/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dna-damage-in-older-age-increases-expression-of-ace2-and-sars-cov-2-infecti/</guid>
      <description>DNA damage in older age increases expression of ACE2 and SARS-CoV-2 infection risk Impaired DNA repair capacity among elderly increases expression of ACE2 receptor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China launches Covid-19 vaccine inhaled through the mouth</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/china-launches-covid-19-vaccine-inhaled-through-the-mouth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 08:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/china-launches-covid-19-vaccine-inhaled-through-the-mouth/</guid>
      <description>China launches Covid-19 vaccine inhaled through the mouth Beijing, October 26 The Chinese city of Shanghai started administering an inhalable COVID-19 vaccine on Wednesday in what appears to be a world first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring new therapeutic targets and biomarkers for neurodegenerative disorders</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/exploring-new-therapeutic-targets-and-biomarkers-for-neurodegenerative-diso/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 06:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/exploring-new-therapeutic-targets-and-biomarkers-for-neurodegenerative-diso/</guid>
      <description>Exploring new therapeutic targets and biomarkers for neurodegenerative disorders In this interview, Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIT professor receives grant to investigate new therapeutic approaches for scleroderma</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rit-professor-receives-grant-to-investigate-new-therapeutic-approaches-for-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 02:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rit-professor-receives-grant-to-investigate-new-therapeutic-approaches-for-/</guid>
      <description>RIT professor receives grant to investigate new therapeutic approaches for scleroderma More collagen in the human body is not always good, and Karin Wuertz-Kozak is investigating how disease progresses because of the increase in this important protein.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exposure to e-cigarette aerosols can cause heart arrhythmias, study shows</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/exposure-to-e-cigarette-aerosols-can-cause-heart-arrhythmias-study-shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 02:28:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/exposure-to-e-cigarette-aerosols-can-cause-heart-arrhythmias-study-shows/</guid>
      <description>Exposure to e-cigarette aerosols can cause heart arrhythmias, study shows A new study from University of Louisville researchers in the Christina Lee Brown Envirome Institute has found that exposure to e-cigarette aerosols can cause heart arrhythmias in animal models -; both in the form of premature and skipped heart beats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discovery of small molecule enzyme inhibitor could be the key to treating cancers, autoimmune diseases</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/discovery-of-small-molecule-enzyme-inhibitor-could-be-the-key-to-treating-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 01:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/discovery-of-small-molecule-enzyme-inhibitor-could-be-the-key-to-treating-c/</guid>
      <description>Discovery of small molecule enzyme inhibitor could be the key to treating cancers, autoimmune diseases Researchers at the University of Illinois Chicago have found a small molecule capable of manipulating an immune process that plays an important role in cancers and autoimmune diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UArizona researchers working on a less toxic treatment for deadly breast cancer</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/uarizona-researchers-working-on-a-less-toxic-treatment-for-deadly-breast-ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/uarizona-researchers-working-on-a-less-toxic-treatment-for-deadly-breast-ca/</guid>
      <description>UArizona researchers working on a less toxic treatment for deadly breast cancer After decades of research and two previous drug development attempts, things are looking promising for a team of University of Arizona researchers working on a less toxic treatment for a specific type of breast cancer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily exercise: 5 Benefits of walking 10000 steps a day besides losing weight</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/daily-exercise-5-benefits-of-walking-10000-steps-a-day-besides-losing-weig/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/daily-exercise-5-benefits-of-walking-10000-steps-a-day-besides-losing-weig/</guid>
      <description>Daily exercise: 5 Benefits of walking 10000 steps a day besides losing weight Walking 10000 steps daily seems like a big task but once you start there&#39;s no stopping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overexpression of KIF11 gene may offset Alzheimer’s-related cognitive decline in mice and humans</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/overexpression-of-kif11-gene-may-offset-alzheimers-related-cognitive-dec/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/overexpression-of-kif11-gene-may-offset-alzheimers-related-cognitive-dec/</guid>
      <description>Overexpression of KIF11 gene may offset Alzheimer’s-related cognitive decline in mice and humans The overexpression of a gene tied to cell division and the structure and function of neurons may prevent and protect against cognitive decline in both mice and humans with Alzheimer’s disease (AD), according to a new study by scientists at the University of Colorado Anschutz Medical Campus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Combination treatment improves progression-free survival in patients with oligometastatic prostate cancer</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/combination-treatment-improves-progression-free-survival-in-patients-with-o/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:13:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/combination-treatment-improves-progression-free-survival-in-patients-with-o/</guid>
      <description>Combination treatment improves progression-free survival in patients with oligometastatic prostate cancer Researchers from The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center demonstrated that adding metastasis-directed radiation therapy to intermittent hormone therapy improved progression-free survival (PFS) in patients with oligometastatic prostate cancer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New approach to immunotherapy provokes a robust anti-tumor immune response in preclinical models</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-approach-to-immunotherapy-provokes-a-robust-anti-tumor-immune-response-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-approach-to-immunotherapy-provokes-a-robust-anti-tumor-immune-response-/</guid>
      <description>New approach to immunotherapy provokes a robust anti-tumor immune response in preclinical models A new approach to cancer immunotherapy that uses one type of immune cell to kill another-;rather than directly attacking the cancer-;provokes a robust anti-tumor immune response that shrinks ovarian, lung, and pancreatic tumors in preclinical disease models, according to researchers at the Icahn School of Medicine at Mount Sinai in New York.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brain development determines nap transitions in early childhood</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/brain-development-determines-nap-transitions-in-early-childhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:07:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/brain-development-determines-nap-transitions-in-early-childhood/</guid>
      <description>Brain development determines nap transitions in early childhood Why do some 4- and 5-year-olds still nap like clockwork every afternoon, while other preschoolers start giving up habitual napping at age 3?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New type of antibiotic effectively kills hard-to-fight bacteria</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-type-of-antibiotic-effectively-kills-hard-to-fight-bacteria/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 14:54:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-type-of-antibiotic-effectively-kills-hard-to-fight-bacteria/</guid>
      <description>New type of antibiotic effectively kills hard-to-fight bacteria Bacterial resistance to antibiotics is a growing threat to human health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Researchers focus on the identification of markers to improve head and neck cancer risk assessment</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/researchers-focus-on-the-identification-of-markers-to-improve-head-and-neck/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 14:49:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/researchers-focus-on-the-identification-of-markers-to-improve-head-and-neck/</guid>
      <description>Researchers focus on the identification of markers to improve head and neck cancer risk assessment Malignant tumors in the head and neck region are very heterogeneous and therefore difficult to treat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get fit: Make THESE five lifestyle changes and keep sickness at bay!</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/get-fit-make-these-five-lifestyle-changes-and-keep-sickness-at-bay/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/get-fit-make-these-five-lifestyle-changes-and-keep-sickness-at-bay/</guid>
      <description>Get fit: Make THESE five lifestyle changes and keep sickness at bay!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engineered particles of purified sand could be a potential cure for obesity</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/engineered-particles-of-purified-sand-could-be-a-potential-cure-for-obesity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 05:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/engineered-particles-of-purified-sand-could-be-a-potential-cure-for-obesity/</guid>
      <description>Engineered particles of purified sand could be a potential cure for obesity Engineered particles of purified sand could be the next anti-obesity therapy as new research from the University of South Australia shows that porous silica can prevent fats and carbohydrates from being adsorbed in the body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSU researchers receive $3 million NIH grant to study testosterone’s role in depression</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/msu-researchers-receive-3-million-nih-grant-to-study-testosterones-role/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 01:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/msu-researchers-receive-3-million-nih-grant-to-study-testosterones-role/</guid>
      <description>MSU researchers receive $3 million NIH grant to study testosterone’s role in depression Major depressive disorder affects women twice as often as men, but researchers are still trying to identify the reasons why.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Large genome-wide association study on nonalcoholic fatty liver disease</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/large-genome-wide-association-study-on-nonalcoholic-fatty-liver-disease/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 01:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/large-genome-wide-association-study-on-nonalcoholic-fatty-liver-disease/</guid>
      <description>Large genome-wide association study on nonalcoholic fatty liver disease Scientists at deCODE genetics in Iceland have discovered rare, protective loss-of-function variants that point to potential drug targets for nonalcoholic fatty liver disease (NAFLD).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iowa researchers identify neural circuit linked with stress response</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/iowa-researchers-identify-neural-circuit-linked-with-stress-response/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 01:07:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/iowa-researchers-identify-neural-circuit-linked-with-stress-response/</guid>
      <description>Iowa researchers identify neural circuit linked with stress response At one time or another, we&#39;ve all felt paralyzed by a threat or danger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Near-infrared spectroscopy can provide a cost-effective way to noninvasively monitor intracranial pressure</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/near-infrared-spectroscopy-can-provide-a-cost-effective-way-to-noninvasivel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 01:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/near-infrared-spectroscopy-can-provide-a-cost-effective-way-to-noninvasivel/</guid>
      <description>Near-infrared spectroscopy can provide a cost-effective way to noninvasively monitor intracranial pressure An increase in intracranial pressure (ICP) is a dangerous condition that can be caused by brain bleeds, a brain tumor, cerebral edema, traumatic brain injury, and hydrocephalus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In utero exposure to flame retardant results in altered brain development in newborn rats</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/in-utero-exposure-to-flame-retardant-results-in-altered-brain-development-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/in-utero-exposure-to-flame-retardant-results-in-altered-brain-development-i/</guid>
      <description>In utero exposure to flame retardant results in altered brain development in newborn rats A new study from North Carolina State University shows that exposure in utero to the flame retardant FireMaster 550 (FM 550), or to its individual brominated (BFR) or organophosphate ester (OPFR) components, resulted in altered brain development in newborn rats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prescribed fire could play a role in reducing the abundance of ticks and pathogen transmission</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/prescribed-fire-could-play-a-role-in-reducing-the-abundance-of-ticks-and-pa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/prescribed-fire-could-play-a-role-in-reducing-the-abundance-of-ticks-and-pa/</guid>
      <description>Prescribed fire could play a role in reducing the abundance of ticks and pathogen transmission Prescribed fire -; a tool increasingly used by forest managers and landowners to combat invasive species, improve wildlife habitat and restore ecosystem health -; also could play a role in reducing the abundance of ticks and the transmission of disease pathogens they carry, according to a team of scientists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Researchers study the effects of alcohol intake and seek better treatment for alcoholic pancreatitis</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/researchers-study-the-effects-of-alcohol-intake-and-seek-better-treatment-f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:20:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/researchers-study-the-effects-of-alcohol-intake-and-seek-better-treatment-f/</guid>
      <description>Researchers study the effects of alcohol intake and seek better treatment for alcoholic pancreatitis Many alcoholic pancreatitis patients continued drinking during COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heart attack death rates took a sharp turn and increased during the pandemic, study shows</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/heart-attack-death-rates-took-a-sharp-turn-and-increased-during-the-pandemi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/heart-attack-death-rates-took-a-sharp-turn-and-increased-during-the-pandemi/</guid>
      <description>Heart attack death rates took a sharp turn and increased during the pandemic, study shows New data analysis from the Smidt Heart Institute at Cedars-Sinai found that deaths from heart attacks rose significantly during pandemic surges, including the COVID-19 Omicron surges, overall reversing a heart-healthier pre-pandemic trend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New diagnostic method applies machine learning to advanced genomics data to detect sepsis</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-diagnostic-method-applies-machine-learning-to-advanced-genomics-data-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:09:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-diagnostic-method-applies-machine-learning-to-advanced-genomics-data-to/</guid>
      <description>New diagnostic method applies machine learning to advanced genomics data to detect sepsis Sepsis, the overreaction of the immune system in response to an infection, causes an estimated 20% of deaths globally and as many as 20 to 50% of U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientists use systems biology approach to identify molecular players in rheumatoid arthritis</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/scientists-use-systems-biology-approach-to-identify-molecular-players-in-rh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 23:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/scientists-use-systems-biology-approach-to-identify-molecular-players-in-rh/</guid>
      <description>Scientists use systems biology approach to identify molecular players in rheumatoid arthritis Using a novel systems biology approach, scientists at University of California San Diego School of Medicine have further parsed the cellular players and roles involved in rheumatoid arthritis (RA), a complex disease that affects more than one million Americans in ways that have defied development of uniform treatments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study highlights the need to strengthen trust in healthcare to limit antibiotic use</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/study-highlights-the-need-to-strengthen-trust-in-healthcare-to-limit-antibi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 23:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/study-highlights-the-need-to-strengthen-trust-in-healthcare-to-limit-antibi/</guid>
      <description>Study highlights the need to strengthen trust in healthcare to limit antibiotic use Do many Swedes obtain antibiotics without a prescription, and what drives their behaviour when this happens?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study estimates the burden of dementia among older adults in the U.S.</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/study-estimates-the-burden-of-dementia-among-older-adults-in-the-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 23:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/study-estimates-the-burden-of-dementia-among-older-adults-in-the-us/</guid>
      <description>Study estimates the burden of dementia among older adults in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Novel oxytocin derivative can reverse Aβ25-35-induced cognitive impairment in mice</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/novel-oxytocin-derivative-can-reverse-a25-35-induced-cognitive-impairment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 23:07:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/novel-oxytocin-derivative-can-reverse-a25-35-induced-cognitive-impairment/</guid>
      <description>Novel oxytocin derivative can reverse Aβ25-35-induced cognitive impairment in mice Alzheimer&#39;s disease (AD), characterized by an accumulation of β-amyloid protein (Aβ) in brain tissue, is a leading cause of dementia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Researchers discover new type of microglia related to stroke in the ischemia/reperfusion injured brain</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/researchers-discover-new-type-of-microglia-related-to-stroke-in-the-ischemi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 22:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/researchers-discover-new-type-of-microglia-related-to-stroke-in-the-ischemi/</guid>
      <description>Researchers discover new type of microglia related to stroke in the ischemia/reperfusion injured brain A research team, affiliated with UNIST has identified a new type of microglia associated with stroke in the ischemia/reperfusion (I/R) injured brain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More intensive prostate cancer screening may reduce the risk of metastatic cancer later</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/more-intensive-prostate-cancer-screening-may-reduce-the-risk-of-metastatic-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 22:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/more-intensive-prostate-cancer-screening-may-reduce-the-risk-of-metastatic-/</guid>
      <description>More intensive prostate cancer screening may reduce the risk of metastatic cancer later In the face of conflicting evidence over the risks and benefits of routine prostate cancer screenings, a large, longitudinal analysis found Veterans Health Administration medical centers with lower prostate screening rates had higher rates of metastatic prostate cancer cases in subsequent years than centers with higher screening rates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Systematic review uncovers new links between the thyroid and the heart</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/systematic-review-uncovers-new-links-between-the-thyroid-and-the-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 22:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/systematic-review-uncovers-new-links-between-the-thyroid-and-the-heart/</guid>
      <description>Systematic review uncovers new links between the thyroid and the heart Systematic review of 32 studies with 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playing video games may be linked with improved cognitive abilities in children</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/playing-video-games-may-be-linked-with-improved-cognitive-abilities-in-chil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 22:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/playing-video-games-may-be-linked-with-improved-cognitive-abilities-in-chil/</guid>
      <description>Playing video games may be linked with improved cognitive abilities in children A study of nearly 2,000 children found that those who reported playing video games for three hours per day or more performed better on cognitive skills tests involving impulse control and working memory compared to children who had never played video games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Combination of radiation and systemic therapy can prolong survival for advanced liver cancer patients</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/combination-of-radiation-and-systemic-therapy-can-prolong-survival-for-adva/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 16:43:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/combination-of-radiation-and-systemic-therapy-can-prolong-survival-for-adva/</guid>
      <description>Combination of radiation and systemic therapy can prolong survival for advanced liver cancer patients Adding radiation therapy to systemic therapy for patients with advanced liver cancer can extend overall survival and delay tumor progression without compromising patients&#39; quality of life, a randomized phase III clinical trial shows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clinical trial confirms the safety, efficacy of shortened radiation therapy for high-risk prostate cancer patients</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/clinical-trial-confirms-the-safety-efficacy-of-shortened-radiation-therapy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 16:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/clinical-trial-confirms-the-safety-efficacy-of-shortened-radiation-therapy/</guid>
      <description>Clinical trial confirms the safety, efficacy of shortened radiation therapy for high-risk prostate cancer patients A new randomized study confirms that men with high-risk prostate cancer can be treated with five versus eight weeks of radiation therapy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Polio Day 2022: Technical update - Rotary</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/world-polio-day-2022-technical-update-rotary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 15:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/world-polio-day-2022-technical-update-rotary/</guid>
      <description>World Polio Day 2022: Technical update - Rotary World Polio Day 2022: Technical update RotaryJoe Randig: Vaccination the key to preventing more polio outbreaks TribLIVE(WATCH) Analyzing The Risk Of Polio In Polio Free Countries TVC News NigeriaOTISO: More awareness needed to eradicate polio The Star Kenya World Polio Day 2022: Zero Dose Children RotaryView Full coverage on Google News</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analysis finds higher level of opioid abuse among sexual minorities compared to heterosexuals</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/analysis-finds-higher-level-of-opioid-abuse-among-sexual-minorities-compare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 15:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/analysis-finds-higher-level-of-opioid-abuse-among-sexual-minorities-compare/</guid>
      <description>Analysis finds higher level of opioid abuse among sexual minorities compared to heterosexuals Although opioid abuse in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating the Alderley Park Grand Opening</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/celebrating-the-alderley-park-grand-opening/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/celebrating-the-alderley-park-grand-opening/</guid>
      <description>Celebrating the Alderley Park Grand Opening HQ Plasmid Center of Excellence based at UK life science hotspot now open for business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diwali 2022: What happens after bursting crackers post-Diwali?</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/diwali-2022-what-happens-after-bursting-crackers-post-diwali/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/diwali-2022-what-happens-after-bursting-crackers-post-diwali/</guid>
      <description>Diwali 2022: What happens after bursting crackers post-Diwali? Diwali celebrations are said to be incomplete without bursting crackers but is it so?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Try THESE 3 lifestyle tips for balancing Vata dosha</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/try-these-3-lifestyle-tips-for-balancing-vata-dosha/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/try-these-3-lifestyle-tips-for-balancing-vata-dosha/</guid>
      <description>Try THESE 3 lifestyle tips for balancing Vata dosha Almonds work best to calm the Vata dosha due to their after-digestion sweet and warming qualities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reasons why you should never skip breakfast</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/reasons-why-you-should-never-skip-breakfast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 06:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/reasons-why-you-should-never-skip-breakfast/</guid>
      <description>Reasons why you should never skip breakfast IANSlife New Delhi, October 24 What is the first thing that concerns most people immediately after waking up in the morning?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diwali 2022: Tips to maintain safety and health during the festival</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/diwali-2022-tips-to-maintain-safety-and-health-during-the-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 06:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/diwali-2022-tips-to-maintain-safety-and-health-during-the-festival/</guid>
      <description>Diwali 2022: Tips to maintain safety and health during the festival Diwali is a festival which is full of our energy and excitement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anxiety disorders had no effect on vaccine hesitancy</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/anxiety-disorders-had-no-effect-on-vaccine-hesitancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 05:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/anxiety-disorders-had-no-effect-on-vaccine-hesitancy/</guid>
      <description>Anxiety disorders had no effect on vaccine hesitancy These findings help shed light on the best way for the government to promote vaccination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anxiety disorder has no effect on vaccine hesitancy: Study</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/anxiety-disorder-has-no-effect-on-vaccine-hesitancy-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 05:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/anxiety-disorder-has-no-effect-on-vaccine-hesitancy-study/</guid>
      <description>Anxiety disorder has no effect on vaccine hesitancy: Study IANS New Delhi, October 24 Individuals who deal with anxiety are no less hesitant to get the Covid-19 vaccine compared to those without anxiety, according to new research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 vaccination during pregnancy protects infants from SARS-CoV-2 infection</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/covid-19-vaccination-during-pregnancy-protects-infants-from-sars-cov-2-infe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 04:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/covid-19-vaccination-during-pregnancy-protects-infants-from-sars-cov-2-infe/</guid>
      <description>COVID-19 vaccination during pregnancy protects infants from SARS-CoV-2 infection In a recent study under review at the Nature Portfolio journal and currently posted to Research Square* preprint server, researchers evaluated the efficacy of maternal coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) vaccination against infection of infants with severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A novel approach for viral genomic surveillance</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/a-novel-approach-for-viral-genomic-surveillance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 04:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/a-novel-approach-for-viral-genomic-surveillance/</guid>
      <description>A novel approach for viral genomic surveillance In a recent study posted to the bioRxiv* preprint server, researchers in the United States explored a novel technique to improve representation in viral genomic surveillance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Antibody-mediated protection against symptomatic COVID achieved at low serum neutralizing titers</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/antibody-mediated-protection-against-symptomatic-covid-achieved-at-low-seru/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/antibody-mediated-protection-against-symptomatic-covid-achieved-at-low-seru/</guid>
      <description>Antibody-mediated protection against symptomatic COVID achieved at low serum neutralizing titers In a recent study posted to the medRxiv* preprint server, researchers in the United States assessed the efficiency of protection mediated by antibodies against symptomatic coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) at low serum-neutralizing titers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research suggests that ORF6 is a major SARS-CoV-2 innate immune antagonist</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/research-suggests-that-orf6-is-a-major-sars-cov-2-innate-immune-antagonist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 03:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/research-suggests-that-orf6-is-a-major-sars-cov-2-innate-immune-antagonist/</guid>
      <description>Research suggests that ORF6 is a major SARS-CoV-2 innate immune antagonist In a recent study posted to the bioRxiv* server, researchers in the United States demonstrated how severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2) open reading frame 6 (ORF6) protein contributes to viral pathogenesis and modulates the host&#39;s immune responses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>United Nations Day: आज है यूनाइटेड नेशंस डे, जानें क्या है इस बार की थीम और इसकी हिस्ट्री</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/united-nations-day-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 03:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/united-nations-day-/</guid>
      <description>United Nations Day: आज है यूनाइटेड नेशंस डे, जानें क्या है इस बार की थीम और इसकी हिस्ट्री United Nations day-October 24- हर साल 24 अक्टूबर को यूनाइटेड नेशंस डे मनाया जाता है और इस दिन ही यूनाइटेड नेशन को ऑफिशियल रूप से स्थापित किया गया था.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
