<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Press release on TechnoStreet</title>
    <link>https://technostreet.github.io/tags/press-release/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Press release on TechnoStreet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 07:03:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://technostreet.github.io/tags/press-release/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>“AIC-BIMTECH, in collaboration with the Canadian High Commission in India, organized the CTA program “Waste to Wealth”</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/aic-bimtech-in-collaboration-with-the-canadian-high-commission-in-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 07:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/aic-bimtech-in-collaboration-with-the-canadian-high-commission-in-india/</guid>
      <description>“AIC-BIMTECH, in collaboration with the Canadian High Commission in India, organized the CTA program “Waste to Wealth” “AIC-BIMTECH, in collaboration with the Canadian High Commission in India, organized a week-long CTA program in various geographies of India on the theme “Waste to Wealth,” which marked its foundation in Delhi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gate US coming to the USA after obtaining licenses for cryptocurrency trading!</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gate-us-coming-to-the-usa-after-obtaining-licenses-for-cryptocurrency-tradi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gate-us-coming-to-the-usa-after-obtaining-licenses-for-cryptocurrency-tradi/</guid>
      <description>Gate US coming to the USA after obtaining licenses for cryptocurrency trading!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diagnostic Ultrasound Market Size Will Attain USD 11.4 Billion by 2030 growing at 5.3% CAGR – Exclusive Report by Acumen Research and Consulting</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/diagnostic-ultrasound-market-size-will-attain-usd-114-billion-by-2030-grow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 16:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/diagnostic-ultrasound-market-size-will-attain-usd-114-billion-by-2030-grow/</guid>
      <description>Diagnostic Ultrasound Market Size Will Attain USD 11.4 Billion by 2030 growing at 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New International Consensus on CGM Clinical Trial Metrics Aims to Spur Diabetes Treatment Advances</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-international-consensus-on-cgm-clinical-trial-metrics-aims-to-spur-diab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 16:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-international-consensus-on-cgm-clinical-trial-metrics-aims-to-spur-diab/</guid>
      <description>New International Consensus on CGM Clinical Trial Metrics Aims to Spur Diabetes Treatment Advances SAN FRANCISCO, Dec.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siemens Gamesa’s Engineering Centre in India grows to become one of its largest hubs for wind energy technology in the world</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/siemens-gamesas-engineering-centre-in-india-grows-to-become-one-of-its-l/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 06:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/siemens-gamesas-engineering-centre-in-india-grows-to-become-one-of-its-l/</guid>
      <description>Siemens Gamesa’s Engineering Centre in India grows to become one of its largest hubs for wind energy technology in the world Siemens Gamesa to expand operations in Bengaluru with the inauguration of a second office for its engineers The Engineering Centre forms one of three major technology hubs for Siemens Gamesa globally, driving the development of future wind turbines The facility now employs 1,100 engineers, which is forecast to grow in coming years BENGALURU, India, Nov.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BYD Rolls Off Its 3 Millionth New Energy Vehicle and Debuts A New Passenger Car Brand Matrix</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/byd-rolls-off-its-3-millionth-new-energy-vehicle-and-debuts-a-new-passenger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 06:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/byd-rolls-off-its-3-millionth-new-energy-vehicle-and-debuts-a-new-passenger/</guid>
      <description>BYD Rolls Off Its 3 Millionth New Energy Vehicle and Debuts A New Passenger Car Brand Matrix Business Wire India BYD&#39;s acceleration on promoting New Energy Vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cambridge Dictionary Word of the Year 2022 is… HOMER</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-cambridge-dictionary-word-of-the-year-2022-is-homer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 06:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-cambridge-dictionary-word-of-the-year-2022-is-homer/</guid>
      <description>The Cambridge Dictionary Word of the Year 2022 is… HOMER Business Wire India ‘Homer’ is Word of the Year, according to the world’s most popular online dictionary for learners of English.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Million Dollar – The First Real Estate Metaverse Company</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/million-dollar-the-first-real-estate-metaverse-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 08:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/million-dollar-the-first-real-estate-metaverse-company/</guid>
      <description>Million Dollar – The First Real Estate Metaverse Company DUBAI, UAE, Nov.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roboyo ramps up global expansion with strategic acquisition of Procensol</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/roboyo-ramps-up-global-expansion-with-strategic-acquisition-of-procensol/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 08:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/roboyo-ramps-up-global-expansion-with-strategic-acquisition-of-procensol/</guid>
      <description>Roboyo ramps up global expansion with strategic acquisition of Procensol NUREMBERG, Germany, Nov.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clarivate Names World’s Influential Researchers with Highly Cited Researchers 2022 List</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/clarivate-names-worlds-influential-researchers-with-highly-cited-researc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 08:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/clarivate-names-worlds-influential-researchers-with-highly-cited-researc/</guid>
      <description>Clarivate Names World’s Influential Researchers with Highly Cited Researchers 2022 List Institute for Scientific Information deepens qualitative analysis of annual list to improve detection of gaming, misconduct LONDON, Nov.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oxalys annonce une première opération de croissance externe avec COBuy</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oxalys-annonce-une-premire-opration-de-croissance-externe-avec-cobuy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 08:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oxalys-annonce-une-premire-opration-de-croissance-externe-avec-cobuy/</guid>
      <description>Oxalys annonce une première opération de croissance externe avec COBuy Oxalys, spécialiste de la digitalisation des achats et des dépenses, annonce la reprise de COBuy et lance sa nouvelle stratégie de croissance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dictador creates the most exclusive spirit in history: the first one billion-dollar limited edition – Dictador M-City Golden Cities</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dictador-creates-the-most-exclusive-spirit-in-history-the-first-one-billio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 08:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dictador-creates-the-most-exclusive-spirit-in-history-the-first-one-billio/</guid>
      <description>Dictador creates the most exclusive spirit in history: the first one billion-dollar limited edition – Dictador M-City Golden Cities MIKOŁÓW, Poland, Nov.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Venture Catalysts &#43;&#43; – the House of Unicorns, Soonicorns Delivers 54 Startups Above USD 50mn in 7 Years</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/venture-catalysts-the-house-of-unicorns-soonicorns-delivers-54-star/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 08:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/venture-catalysts-the-house-of-unicorns-soonicorns-delivers-54-star/</guid>
      <description>Venture Catalysts ++ – the House of Unicorns, Soonicorns Delivers 54 Startups Above USD 50mn in 7 Years Business Wire India Venture Catalysts Group (Vcats++), India’s first integrated incubator and a full-stack investor for early to growth stage startups, has announced that about 54 of its portfolio startups have crossed $50 million valuation this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Esri Enters into Agreement with United Nations Population Fund to Help Modernize National Statistics Programs</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/esri-enters-into-agreement-with-united-nations-population-fund-to-help-mode/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 07:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/esri-enters-into-agreement-with-united-nations-population-fund-to-help-mode/</guid>
      <description>Esri Enters into Agreement with United Nations Population Fund to Help Modernize National Statistics Programs Business Wire India A population and housing census is among the most complex and massive peacetime exercises a nation can undertake, requiring careful planning, resourcing, and implementation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marriott Vacation Club Opens Newest Resort, Marriott’s Bali Nusa Dua Terrace</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/marriott-vacation-club-opens-newest-resort-marriotts-bali-nusa-dua-terr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 07:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/marriott-vacation-club-opens-newest-resort-marriotts-bali-nusa-dua-terr/</guid>
      <description>Marriott Vacation Club Opens Newest Resort, Marriott’s Bali Nusa Dua Terrace Business Wire India Marriott Vacation Club — a global industry leader in Vacation Ownership and brand of Marriott Vacations Worldwide (NYSE: VAC) — announced today they have officially opened Marriott’s Bali Nusa Dua Terrace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DEINOVE REQUESTS RECEIVERSHIP PROCEEDINGS</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/deinove-requests-receivership-proceedings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 16:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/deinove-requests-receivership-proceedings/</guid>
      <description>DEINOVE REQUESTS RECEIVERSHIP PROCEEDINGS DEINOVE (Euronext Growth Paris: ALDEI), a French biotech company, pioneer in the exploration and exploitation of bacterial biodiversity to address the urgent, global challenge of antibiotic resistance, announces having filed today a declaration of cessation of payments (“déclaration de cessation des paiements“) and a request for receivership proceedings (“procédure de redressement judiciaire”) of the Company… The post DEINOVE REQUESTS RECEIVERSHIP PROCEEDINGS appeared first on DKODING.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HDFC Life elevates Suresh Badami as Deputy Managing Director</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hdfc-life-elevates-suresh-badami-as-deputy-managing-director/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 16:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hdfc-life-elevates-suresh-badami-as-deputy-managing-director/</guid>
      <description>HDFC Life elevates Suresh Badami as Deputy Managing Director Business Wire India HDFC Life, one of India&#39;s leading life insurers, at its board meeting, announced that it has elevated Suresh Badami to the role of Deputy Managing Director.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LBank Exchange Will List VNX Gold (VNXAU) on October 25, 2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/lbank-exchange-will-list-vnx-gold-vnxau-on-october-25-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 05:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/lbank-exchange-will-list-vnx-gold-vnxau-on-october-25-2022/</guid>
      <description>LBank Exchange Will List VNX Gold (VNXAU) on October 25, 2022 PRESS RELEASE.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
