<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bhopal News on TechnoStreet</title>
    <link>https://technostreet.github.io/tags/bhopal-news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bhopal News on TechnoStreet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 05:09:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://technostreet.github.io/tags/bhopal-news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hindutva body puts up posters in MP town demanding action against Rahul for his remarks on V D Savarkar</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hindutva-body-puts-up-posters-in-mp-town-demanding-action-against-rahul-for/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 05:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hindutva-body-puts-up-posters-in-mp-town-demanding-action-against-rahul-for/</guid>
      <description>Hindutva body puts up posters in MP town demanding action against Rahul for his remarks on V D Savarkar Burhanpur (Madhya Pradesh): A day ahead of Rahul Gandhi-led Bharat Jodo Yatra entering Madhya Pradesh, a right-wing outfit on Tuesday put up posters in Burhanpur city criticising his remarks on freedom fighter V D Savarkar and staged a protest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chhindwara: Desh Jodo Yatra can be taken out in India only, says Kamal Nath</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/chhindwara-desh-jodo-yatra-can-be-taken-out-in-india-only-says-kamal-nath/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 16:44:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/chhindwara-desh-jodo-yatra-can-be-taken-out-in-india-only-says-kamal-nath/</guid>
      <description>Chhindwara: Desh Jodo Yatra can be taken out in India only, says Kamal Nath Kamal Nath at Gandhi Chaupal in Chhindwara district on TuesdayBhopal (Madhya Pradesh): In place of giving importance to diversity of culture in India, some people indulge in narrow politics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bhind: Woman dies in stampede during religious discourse at village temple</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bhind-woman-dies-in-stampede-during-religious-discourse-at-village-temple/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 16:38:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bhind-woman-dies-in-stampede-during-religious-discourse-at-village-temple/</guid>
      <description>Bhind: Woman dies in stampede during religious discourse at village temple Bhopal (Madhya Pradesh): An elderly woman died in a stampede during a religious discourse event organised at a temple in village Dadraua of Bhind district on Tuesday, said the officials.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
