<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>F1 on TechnoStreet</title>
    <link>https://technostreet.github.io/tags/f1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in F1 on TechnoStreet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 13:30:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://technostreet.github.io/tags/f1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>When Footballing legend Pele awarded 7-time F1 Champion Michael Schumacher ahead of his final race with Ferrari</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/when-footballing-legend-pele-awarded-7-time-f1-champion-michael-schumacher-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 13:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/when-footballing-legend-pele-awarded-7-time-f1-champion-michael-schumacher-/</guid>
      <description>When Footballing legend Pele awarded 7-time F1 Champion Michael Schumacher ahead of his final race with Ferrari On the 22nd of October 2006, fans witnessed two of the greatest sportsmen of all time together on the centre stage, Brazilian Footballer Pele awarded Michael Schumacher the “Lifetime Achievement Award” for his tremendous career in F1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“For me, that’s not really a race”: Max Verstappen doesn’t get point behind having more sprint races</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/for-me-thats-not-really-a-race-max-verstappen-doesnt-get-poin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 16:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/for-me-thats-not-really-a-race-max-verstappen-doesnt-get-poin/</guid>
      <description>“For me, that’s not really a race”: Max Verstappen doesn’t get point behind having more sprint races In 2021, F1 introduced sprint races to Formula 1 weekend and saw it had significant success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“You should try driving, mate”: Lando Norris gets defensive against Ted Kravitz</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/you-should-try-driving-mate-lando-norris-gets-defensive-against-ted/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/you-should-try-driving-mate-lando-norris-gets-defensive-against-ted/</guid>
      <description>“You should try driving, mate”: Lando Norris gets defensive against Ted Kravitz Amidst his controversy with Red Bull and Max Verstappen, Ted Kravitz has gained immense spotlight over the last weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Constant digging is disrespectful” – Max Verstappen hits out at reporter Ted Kravitz as he continues to snub Sky Sports F1</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/constant-digging-is-disrespectful-max-verstappen-hits-out-at-repo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 09:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/constant-digging-is-disrespectful-max-verstappen-hits-out-at-repo/</guid>
      <description>“Constant digging is disrespectful” – Max Verstappen hits out at reporter Ted Kravitz as he continues to snub Sky Sports F1 Red Bull F1 team and Max Verstappen decided to boycott the UK, German and Italian affiliates of the British media house Sky Sports during the Mexican GP weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lewis Hamilton reveals his father’s confusion on calling 7-time World Champion ‘Sir’ after knighthood</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/lewis-hamilton-reveals-his-fathers-confusion-on-calling-7-time-world-cha/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/lewis-hamilton-reveals-his-fathers-confusion-on-calling-7-time-world-cha/</guid>
      <description>Lewis Hamilton reveals his father’s confusion on calling 7-time World Champion ‘Sir’ after knighthood Lewis Hamilton revealed that his niece and nephew call him “Sir Uncle” while his father was confused after Prince Charles knighted the Mercedes driver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“You need to have 2 mirrors” – Guenther Steiner believes Fernando Alonso should have been disqualified from US GP</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/you-need-to-have-2-mirrors-guenther-steiner-believes-fernando-alo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/you-need-to-have-2-mirrors-guenther-steiner-believes-fernando-alo/</guid>
      <description>“You need to have 2 mirrors” – Guenther Steiner believes Fernando Alonso should have been disqualified from US GP Guenther Steiner believes Fernando Alonso was driving an unsafe car after losing a side mirror following a high-speed crash with Lance Stroll.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Toto Wolff was proud to wear Red Bull colours</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/when-toto-wolff-was-proud-to-wear-red-bull-colours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/when-toto-wolff-was-proud-to-wear-red-bull-colours/</guid>
      <description>When Toto Wolff was proud to wear Red Bull colours Toto Wolff once represented Red Bull colours when he was a GT driver, and his compatriot Deitrich Mateschitz sponsored him.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
