<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on TechnoStreet</title>
    <link>https://technostreet.github.io/tags/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on TechnoStreet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 06:04:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://technostreet.github.io/tags/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Netflix kicks off 2023 on a patriotic high with Sidharth Malhotra’s ‘Mission Majnu’</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/netflix-kicks-off-2023-on-a-patriotic-high-with-sidharth-malhotras-mi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 06:04:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/netflix-kicks-off-2023-on-a-patriotic-high-with-sidharth-malhotras-mi/</guid>
      <description>Netflix kicks off 2023 on a patriotic high with Sidharth Malhotra’s ‘Mission Majnu’ Kick-staring 2023 on a patriotic high, Netflix brings to you some of the finest actors, including Sidharth Malhotra, Rashmika Mandanna, Parmeet Sethi, Sharib Hashmi, Kumud Mishra, Zakir Hussain and Mir Sarwar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samantha tears up at ‘Shaakuntalam’ trailer launch event</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samantha-tears-up-at-shaakuntalam-trailer-launch-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 05:27:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samantha-tears-up-at-shaakuntalam-trailer-launch-event/</guid>
      <description>Samantha tears up at ‘Shaakuntalam’ trailer launch event At the trailer launch event, Samantha was seen getting emotional and tearing up on the stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter’s advanced search filters for iOS coming soon</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitters-advanced-search-filters-for-ios-coming-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 05:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitters-advanced-search-filters-for-ios-coming-soon/</guid>
      <description>Twitter’s advanced search filters for iOS coming soon According to social media analyst Matt Navarra, Twitter&#39;s advanced search filters for smartphone users are &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.25 लाख वीजा जारी कर तोड़े सारे रिकॉर्ड,अमेरिका ने दी भारतीय छात्रों को अब तक की सबसे बड़ी सौगात</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/125-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 05:23:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/125-/</guid>
      <description>1.25 लाख वीजा जारी कर तोड़े सारे रिकॉर्ड,अमेरिका ने दी भारतीय छात्रों को अब तक की सबसे बड़ी सौगात क्या भारत के और करीब आना चाहता है अमेरिका?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bharat Jodo Yatra resumes journey in Uttar Pradesh</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bharat-jodo-yatra-resumes-journey-in-uttar-pradesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 05:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bharat-jodo-yatra-resumes-journey-in-uttar-pradesh/</guid>
      <description>Bharat Jodo Yatra resumes journey in Uttar Pradesh Former party chief Rahul Gandhi reached the village from Delhi ahead of the resumption of the march, Congress Uttar Pradesh unit spokesperson Anshu Awasthi said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Central Bank Gold Demand Rose at the Fastest Pace in 55 Years, Analyst Says Silver Could Outperform Gold in 2023</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/central-bank-gold-demand-rose-at-the-fastest-pace-in-55-years-analyst-says/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 14:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/central-bank-gold-demand-rose-at-the-fastest-pace-in-55-years-analyst-says/</guid>
      <description>Central Bank Gold Demand Rose at the Fastest Pace in 55 Years, Analyst Says Silver Could Outperform Gold in 2023 According to a myriad of reports, the People’s Republic of China has been buying hoards of gold during the last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Pixel to get 5G support in India in Q1 2023: Report</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-pixel-to-get-5g-support-in-india-in-q1-2023-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 13:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-pixel-to-get-5g-support-in-india-in-q1-2023-report/</guid>
      <description>Google Pixel to get 5G support in India in Q1 2023: Report 5G connectivity arrived in India in October this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung’s Galaxy S24 Ultra for 2024 will feature a new telephoto sensor</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsungs-galaxy-s24-ultra-for-2024-will-feature-a-new-telephoto-sensor/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 05:39:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsungs-galaxy-s24-ultra-for-2024-will-feature-a-new-telephoto-sensor/</guid>
      <description>Samsung’s Galaxy S24 Ultra for 2024 will feature a new telephoto sensor Samsung’s Galaxy S24 Ultra for 2024 will feature a new telephoto sensor</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stopped from using mobile, 10-year-old ends life in UP</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/stopped-from-using-mobile-10-year-old-ends-life-in-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 04:28:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/stopped-from-using-mobile-10-year-old-ends-life-in-up/</guid>
      <description>Stopped from using mobile, 10-year-old ends life in UP In a shocking incident, a 10-year-old boy allegedly died by suicide in Lucknow after his mother took away the phone and did not let him play online games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jio True 5G services now available in Andhra Pradesh</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/jio-true-5g-services-now-available-in-andhra-pradesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 04:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/jio-true-5g-services-now-available-in-andhra-pradesh/</guid>
      <description>Jio True 5G services now available in Andhra Pradesh The 5G services were launched in Tirumala, Visakhapatnam, Vijayawada, and Guntur districts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gujarat: BSF man killed for reprimanding youth for uploading daughter’s video</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gujarat-bsf-man-killed-for-reprimanding-youth-for-uploading-daughters-v/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 04:12:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gujarat-bsf-man-killed-for-reprimanding-youth-for-uploading-daughters-v/</guid>
      <description>Gujarat: BSF man killed for reprimanding youth for uploading daughter’s video The seven family members, including two women, have been arrested on charges of murder and rioting and sent to judicial custody.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corona Omicron Variant: अलर्ट मोड में भारत सरकार , जानें किस जिले की रिपोर्ट कितने डराने वाली ?</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/corona-omicron-variant-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 07:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/corona-omicron-variant-/</guid>
      <description>Corona Omicron Variant: अलर्ट मोड में भारत सरकार , जानें किस जिले की रिपोर्ट कितने डराने वाली ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>With record recruitment drives, 2022 ushered in new hope for Telangana’s youth</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/with-record-recruitment-drives-2022-ushered-in-new-hope-for-telanganas-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 14:32:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/with-record-recruitment-drives-2022-ushered-in-new-hope-for-telanganas-/</guid>
      <description>With record recruitment drives, 2022 ushered in new hope for Telangana’s youth The Year 2022 would be remembered for a long time to come as it ushered in a new hope for the unemployed youth and government job aspirants</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangladesh 82-2 on 1st morning of 2nd test against India</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bangladesh-82-2-on-1st-morning-of-2nd-test-against-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 06:19:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bangladesh-82-2-on-1st-morning-of-2nd-test-against-india/</guid>
      <description>Bangladesh 82-2 on 1st morning of 2nd test against India Following its 188-run defeat in the first test at Chattogram, Bangladesh made two changes with batter Mominul Haque and fast bowler Taskin Ahmed replacing Yasir Ali and Ebadot Hossain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>बिहार में DGP भट्टी से सीनियर हैं, अब क्या करें समकक्ष पद पर आएं या केंद्र जाएं</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-dgp-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 06:18:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-dgp-/</guid>
      <description>बिहार में DGP भट्टी से सीनियर हैं, अब क्या करें समकक्ष पद पर आएं या केंद्र जाएं पुलिस महकमे के सबसे शक्तिशाली पद पर नियुक्ति को लेकर राज्य सरकार ने जो परंपरा तोड़ी है, उससे विकट स्थिति पैदा हो गई है। 1990 बैच के भारतीय पुलिस सेवा (आईपीएस) अधिकारी राजविंदर सिंह भट्टी पुलिस महानिदेशक बना दिए गए और 1989 बैच के आईपीएस आलोक राज देखते ही रह गए। संकट यहीं शुरू हुआ […] The post बिहार में DGP भट्टी से सीनियर हैं, अब क्या करें समकक्ष पद पर आएं या केंद्र जाएं appeared first on NEWSADDAINDIA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bihar Sharab Case : जानिए शराबकांड में अब तक क्या हुए बड़े खुलासे</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bihar-sharab-case-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 07:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bihar-sharab-case-/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Sharab Case : जानिए शराबकांड में अब तक क्या हुए बड़े खुलासे Bihar Liquor Death Tragedy: बिहार में जहरीली शराब पीकर मरने वालों की संख्या बढ़कर 75 पहुंच गई है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIA charge sheets 5 CPI (Maoist) cadres for luring girls</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nia-charge-sheets-5-cpi-maoist-cadres-for-luring-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 07:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nia-charge-sheets-5-cpi-maoist-cadres-for-luring-girls/</guid>
      <description>NIA charge sheets 5 CPI (Maoist) cadres for luring girls The case was initially registered by Peddabayalu Police Station of Visakhapatnam and later re-registered by the NIA in June 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>एलन मस्क ट्विटर CEO के पद से इस्तीफा देंगे</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-ceo-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 07:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-ceo-/</guid>
      <description>एलन मस्क ट्विटर CEO के पद से इस्तीफा देंगे ट्विटर पर बड़े नीतिगत बदलावों के कारण एलन मस्क लगातार आलोचना का शिकार हो रहे हैं। ऐसे में उन्होंने ट्विटर प्रमुख के पद से पीछे हटने का फैसला किया है। हालांकि, उन्होंने इस फैसले के बारे में ट्विटर यूजर्स की राय मांगी है। मस्क ने ट्वीट कर लोगों से पूछा है कि क्या उन्हें ट्विटर […] The post एलन मस्क ट्विटर CEO के पद से इस्तीफा देंगे appeared first on NEWSADDAINDIA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Supreme Court benches to be available during winter vacation: CJI D Y Chandrachud</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/no-supreme-court-benches-to-be-available-during-winter-vacation-cji-d-y-ch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 07:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/no-supreme-court-benches-to-be-available-during-winter-vacation-cji-d-y-ch/</guid>
      <description>No Supreme Court benches to be available during winter vacation: CJI D Y Chandrachud NEW DELHI, Dec 16: Chief Justice of India D Y Chandrachud on Friday said no Supreme Court bench will be available from December 17 till January 1 during the ensuing winter vacations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ten-year-old missing girl found dead in Hyderabad</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ten-year-old-missing-girl-found-dead-in-hyderabad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 07:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ten-year-old-missing-girl-found-dead-in-hyderabad/</guid>
      <description>Ten-year-old missing girl found dead in Hyderabad Anxious family members after searching for her in all possible places, approached the police.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>थाने का चौकीदार समेत 5 की मौत से हड़कंप,अब सीवान में जहरीली शराब का कहर</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-5-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 07:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-5-/</guid>
      <description>थाने का चौकीदार समेत 5 की मौत से हड़कंप,अब सीवान में जहरीली शराब का कहर सारण में जहरीली शराब से मौतों का सिलसिला थमने को तैयार नहीं और इधर अब इसी तरह की खबरें निकटवर्ती जिले सीवान से आने लगी हैं। भगवानपुर थाना क्षेत्र में मौतों का सिलसिला शुक्रवार सुबह शुरू हुआ तो थाने के चौकीदार समेत पांच की एक-एक कर मौत हो गई। मृतकों की पहचान महेश राय, अमीर […] The post थाने का चौकीदार समेत 5 की मौत से हड़कंप,अब सीवान में जहरीली शराब का कहर appeared first on NEWSADDAINDIA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Young writer, once a catering steward, now has his poems taught in universities</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/young-writer-once-a-catering-steward-now-has-his-poems-taught-in-universi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 16:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/young-writer-once-a-catering-steward-now-has-his-poems-taught-in-universi/</guid>
      <description>Young writer, once a catering steward, now has his poems taught in universities Ramesh Karthik, who used to work as a steward in catering events to earn some money to publish his books, has been writing on the culture and lifestyle of Banjara communities, adding a dash of fiction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confusion over Saudi Tourist visa rules: Many Indians land in trouble</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/confusion-over-saudi-tourist-visa-rules-many-indians-land-in-trouble/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 16:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/confusion-over-saudi-tourist-visa-rules-many-indians-land-in-trouble/</guid>
      <description>Confusion over Saudi Tourist visa rules: Many Indians land in trouble The multiple-entry tourist visa is valid for one year from the date of issuance, and the permissible period of stay is 90 days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AP lagging behind in IT, says BJP MP</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ap-lagging-behind-in-it-says-bjp-mp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 16:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ap-lagging-behind-in-it-says-bjp-mp/</guid>
      <description>AP lagging behind in IT, says BJP MP Talking to reporters on Sunday, he pointed out that five lakh employees were working from home and several lakhs had gone to Bangalore for IT jobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Aave Companies’ latest acquisition an attempt to boost AAVE’s price action</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/is-aave-companies-latest-acquisition-an-attempt-to-boost-aaves-price-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 16:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/is-aave-companies-latest-acquisition-an-attempt-to-boost-aaves-price-/</guid>
      <description>Is Aave Companies’ latest acquisition an attempt to boost AAVE’s price action Aave Companies confirmed the acquisition of Sonar, a Web3 social gaming application AAVE’s price continued to decline and remained significantly unprofitable Aave Companies, the developers of DeFi protocol Aave and decentralized social network Lens Protocol, announced the acquisition of web3 social gaming application Sonar on 5 December.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human trafficking: Women from West Bengal, Karnataka account for 70% of victims</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/human-trafficking-women-from-west-bengal-karnataka-account-for-70-of-vic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 16:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/human-trafficking-women-from-west-bengal-karnataka-account-for-70-of-vic/</guid>
      <description>Human trafficking: Women from West Bengal, Karnataka account for 70% of victims The women forced into prostitution by the racket were also found to be from Maharashtra (15%), Delhi (7%) and other States (5%).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Punjagutta graveyard revamped, more greenery will be added: KTR</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/punjagutta-graveyard-revamped-more-greenery-will-be-added-ktr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 14:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/punjagutta-graveyard-revamped-more-greenery-will-be-added-ktr/</guid>
      <description>Punjagutta graveyard revamped, more greenery will be added: KTR The graveyard is being developed on lines of Vaikunta Mahaprasthanam in Jubilee Hills</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Woxsen University holds convocation ceremony in Hyderabad</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/woxsen-university-holds-convocation-ceremony-in-hyderabad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 14:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/woxsen-university-holds-convocation-ceremony-in-hyderabad/</guid>
      <description>Woxsen University holds convocation ceremony in Hyderabad Students of Woxsen University were awarded degree certificates on successful completion of two-year full-time MBA</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyderabad: IBS crowned overall champions at AAVEG 13</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hyderabad-ibs-crowned-overall-champions-at-aaveg-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 14:33:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hyderabad-ibs-crowned-overall-champions-at-aaveg-13/</guid>
      <description>Hyderabad: IBS crowned overall champions at AAVEG 13 ICFAI Business School (IBS) emerged overall champion after winning top honours in ten event at the three-day sports fest</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polygon (MATIC) Price Prediction 2025-2030: Read it if you are HODLing MATIC in your portfolio</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/polygon-matic-price-prediction-2025-2030-read-it-if-you-are-hodling-mati/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 15:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/polygon-matic-price-prediction-2025-2030-read-it-if-you-are-hodling-mati/</guid>
      <description>Polygon (MATIC) Price Prediction 2025-2030: Read it if you are HODLing MATIC in your portfolio Disclaimer: The datasets shared in the following article have been compiled from a set of online resources and do not reflect AMBCrypto’s own research on the subject Polygon, the blockchain firm behind the world’s 10th largest cryptocurrency MATIC, has been making considerable progress on its corporate front.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telangana: District Academic Task Force on FLN kept on hold</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/telangana-district-academic-task-force-on-fln-kept-on-hold/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 15:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/telangana-district-academic-task-force-on-fln-kept-on-hold/</guid>
      <description>Telangana: District Academic Task Force on FLN kept on hold The orders issued constituting the DATF on FLN were kept on hold due to administrative reasons</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telangana best among other Indian states in organ donation: Harish Rao</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/telangana-best-among-other-indian-states-in-organ-donation-harish-rao/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 13:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/telangana-best-among-other-indian-states-in-organ-donation-harish-rao/</guid>
      <description>Telangana best among other Indian states in organ donation: Harish Rao State government will use choppers to transport donated organs of the brain dead patients from districts hospitals to teaching hospitals</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City’s EVM Warehouse to get new machines</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/citys-evm-warehouse-to-get-new-machines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 13:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/citys-evm-warehouse-to-get-new-machines/</guid>
      <description>City’s EVM Warehouse to get new machines A permanent solution to store election-related material Electronic Voting Machines, Control Units, Ballot Units in transit from Hyderabad Mysuru: Things are falling in place to equip the Election Commission of India’s newly-constructed Electronic Voting Machine (EVM) Warehouse that was recently inaugurated in city near the new Deputy Commissioner’s Office at Siddarthanagar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10-Bed-ICU initiative comes to K.R. Hospital</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/10-bed-icu-initiative-comes-to-kr-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 13:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/10-bed-icu-initiative-comes-to-kr-hospital/</guid>
      <description>10-Bed-ICU initiative comes to K.R. Hospital CM Basavaraj Bommai to inaugurate tomorrow along with a Tele-ICU Hub Mysuru: Chief Minister Basavaraj Bommai will launch a 10-Bed-ICU initiative where ICUs with 10 beds have been set up at K.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dedicated to my mother: Srikanth Nadhamuni</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dedicated-to-my-mother-srikanth-nadhamuni/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 13:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dedicated-to-my-mother-srikanth-nadhamuni/</guid>
      <description>Dedicated to my mother: Srikanth Nadhamuni Mysuru: Speaking to Star of Mysore this morning, Srikanth Nadhamuni, co-founder of 10-Bed-ICU, said the programme consists of 10-Bed-ICU equipment donation, COVID Management Technology Platform and a Doctor Connect programme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safari in Nagarahole buffer zone dropped</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/safari-in-nagarahole-buffer-zone-dropped/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 13:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/safari-in-nagarahole-buffer-zone-dropped/</guid>
      <description>Safari in Nagarahole buffer zone dropped Scientific study to be done to retain animals inside forests and to minimise human-animal conflict Kushalnagar: Under pressure from the farmers, environment activists and the people of Kodagu, the Forest Department has dropped the proposed safari inside the buffer zone of Nagarahole Tiger Reserve that was likely to commence during winter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Need for Speed unbound gameplay video leak has surfaced online</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/need-for-speed-unbound-gameplay-video-leak-has-surfaced-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 15:47:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/need-for-speed-unbound-gameplay-video-leak-has-surfaced-online/</guid>
      <description>Need for Speed unbound gameplay video leak has surfaced online Days before its scheduled release, internet leaks of the Need for Speed Unbound gameplay video have been surfacing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PT Usha throws her hat into IOA ring, to fight for president’s post</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/pt-usha-throws-her-hat-into-ioa-ring-to-fight-for-presidents-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 15:45:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/pt-usha-throws-her-hat-into-ioa-ring-to-fight-for-presidents-post/</guid>
      <description>PT Usha throws her hat into IOA ring, to fight for president’s post The legendary P T Usha on Saturday announced that she will contest for the post of Indian Olympic Association</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charge sheet against 4 Hizbul Mujahideen associates in J&amp;K’s Rajouri</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/charge-sheet-against-4-hizbul-mujahideen-associates-in-jks-rajouri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 15:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/charge-sheet-against-4-hizbul-mujahideen-associates-in-jks-rajouri/</guid>
      <description>Charge sheet against 4 Hizbul Mujahideen associates in J&amp;amp;K’s Rajouri Jammu, Nov 26: Jammu and Kashmir Police on Saturday filed a charge sheet against four Hizbul Mujahideen associates in border Rajouri district here, an official said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cristiano Ronaldo fined, suspended for two games for incident with fan at Goodison Park</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cristiano-ronaldo-fined-suspended-for-two-games-for-incident-with-fan-at-g/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 04:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cristiano-ronaldo-fined-suspended-for-two-games-for-incident-with-fan-at-g/</guid>
      <description>Cristiano Ronaldo fined, suspended for two games for incident with fan at Goodison Park The 37-year-old is a free agent now after Manchester United announced his release from the contract on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSCHE to hold conclave on employability in Hyderabad on Nov 21</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tsche-to-hold-conclave-on-employability-in-hyderabad-on-nov-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 15:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tsche-to-hold-conclave-on-employability-in-hyderabad-on-nov-21/</guid>
      <description>TSCHE to hold conclave on employability in Hyderabad on Nov 21 State-level conclave on ‘Empowering Education to Augment Employability’ at Taj Deccan here on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telangana: Concern voiced over BJP’s misuse of central agencies</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/telangana-concern-voiced-over-bjps-misuse-of-central-agencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 13:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/telangana-concern-voiced-over-bjps-misuse-of-central-agencies/</guid>
      <description>Telangana: Concern voiced over BJP’s misuse of central agencies Nalgonda: Leaders of different organizations have in a single voice expressed strong concern over the misuse of central agencies including the Enforcement Directorate (ED) and the Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI) by the BJP government to target opposition parties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tesla to Deliver 30 Manually Built Cybertrucks in December</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tesla-to-deliver-30-manually-built-cybertrucks-in-december/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 07:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tesla-to-deliver-30-manually-built-cybertrucks-in-december/</guid>
      <description>Tesla to Deliver 30 Manually Built Cybertrucks in December Over the years, Tesla has been known for its leading role in the electric vehicles industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyderabad: Water Board to cut supply over non-payment of bills</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hyderabad-water-board-to-cut-supply-over-non-payment-of-bills/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 07:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hyderabad-water-board-to-cut-supply-over-non-payment-of-bills/</guid>
      <description>Hyderabad: Water Board to cut supply over non-payment of bills HMWS&amp;SB MD Dana Kishore instructed the officials to focus on the collection of dues from commercial and non-free water scheme connections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human killings by tigers in Adilabad trigger fake videos on social media</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/human-killings-by-tigers-in-adilabad-trigger-fake-videos-on-social-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 06:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/human-killings-by-tigers-in-adilabad-trigger-fake-videos-on-social-media/</guid>
      <description>Human killings by tigers in Adilabad trigger fake videos on social media A video of a tiger resting calmly on a tarred road was shared widely in WhatsApp groups on Wednesday and Thursday, triggering panic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZTE Launched 6G Key Technology Research and Registered for Related Patents</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/zte-launched-6g-key-technology-research-and-registered-for-related-patents/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 06:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/zte-launched-6g-key-technology-research-and-registered-for-related-patents/</guid>
      <description>ZTE Launched 6G Key Technology Research and Registered for Related Patents Chinese telecommunications firm ZTE announced that the firm tethers the utmost importance to research and development investments; as part of the process, the company ultimately joined forces to provide a place where we can connect with a 6G network from a sitting at the park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telangana: Over 8.93 lakh tonnes paddy procured for Vaanakalam season</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/telangana-over-893-lakh-tonnes-paddy-procured-for-vaanakalam-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 16:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/telangana-over-893-lakh-tonnes-paddy-procured-for-vaanakalam-season/</guid>
      <description>Telangana: Over 8.93 lakh tonnes paddy procured for Vaanakalam season The paddy procurement for Vaanakalam (Kharif) season is being undertaken at a brisk pace, with around 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pressure mine planted by Maoists explodes, injures a cow in Kothagudem</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/pressure-mine-planted-by-maoists-explodes-injures-a-cow-in-kothagudem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 16:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/pressure-mine-planted-by-maoists-explodes-injures-a-cow-in-kothagudem/</guid>
      <description>Pressure mine planted by Maoists explodes, injures a cow in Kothagudem Cherla police, Kothagudem special party personnel and bomb disposal team found two more pressure mines at the incident site and defused them on the spot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Mobiles Under 20000 in India</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/best-mobiles-under-20000-in-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 08:27:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/best-mobiles-under-20000-in-india/</guid>
      <description>Best Mobiles Under 20000 in India The flagship and premium smartphones may have been grabbing all the eyeballs across the globe, but there have been intriguing developments in the world of mid-range handsets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vice President Dhankhar meets Cambodian PM, discuss bilateral ties</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/vice-president-dhankhar-meets-cambodian-pm-discuss-bilateral-ties/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 06:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/vice-president-dhankhar-meets-cambodian-pm-discuss-bilateral-ties/</guid>
      <description>Vice President Dhankhar meets Cambodian PM, discuss bilateral ties Both leaders also witnessed the exchange of four agreements in the areas of culture, wildlife and health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attack on Owaisi in UP: SC quashes HC order granting bail to two accused</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/attack-on-owaisi-in-up-sc-quashes-hc-order-granting-bail-to-two-accused/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 07:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/attack-on-owaisi-in-up-sc-quashes-hc-order-granting-bail-to-two-accused/</guid>
      <description>Attack on Owaisi in UP: SC quashes HC order granting bail to two accused A bench of Justices M R Shah and M M Sundresh said the high court did not accord any reason while giving bail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intel Partners VCX to Unveil VCX-WebCam for Video Conferencing</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/intel-partners-vcx-to-unveil-vcx-webcam-for-video-conferencing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 07:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/intel-partners-vcx-to-unveil-vcx-webcam-for-video-conferencing/</guid>
      <description>Intel Partners VCX to Unveil VCX-WebCam for Video Conferencing Intel, in partnership with VCX-Forum, has announced the launching of the first consensus-driven camera benchmark specifically targeted for videoconferencing image quality named VCX-WebCam 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women Safety Wing of Telangana police invites applications for various posts on contract basis</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/women-safety-wing-of-telangana-police-invites-applications-for-various-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 07:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/women-safety-wing-of-telangana-police-invites-applications-for-various-post/</guid>
      <description>Women Safety Wing of Telangana police invites applications for various posts on contract basis Hyderabad: Telangana police Women Safety Wing is inviting applications from eligible candidates for different posts on a contractual basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail’s old design is going away forever: What that means for you</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gmails-old-design-is-going-away-forever-what-that-means-for-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 04:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gmails-old-design-is-going-away-forever-what-that-means-for-you/</guid>
      <description>Gmail’s old design is going away forever: What that means for you Google today announced that it is making the new Gmail interface standard for all users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter will introduce ‘Official’ label for some high-profile verified accounts</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-will-introduce-official-label-for-some-high-profile-verified-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 03:50:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-will-introduce-official-label-for-some-high-profile-verified-/</guid>
      <description>Twitter will introduce ‘Official’ label for some high-profile verified accounts Billionaire Elon Musk’s social media platform Twitter will introduce an “Official” label for select verified accounts including major media outlets and governments when it launches its new $8 premium subscription product, its early stage products executive Esther Crawford said on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Inseam Measurement: Let’s Check Out The Ways</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-inseam-measurement-lets-check-out-the-ways/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 07:34:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-inseam-measurement-lets-check-out-the-ways/</guid>
      <description>How To Inseam Measurement: Let’s Check Out The Ways If you want to look your best in jeans, you need to know your inseam measurement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wi-Fi flaw lets drone track your smart devices through walls: How it works</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/wi-fi-flaw-lets-drone-track-your-smart-devices-through-walls-how-it-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 04:41:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/wi-fi-flaw-lets-drone-track-your-smart-devices-through-walls-how-it-works/</guid>
      <description>Wi-Fi flaw lets drone track your smart devices through walls: How it works Wi-Fi is one of the most commonly used wireless standards that is used for connecting devices such as personal computers, tablets, smartphones, printers, smart TVs, smart home devices such as lights and speakers and smart home appliances such as washing machines, refrigerators and air conditioners with the internet in a small space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indie game ‘Wavetale’ survives Stadia’s obliteration, coming soon to consoles and PC</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indie-game-wavetale-survives-stadias-obliteration-coming-soon-to-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 17:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indie-game-wavetale-survives-stadias-obliteration-coming-soon-to-/</guid>
      <description>Indie game ‘Wavetale’ survives Stadia’s obliteration, coming soon to consoles and PC When Google Stadia made the insanely rash decision to shutter its consumer-facing cloud gaming platform, a handful of games were threatened to be dragged into the pit with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kothagudem: CI extends financial support to ailing man</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/kothagudem-ci-extends-financial-support-to-ailing-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/kothagudem-ci-extends-financial-support-to-ailing-man/</guid>
      <description>Kothagudem: CI extends financial support to ailing man Yellandu Inspector of Police, Banoth Raju extended financial assistance to an ailing private worker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OU invites applications for admissions to Diploma in Radiological Physics</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ou-invites-applications-for-admissions-to-diploma-in-radiological-physics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ou-invites-applications-for-admissions-to-diploma-in-radiological-physics/</guid>
      <description>OU invites applications for admissions to Diploma in Radiological Physics The course is offered by department of Physics, OU, in collaboration with certain hospitals in Hyderabad</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Horse Racing: Elusive and Rising Tycoon shine in morning trials</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/horse-racing-elusive-and-rising-tycoon-shine-in-morning-trials/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/horse-racing-elusive-and-rising-tycoon-shine-in-morning-trials/</guid>
      <description>Horse Racing: Elusive and Rising Tycoon shine in morning trials Elusive and Rising Tycoon impressed when the following horses were exercised at Malakpet Race Course on Tuesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Punjabi Singer AP Dhillon hospitalised after suffering injury during US tour</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/punjabi-singer-ap-dhillon-hospitalised-after-suffering-injury-during-us-tou/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:27:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/punjabi-singer-ap-dhillon-hospitalised-after-suffering-injury-during-us-tou/</guid>
      <description>Punjabi Singer AP Dhillon hospitalised after suffering injury during US tour On Tuesday, the ‘Excuses’ singer took to his Instagram and informed his fans and followers about the same</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BJP MP Laxman doesn’t see early polls in Telangana</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bjp-mp-laxman-doesnt-see-early-polls-in-telangana/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bjp-mp-laxman-doesnt-see-early-polls-in-telangana/</guid>
      <description>BJP MP Laxman doesn’t see early polls in Telangana Speaking at a Meet the Press programme at the Press Club at Somajiguda here, Laxman stated that even if the Chief Minister dissolves the state assembly, there is very less possibility of conducting early polls, as the entire decision lies with the Election Commission.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Workspace Individual accounts now have up to 1TB storage space</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-workspace-individual-accounts-now-have-up-to-1tb-storage-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 06:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-workspace-individual-accounts-now-have-up-to-1tb-storage-space/</guid>
      <description>Google Workspace Individual accounts now have up to 1TB storage space Google has announced that it will soon introduce more features for “Workspace Individual” users, including an increase in storage capacity and advances in email personalisation for all customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Rupee trials to start from Tuesday, November 1</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/digital-rupee-trials-to-start-from-tuesday-november-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/digital-rupee-trials-to-start-from-tuesday-november-1/</guid>
      <description>Digital Rupee trials to start from Tuesday, November 1 As promised by RBI, the first pilot of the Digital currency, the Digital Rupee (e₹) will commence on November 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter head Elon Musk shots down job cuts to avoid paying stock grants rumours</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-head-elon-musk-shots-down-job-cuts-to-avoid-paying-stock-grants-rum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 05:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-head-elon-musk-shots-down-job-cuts-to-avoid-paying-stock-grants-rum/</guid>
      <description>Twitter head Elon Musk shots down job cuts to avoid paying stock grants rumours Tesla, SpaceX CEO Elon Musk took over Twitter last week and the first thing that he did was to fire top executives including CEO Parag Agrawal, CFO Ned Segal, and Head of Legal Policy, Trust and Safety Vijaya Gadde.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily walking is the secret to lead an active life, says 87-year-old cardiologist</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/daily-walking-is-the-secret-to-lead-an-active-life-says-87-year-old-cardio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/daily-walking-is-the-secret-to-lead-an-active-life-says-87-year-old-cardio/</guid>
      <description>Daily walking is the secret to lead an active life, says 87-year-old cardiologist Hyderabad: What is the ‘secret sauce’ that drives an 87-year-old cardiologist to lead an active life, treat his patients on a daily basis, and be considered as an experienced physician with best diagnostic skills in town?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traffic diversions in view of Bharath Jodo Yatra in Telangana</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/traffic-diversions-in-view-of-bharath-jodo-yatra-in-telangana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:47:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/traffic-diversions-in-view-of-bharath-jodo-yatra-in-telangana/</guid>
      <description>Traffic diversions in view of Bharath Jodo Yatra in Telangana The Cyberabad traffic police in view of the &#39;Bharath Jodo Yatra&#39; have announced certain traffic diversions for four days starting Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T-Hub, MEE School announces Cinepreneur Entrepreneurship Certification course</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/t-hub-mee-school-announces-cinepreneur-entrepreneurship-certification-cour/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/t-hub-mee-school-announces-cinepreneur-entrepreneurship-certification-cour/</guid>
      <description>T-Hub, MEE School announces Cinepreneur Entrepreneurship Certification course Cinepreneur is a Media and Entrepreneurship (M&amp;E) program that imparts module-based learning for media business enthusiasts and aspirants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How a new update might just save Polygon’s declining dApp activity</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-a-new-update-might-just-save-polygons-declining-dapp-activity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-a-new-update-might-just-save-polygons-declining-dapp-activity/</guid>
      <description>How a new update might just save Polygon’s declining dApp activity Polygon’s MATIC is now ranked 11th in terms of market cap, with the altcoin having garnered a lot of interest due to its increasing number of collaborations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google and Coinbase join forces for the future of Web3</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-and-coinbase-join-forces-for-the-future-of-web3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:03:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-and-coinbase-join-forces-for-the-future-of-web3/</guid>
      <description>Google and Coinbase join forces for the future of Web3 Cryptocurrency as a means of decentralized money may be volatile and uncertain but building the future of the web on decentralized blockchain technologies is an explosively emerging market and many tech giants are jumping into the Web3 arena feet first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy M23 5G, Galaxy A04, Galaxy A04e to launch in India soon as support pages go live</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-galaxy-m23-5g-galaxy-a04-galaxy-a04e-to-launch-in-india-soon-as-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 15:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-galaxy-m23-5g-galaxy-a04-galaxy-a04e-to-launch-in-india-soon-as-s/</guid>
      <description>Samsung Galaxy M23 5G, Galaxy A04, Galaxy A04e to launch in India soon as support pages go live Samsung is gearing to launch a bunch of new M-series and A-series smartphones in India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Byju’s allegedly shuts Kerala office, forces employees to resign</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/byjus-allegedly-shuts-kerala-office-forces-employees-to-resign/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 09:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/byjus-allegedly-shuts-kerala-office-forces-employees-to-resign/</guid>
      <description>Byju’s allegedly shuts Kerala office, forces employees to resign Byju’s, the world’s most valued edtech firm backed by Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg’s Chan Zuckerberg Initiative, may have shut its office in Technopark, Thiruvananthapuram, Kerala and asked employees working there to resign.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One UI 5.0 update roll out scheduled released for a host of Samsung devices</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/one-ui-50-update-roll-out-scheduled-released-for-a-host-of-samsung-devices/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 07:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/one-ui-50-update-roll-out-scheduled-released-for-a-host-of-samsung-devices/</guid>
      <description>One UI 5.0 update roll out scheduled released for a host of Samsung devices Samsung has announced the One UI 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX usurps Boeing to become NASA’s largest for-profit vendor</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/spacex-usurps-boeing-to-become-nasas-largest-for-profit-vendor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 06:34:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/spacex-usurps-boeing-to-become-nasas-largest-for-profit-vendor/</guid>
      <description>SpaceX usurps Boeing to become NASA’s largest for-profit vendor Fourteen years after winning its first major NASA contract, data shared by Aviation Week reporter Irene Klotz shows that SpaceX has usurped every other major aerospace company in the US to become the space agency’s largest for-profit vendor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motorola Moto Razr 2022 flip phone arrives in Europe, India launch likely</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/motorola-moto-razr-2022-flip-phone-arrives-in-europe-india-launch-likely/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 14:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/motorola-moto-razr-2022-flip-phone-arrives-in-europe-india-launch-likely/</guid>
      <description>Motorola Moto Razr 2022 flip phone arrives in Europe, India launch likely Motorola has announced the international release of its next-generation flagship foldable smartphone Moto Razr 2022, which comes with Qualcomms’ latest chipset, Snapdragon 8 Plus Gen 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redmi Note 12 Pro&#43; 5G camera specifications confirmed ahead of launch</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/redmi-note-12-pro-5g-camera-specifications-confirmed-ahead-of-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/redmi-note-12-pro-5g-camera-specifications-confirmed-ahead-of-launch/</guid>
      <description>Redmi Note 12 Pro+ 5G camera specifications confirmed ahead of launch Redmi Note 12 series is arriving on October 27 and the brand is building hype around it before the launch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy S22 Series gets Android 13-based One UI 5 update: Check its top features here</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-galaxy-s22-series-gets-android-13-based-one-ui-5-update-check-its-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samsung-galaxy-s22-series-gets-android-13-based-one-ui-5-update-check-its-/</guid>
      <description>Samsung Galaxy S22 Series gets Android 13-based One UI 5 update: Check its top features here Samsung has finally started rolling out Android 13-based One UI 5 update to its Galaxy S22 series smartphones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What of Bitcoin [BTC] when things start getting ‘difficult’</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/what-of-bitcoin-btc-when-things-start-getting-difficult/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 02:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/what-of-bitcoin-btc-when-things-start-getting-difficult/</guid>
      <description>What of Bitcoin [BTC] when things start getting ‘difficult’ Bitcoin mining has been subject to a lot of controversies of late.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can Reddit NFTs’ launch have a positive impact on Polygon’s growth?</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/can-reddit-nfts-launch-have-a-positive-impact-on-polygons-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/can-reddit-nfts-launch-have-a-positive-impact-on-polygons-growth/</guid>
      <description>Can Reddit NFTs’ launch have a positive impact on Polygon’s growth?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why you should read this before going all in on Tron [TRX]</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/why-you-should-read-this-before-going-all-in-on-tron-trx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 23:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/why-you-should-read-this-before-going-all-in-on-tron-trx/</guid>
      <description>Why you should read this before going all in on Tron [TRX] Tron [TRX], the cryptocurrency currently ranked 14th in terms of market cap, was in the news recently for its collaboration with the Dominican government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EOS’s presence around this liquidity pocket will keep these parties interested</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/eoss-presence-around-this-liquidity-pocket-will-keep-these-parties-inter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 22:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/eoss-presence-around-this-liquidity-pocket-will-keep-these-parties-inter/</guid>
      <description>EOS’s presence around this liquidity pocket will keep these parties interested Disclaimer: The information presented does not constitute financial, investment, trading, or other types of advice and is solely the writer’s opinion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Texas Governor celebrates Diwali with Indian-Americans</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/texas-governor-celebrates-diwali-with-indian-americans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 07:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/texas-governor-celebrates-diwali-with-indian-americans/</guid>
      <description>Texas Governor celebrates Diwali with Indian-Americans The couple was dressed in ethnic Indian attire as they welcomed guests, and also lit the traditional lamp to mark the festival.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk visits Monterrey, Nuevo León, Mexico &amp; chats with officials</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-visits-monterrey-nuevo-len-mexico-chats-with-officials/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 21:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-visits-monterrey-nuevo-len-mexico-chats-with-officials/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk visits Monterrey, Nuevo León, Mexico &amp;amp; chats with officials Tesla CEO Elon Musk took a trip to Nuevo León, Mexico, this weekend, where he was spotted talking with a state official and the wife of Governor Samuel García Sepulveda, Mariana Rodríguez.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flipkart Big Diwali Sale: Ordered gaming laptop from Flipkart received a giant stone and e-waste</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/flipkart-big-diwali-sale-ordered-gaming-laptop-from-flipkart-received-a-gi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 13:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/flipkart-big-diwali-sale-ordered-gaming-laptop-from-flipkart-received-a-gi/</guid>
      <description>Flipkart Big Diwali Sale: Ordered gaming laptop from Flipkart received a giant stone and e-waste Chinmaya Ramana of Mangalore, Karnataka ordered a gaming laptop on Flipkart in the Big Diwali Sale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gujarat BJP targets Kejriwal over cracker ban in Delhi</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gujarat-bjp-targets-kejriwal-over-cracker-ban-in-delhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 08:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gujarat-bjp-targets-kejriwal-over-cracker-ban-in-delhi/</guid>
      <description>Gujarat BJP targets Kejriwal over cracker ban in Delhi Rajkot: Gujarat BJP chief C R Paatil has hit out at Delhi Chief Minister Arvind Kejriwal over his government’s decision to completely ban firecrackers in the national capital, and dubbed such people “anti-religious” who were stopping citizens from celebrating their festivals.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
