<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>business on TechnoStreet</title>
    <link>https://technostreet.github.io/categories/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in business on TechnoStreet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 05:11:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://technostreet.github.io/categories/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jobs 2023: NTRO में निकली इन पद पर वैकेंसी, फटाफट करें अप्लाई</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/jobs-2023-ntro-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 05:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/jobs-2023-ntro-/</guid>
      <description>Jobs 2023: NTRO में निकली इन पद पर वैकेंसी, फटाफट करें अप्लाई NTRO Recruitment 2023: इंजीनियरिंग की पढ़ाई कर चुके युवाओं के लिए अच्छी खबर है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cognizant CEO Ravi Kumar to make $7 million in annual salary</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cognizant-ceo-ravi-kumar-to-make-7-million-in-annual-salary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 04:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cognizant-ceo-ravi-kumar-to-make-7-million-in-annual-salary/</guid>
      <description>Cognizant CEO Ravi Kumar to make $7 million in annual salary In addition, he is offered a one-time new hire award of $5 million within one year of his joining based on stockholder return, $3 million as PSUs over four years subject to meeting stock price performance, and $750,000 as a sign-in bonus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>​Sarkari Naukri: इस राज्य में निकली 1000 से ज्यादा पद पर भर्ती, जानें कौन कर सकता है आवेदन</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sarkari-naukri-1000-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 04:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sarkari-naukri-1000-/</guid>
      <description>​Sarkari Naukri: इस राज्य में निकली 1000 से ज्यादा पद पर भर्ती, जानें कौन कर सकता है आवेदन ​RSMSSB Recruitment 2023: राजस्थान चिकित्सा एवं स्वास्थ्य विभाग ने एक भर्ती नोटिफिकेशन जारी कर असिस्टेंट रेडियोग्राफर के बम्पर पद पर भर्तियां निकाली हैं.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Equities trade lower in early trade</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/equities-trade-lower-in-early-trade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 04:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/equities-trade-lower-in-early-trade/</guid>
      <description>Equities trade lower in early trade Mumbai, January 13 Market benchmarks declined in early trade on Friday dragged down by index major Reliance Industries and IT counters along with continuous foreign fund outflows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>शेयर बाजार में गिरावट, सेंसेक्स 60000 और निफ्टी 18000 के नीचे</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 04:04:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-/</guid>
      <description>शेयर बाजार में गिरावट, सेंसेक्स 60000 और निफ्टी 18000 के नीचे शेयर बाजार में सप्ताह के अंतिम कारोबारी दिन भी एक और गिरावट देखने को मिली.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sah Polymers IPO: साह पॉलीमर्स की स्टॉक एक्सचेंज पर बंपर लिस्टिंग, 31 फीसदी के प्रीमियम पर लिस्ट हुआ शेयर</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sah-polymers-ipo-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 05:04:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sah-polymers-ipo-/</guid>
      <description>Sah Polymers IPO: साह पॉलीमर्स की स्टॉक एक्सचेंज पर बंपर लिस्टिंग, 31 फीसदी के प्रीमियम पर लिस्ट हुआ शेयर Sah Polymers IPO Listing: साह पॉलीमर्स (Sah Polymers) की स्टॉक एक्सचेंज पर शानदार लिस्टिंग हुई है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tour Package: कम पैसों में करना चाहते हैं दुबई की सैर तो IRCTC टूर पैकेज में कराएं बुकिंग, मिलेगी रहने खाने की सुविधा</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tour-package-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 04:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tour-package-/</guid>
      <description>Tour Package: कम पैसों में करना चाहते हैं दुबई की सैर तो IRCTC टूर पैकेज में कराएं बुकिंग, मिलेगी रहने खाने की सुविधा abplive</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency Rate Today, 12th January 2023: बिटकॉइन में बड़ी तेजी, 18000 डॉलर के पार पहुंचा प्राइस, अन्य कॉइन में भी अच्छी उछाल</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cryptocurrency-rate-today-12th-january-2023-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 04:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cryptocurrency-rate-today-12th-january-2023-/</guid>
      <description>Cryptocurrency Rate Today, 12th January 2023: बिटकॉइन में बड़ी तेजी, 18000 डॉलर के पार पहुंचा प्राइस, अन्य कॉइन में भी अच्छी उछाल Cryptocurrency Rate Today: ग्लोबल स्तर पर क्रिप्टोकरेंसी में अच्छी उछाल देखने को मिली है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FD Rate Hike: Axis बैंक के साथ ही इस सरकारी बैंक ने भी बढ़ाई FD पर अपनी ब्याज दर, यहां जानें ग्राहकों को कितना मिल रहा फायदा</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/fd-rate-hike-axis-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 04:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/fd-rate-hike-axis-/</guid>
      <description>FD Rate Hike: Axis बैंक के साथ ही इस सरकारी बैंक ने भी बढ़ाई FD पर अपनी ब्याज दर, यहां जानें ग्राहकों को कितना मिल रहा फायदा Fixed Deposit Rates: साल 2022 में महंगाई ने आम लोगों की कमर तोड़ रखी थी.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Much Does an Average Commercial Auto Insurance Cost?</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-much-does-an-average-commercial-auto-insurance-cost/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 03:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-much-does-an-average-commercial-auto-insurance-cost/</guid>
      <description>How Much Does an Average Commercial Auto Insurance Cost? Commercial auto insurance is a kind of insurance that is used to protect vehicles used for any business purpose or vehicles owned by businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock Market Opening: मामूली तेजी के साथ खुले भारतीय शेयर बाजार, आईटी स्टॉक्स में निवेशकों की खरीदारी</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/stock-market-opening-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 03:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/stock-market-opening-/</guid>
      <description>Stock Market Opening: मामूली तेजी के साथ खुले भारतीय शेयर बाजार, आईटी स्टॉक्स में निवेशकों की खरीदारी Stock Market Opening On 12th January 2023: भारतीय शेयर बाजार में मामूली तेजी के साथ कारोबार की शुरुआत हुई है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WEF Says Crypto Will Go Mainstream, But IMF Predicts 2023 Recession</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/wef-says-crypto-will-go-mainstream-but-imf-predicts-2023-recession/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 07:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/wef-says-crypto-will-go-mainstream-but-imf-predicts-2023-recession/</guid>
      <description>WEF Says Crypto Will Go Mainstream, But IMF Predicts 2023 Recession The CBDDC supporters The World Economic Forum (WEF) believes that responsible regulation and long-term experimentation will ensure cryptocurrency’s place in the global economy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia Boosts The Export Capacity Of Its Natural Gas Pipeline To China</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/russia-boosts-the-export-capacity-of-its-natural-gas-pipeline-to-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 07:23:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/russia-boosts-the-export-capacity-of-its-natural-gas-pipeline-to-china/</guid>
      <description>Russia Boosts The Export Capacity Of Its Natural Gas Pipeline To China Russia has increased the export capacity of its pipeline to China to over 60 million cubic meters daily, China Media Group has reported, with total flows this year seen at over 22 billion cubic meters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Federal Bank&#39;s loan grow 19.1% YoY in Q3; deposits cross Rs 2 trn mark</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/federal-banks-loan-grow-191-yoy-in-q3-deposits-cross-rs-2-trn-mark/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 07:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/federal-banks-loan-grow-191-yoy-in-q3-deposits-cross-rs-2-trn-mark/</guid>
      <description>Federal Bank&amp;rsquo;s loan grow 19.1% YoY in Q3; deposits cross Rs 2 trn mark Pace of customer liabilities expands at slower pace of 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No ‘respite’ for exploits, flash loans or exit scams in 2023: Cybersecurity firm</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/no-respite-for-exploits-flash-loans-or-exit-scams-in-2023-cybersecu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 07:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/no-respite-for-exploits-flash-loans-or-exit-scams-in-2023-cybersecu/</guid>
      <description>No ‘respite’ for exploits, flash loans or exit scams in 2023: Cybersecurity firm The industry can expect “further attempts from hackers targeting bridges in 2023,” while users are advised to be more cautious with their private keys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Filings Reveal a $3B Crypto Trader who Still Lives with his Mom</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/public-filings-reveal-a-3b-crypto-trader-who-still-lives-with-his-mom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 07:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/public-filings-reveal-a-3b-crypto-trader-who-still-lives-with-his-mom/</guid>
      <description>Public Filings Reveal a $3B Crypto Trader who Still Lives with his Mom According to public records, this crypto trader made over $7 million in profits in 2021 while living at his parent’s house in Sydney, Australia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum transactions 338% higher in 2022 but Bitcoin remains most popular</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ethereum-transactions-338-higher-in-2022-but-bitcoin-remains-most-popular/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 06:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ethereum-transactions-338-higher-in-2022-but-bitcoin-remains-most-popular/</guid>
      <description>Ethereum transactions 338% higher in 2022 but Bitcoin remains most popular The total number of transactions on the Ethereum network more than quadrupled that of Bitcoin, but Bitcoin remained the most searched cryptocurrency in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyundai Motor elevates senior management; Tarun Garg becomes COO</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hyundai-motor-elevates-senior-management-tarun-garg-becomes-coo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 06:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hyundai-motor-elevates-senior-management-tarun-garg-becomes-coo/</guid>
      <description>Hyundai Motor elevates senior management; Tarun Garg becomes COO Tarun Garg, who was earlier Director (Sales, Marketing Service) will oversee sales, marketing, service and product strategy in his new role, Hyundai Motor India Ltd (HMIL) said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>InCred Capital acquires Orowealth to foray into retail wealth-tech with launch of InCred Money</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/incred-capital-acquires-orowealth-to-foray-into-retail-wealth-tech-with-lau/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 05:49:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/incred-capital-acquires-orowealth-to-foray-into-retail-wealth-tech-with-lau/</guid>
      <description>InCred Capital acquires Orowealth to foray into retail wealth-tech with launch of InCred Money InCred Money has been launched with the acquisition of Orowealth in an all-cash deal</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyundai Motor India Announces Elevation Of Senior Management</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hyundai-motor-india-announces-elevation-of-senior-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 05:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hyundai-motor-india-announces-elevation-of-senior-management/</guid>
      <description>Hyundai Motor India Announces Elevation Of Senior Management Tarun Garg now becomes the Chief Operating Officer at HMIL while Gopala Krishnan CS becomes Chief Manufacturing Officer</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toyota&#39;s Indian Unit Warns Of A Possible Customer Data Breach</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/toyotas-indian-unit-warns-of-a-possible-customer-data-breach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 05:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/toyotas-indian-unit-warns-of-a-possible-customer-data-breach/</guid>
      <description>Toyota&amp;rsquo;s Indian Unit Warns Of A Possible Customer Data Breach Toyota India said it has notified the relevant Indian authorities of the data breach at Toyota Kirloskar Motor</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Auto Sales December 2022: Ather Energy Registers Best Ever Monthly Sales With 9,187 Units Sold</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/auto-sales-december-2022-ather-energy-registers-best-ever-monthly-sales-wi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 05:12:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/auto-sales-december-2022-ather-energy-registers-best-ever-monthly-sales-wi/</guid>
      <description>Auto Sales December 2022: Ather Energy Registers Best Ever Monthly Sales With 9,187 Units Sold Ather Energy has registered its highest ever monthly sales, selling 9,187 units in December 2022, which is a massive 389 per cent year-on-year growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bajaj Auto sales fall 22% to 2,81,486 units in December</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bajaj-auto-sales-fall-22-to-281486-units-in-december/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 05:08:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bajaj-auto-sales-fall-22-to-281486-units-in-december/</guid>
      <description>Bajaj Auto sales fall 22% to 2,81,486 units in December As per the regulatory filing, the total domestic sales rose by 2 percent YoY to 1,48,555 units as compare to 1,45,979 in the same month a year ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last date for higher EPS pension, PAN-Aadhaar linking, investing in PMVVY, other money deadlines of 2023</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/last-date-for-higher-eps-pension-pan-aadhaar-linking-investing-in-pmvvy-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 05:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/last-date-for-higher-eps-pension-pan-aadhaar-linking-investing-in-pmvvy-/</guid>
      <description>Last date for higher EPS pension, PAN-Aadhaar linking, investing in PMVVY, other money deadlines of 2023 With the arrival of new year 2023, there are many deadlines which an individual should know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Central Bank Gold Demand Rose at the Fastest Pace in 55 Years, Analyst Says Silver Could Outperform Gold in 2023</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/central-bank-gold-demand-rose-at-the-fastest-pace-in-55-years-analyst-says/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 14:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/central-bank-gold-demand-rose-at-the-fastest-pace-in-55-years-analyst-says/</guid>
      <description>Central Bank Gold Demand Rose at the Fastest Pace in 55 Years, Analyst Says Silver Could Outperform Gold in 2023 According to a myriad of reports, the People’s Republic of China has been buying hoards of gold during the last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ola कब लॉन्च करेगी अपनी इलेक्ट्रिक बाइक और कार? फाउंडर भाविश अग्रवाल ने दिया ये जवाब</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ola-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 13:29:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ola-/</guid>
      <description>Ola कब लॉन्च करेगी अपनी इलेक्ट्रिक बाइक और कार? फाउंडर भाविश अग्रवाल ने दिया ये जवाब इलेक्ट्रिक टू-व्हीलर मैनुफैक्चरार Ola Electric आने वाले दिनों में अपने कुछ खास प्रोडक्ट लॉन्च करने वाली है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ये शहर बना 2022 का &#39;डिजिटल पेमेंट कैपिटल ऑफ इंडिया&#39;</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-2022-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 13:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-2022-/</guid>
      <description>ये शहर बना 2022 का &amp;lsquo;डिजिटल पेमेंट कैपिटल ऑफ इंडिया&amp;rsquo; Paytm ने साल 2022 पर आधारित अपनी ईयर-एंड रिपोर्ट पेश की है, जिसमें देश के कई हिस्सों में डिजिटल ट्रांजैक्शन कई गुना बढ़ने का खुलासा हुआ है। रिपोर्ट के मुताबिक, डिजिटल ट्रांजैक्शन के मामले में दिल्ली-एनसीआर &#39;डिजिटल पेमेंट कैपिटल ऑफ इंडिया&#39; बनकर उभरा है। वहीं, भारत के नॉर्थ-ईस्ट हिस्से में सबसे ज्यादा ट्रांजैकशन का रिकॉर</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>केंद्र ने NSC और डाकघर जमाओं पर बढ़ाई ब्याज दरें, PPF में कोई बदलाव नहीं</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-nsc-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 13:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-nsc-/</guid>
      <description>केंद्र ने NSC और डाकघर जमाओं पर बढ़ाई ब्याज दरें, PPF में कोई बदलाव नहीं राष्ट्रीय बचत प्रमाणपत्र (NSC) पर एक जनवरी से सात फीसदी की दर से ब्याज मिलेगा.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>जानिए क्या है 4K और 8K टीवी में फर्क, खरीदारी हो जाएगी आसान</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-4k-8k-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 13:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-4k-8k-/</guid>
      <description>जानिए क्या है 4K और 8K टीवी में फर्क, खरीदारी हो जाएगी आसान इन दिनों जब हम यूट्यूब या नेटफ्लिक्स देखते हैं तो हमें कंटेंट की क्वालिटी बहुत पसंद आती है। इस क्वालिटी का कारण 4K की वजह से है, लेकिन अब मार्केट में 8K स्मार्ट टीवी आ चुका है।</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to Expect from Crypto the Year After FTX</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/what-to-expect-from-crypto-the-year-after-ftx/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 08:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/what-to-expect-from-crypto-the-year-after-ftx/</guid>
      <description>What to Expect from Crypto the Year After FTX Users continue to seek to divert funds away from centralized exchanges, paving the way for blockchain-based alternatives to thrive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The FTX Contagion Goes on: Midas Investments Closes Down</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-ftx-contagion-goes-on-midas-investments-closes-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 08:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-ftx-contagion-goes-on-midas-investments-closes-down/</guid>
      <description>The FTX Contagion Goes on: Midas Investments Closes Down Due to severe financial losses caused by Celsius’ bankruptcy and FTX’s debacle, the cryptocurrency platform Midas Investments disabled deposits and swaps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Litecoin [LTC]: Do not get Carried Away by these Bullish Signs</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/litecoin-ltc-do-not-get-carried-away-by-these-bullish-signs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 07:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/litecoin-ltc-do-not-get-carried-away-by-these-bullish-signs/</guid>
      <description>Litecoin [LTC]: Do not get Carried Away by these Bullish Signs Litecoin [LTC] holders are set to end the year on a high note, as the altcoin sees a historical increase in whale accumulation, according to Santiment data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>California Regulator Warns of 17 Crypto Websites Suspected of Fraud</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/california-regulator-warns-of-17-crypto-websites-suspected-of-fraud/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 07:35:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/california-regulator-warns-of-17-crypto-websites-suspected-of-fraud/</guid>
      <description>California Regulator Warns of 17 Crypto Websites Suspected of Fraud The DFPI last issued such a large number of crypto scam alerts in June, when it warned about 26 suspect crypto platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nokhra solar project#39;s 50MW capacity to begin commercial operation from December 30: NTPC</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nokhra-solar-project39s-50mw-capacity-to-begin-commercial-operation-from-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 07:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nokhra-solar-project39s-50mw-capacity-to-begin-commercial-operation-from-/</guid>
      <description>Nokhra solar project#39;s 50MW capacity to begin commercial operation from December 30: NTPC Earlier this month, a 100 MW unit of the project started commercial operation, as per a BSE filing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sam Bankman-Fried’s Life on Bail: Armed Guards, Daily Jogs and Gawkers</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sam-bankman-frieds-life-on-bail-armed-guards-daily-jogs-and-gawkers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 07:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sam-bankman-frieds-life-on-bail-armed-guards-daily-jogs-and-gawkers/</guid>
      <description>Sam Bankman-Fried’s Life on Bail: Armed Guards, Daily Jogs and Gawkers In comparison to his prison quarters in The Bahamas, the former billionaire appears to be leading a fairly normal life while under house arrest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shiba Inu Community Bullish for Potential 2023 Shibarium Release</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/shiba-inu-community-bullish-for-potential-2023-shibarium-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 07:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/shiba-inu-community-bullish-for-potential-2023-shibarium-release/</guid>
      <description>Shiba Inu Community Bullish for Potential 2023 Shibarium Release The Shiba Inu community is optimistic about the new year, looking forward to the release of layer 2 Shibarium and potential new payment integrations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Claims against Dr Reddy#39;s over Revlimid in US dismissed</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/claims-against-dr-reddy39s-over-revlimid-in-us-dismissed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 06:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/claims-against-dr-reddy39s-over-revlimid-in-us-dismissed/</guid>
      <description>Claims against Dr Reddy#39;s over Revlimid in US dismissed In a regulatory filing, the company said on December 22, 2022 and December 27, 2022, the plaintiffs voluntarily dismissed Dr Reddy#39;s Laboratories Ltd and Dr Reddy#39;s Laboratories, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supertech offered 9,705 flats without occupancy certificates: Interim resolution professional to NCLAT</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/supertech-offered-9705-flats-without-occupancy-certificates-interim-resol/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 05:32:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/supertech-offered-9705-flats-without-occupancy-certificates-interim-resol/</guid>
      <description>Supertech offered 9,705 flats without occupancy certificates: Interim resolution professional to NCLAT The Interim Resolution Professional (IRP) Hitesh Goel has submitted the status report about the company to the National Company Law Appellate Tribunal (NCLAT).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kraken Shutting Down Crypto Exchange in Japan Citing Weak Global Crypto Market</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/kraken-shutting-down-crypto-exchange-in-japan-citing-weak-global-crypto-mar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 05:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/kraken-shutting-down-crypto-exchange-in-japan-citing-weak-global-crypto-mar/</guid>
      <description>Kraken Shutting Down Crypto Exchange in Japan Citing Weak Global Crypto Market Cryptocurrency exchange Kraken is shutting down services in Japan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPMSP Exam Date Sheet 2023: जल्द जारी होंगी परीक्षा तारीखें, एक क्लिक में जानें लेटेस्ट अपडेट</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/upmsp-exam-date-sheet-2023-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 04:38:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/upmsp-exam-date-sheet-2023-/</guid>
      <description>UPMSP Exam Date Sheet 2023: जल्द जारी होंगी परीक्षा तारीखें, एक क्लिक में जानें लेटेस्ट अपडेट UP Board 10th, 12th Exam 2023 Dates: उत्तर प्रदेश बोर्ड परीक्षाओं की तारीख रिलीज होने का स्टूडेंट्स को बेसब्री से इंतजार है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold rates today stable and silver hikes in Hyderabad, Bangalore, Kerala, Visakhapatnam - 28 December 2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-rates-today-stable-and-silver-hikes-in-hyderabad-bangalore-kerala-v/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 03:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-rates-today-stable-and-silver-hikes-in-hyderabad-bangalore-kerala-v/</guid>
      <description>Gold rates today stable and silver hikes in Hyderabad, Bangalore, Kerala, Visakhapatnam - 28 December 2022 Gold rates today, 28 December 2022 : Gold rate today in Hyderabad is at Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian Navy में निकले बंपर पद पर आवेदन करने की अंतिम तिथि आज, इस वेबसाइट से करें अप्लाई</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indian-navy-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 02:51:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indian-navy-/</guid>
      <description>Indian Navy में निकले बंपर पद पर आवेदन करने की अंतिम तिथि आज, इस वेबसाइट से करें अप्लाई Indian Navy Recruitment 2022 Registration Last Date: इंडियन नेवी ने अग्निवीर भर्ती के तहत कुछ समय पहले बंपर पद पर वैकेंसी निकाली थी.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMC CEO asks for salary freeze in 2023 as shares slump</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/amc-ceo-asks-for-salary-freeze-in-2023-as-shares-slump/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 02:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/amc-ceo-asks-for-salary-freeze-in-2023-as-shares-slump/</guid>
      <description>AMC CEO asks for salary freeze in 2023 as shares slump AMC CEO Adam Aron asked the theatre chain operator board to stop his compensation for next year as the company&#39;s shares are falling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A tough 2023 awaits Indian fintech startups as funding cools</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/a-tough-2023-awaits-indian-fintech-startups-as-funding-cools/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 02:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/a-tough-2023-awaits-indian-fintech-startups-as-funding-cools/</guid>
      <description>A tough 2023 awaits Indian fintech startups as funding cools Indian fintechs, largely in the payments and lending space, have attracted roughly $35 billion in funding since 2000, and about $10 billion of it came in 2021: Report</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>​​Sarkari Naukri: इस राज्य में निकली ग्रेजुएट से लेकर पोस्ट ग्रेजुएट युवाओं के लिए वैकेंसी, 1 लाख से ज्यादा मिलेगी सैलरी</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sarkari-naukri-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 07:39:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sarkari-naukri-/</guid>
      <description>​​Sarkari Naukri: इस राज्य में निकली ग्रेजुएट से लेकर पोस्ट ग्रेजुएट युवाओं के लिए वैकेंसी, 1 लाख से ज्यादा मिलेगी सैलरी ​TSPSC Recruitment 2022: ग्रेजुएट से लेकर पोस्ट ग्रेजुएट युवाओं तक के लिए अच्छी खबर है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oilmeals Exports: भारत के खली निर्यात में जबरदस्त इजाफा! अप्रैल-नवंबर के बीच Export हुआ 23.92 लाख टन के पार</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oilmeals-exports-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 06:59:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oilmeals-exports-/</guid>
      <description>Oilmeals Exports: भारत के खली निर्यात में जबरदस्त इजाफा! अप्रैल-नवंबर के बीच Export हुआ 23.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Centre cuts windfall tax on domestic crude oil</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/centre-cuts-windfall-tax-on-domestic-crude-oil/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 07:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/centre-cuts-windfall-tax-on-domestic-crude-oil/</guid>
      <description>Centre cuts windfall tax on domestic crude oil The government has also cut the rate on export of diesel to Rs 5 per litre from Rs 8 per litre</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PF money transfer: What is Annexure K and why do you need it? Know how to download it online</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/pf-money-transfer-what-is-annexure-k-and-why-do-you-need-it-know-how-to-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 04:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/pf-money-transfer-what-is-annexure-k-and-why-do-you-need-it-know-how-to-d/</guid>
      <description>PF money transfer: What is Annexure K and why do you need it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markets climb in early trade</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/markets-climb-in-early-trade/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 04:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/markets-climb-in-early-trade/</guid>
      <description>Markets climb in early trade Mumbai: Benchmark indices climbed in early trade Tuesday amid firm global market trends and as retail inflation dipped below the RBI’s upper tolerance level of 6 per cent for the first time in 11 months in November.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBI Penalty on Banks: रिजर्व बैंक ने इन 13 बैंकों पर लगाया भारी जुर्माना, जानिए क्या रही वजह</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-penalty-on-banks-13-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 04:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-penalty-on-banks-13-/</guid>
      <description>RBI Penalty on Banks: रिजर्व बैंक ने इन 13 बैंकों पर लगाया भारी जुर्माना, जानिए क्या रही वजह RBI Penalty on Banks: रिजर्व बैंक ऑफ इंडिया (RBI Impose Penalty) ने देश के 13 कॉर्पोरेटिव बैंकों पर जुर्माना लगाया है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vehicle Scrappage Policy: अब 15 साल पुरानी गाड़ियां नहीं चला पाएंगे सरकारी कर्मचारी, वित्त मंत्रालय ने जारी किया आदेश</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/vehicle-scrappage-policy-15-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 04:39:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/vehicle-scrappage-policy-15-/</guid>
      <description>Vehicle Scrappage Policy: अब 15 साल पुरानी गाड़ियां नहीं चला पाएंगे सरकारी कर्मचारी, वित्त मंत्रालय ने जारी किया आदेश Vehicle Scrappage Policy: केंद्र की मोदी सरकार ने 15 साल से अधिक पुरानी गाड़ी के लिए एक बड़ा फैसला किया है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Holidays 2023: साल 2023 में 4 महीने बंद रहेंगे स्कूल, इतनी छुट्टियां मिलेंगी कि मन भर जाएगा!</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/school-holidays-2023-2023-4-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 04:37:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/school-holidays-2023-2023-4-/</guid>
      <description>School Holidays 2023: साल 2023 में 4 महीने बंद रहेंगे स्कूल, इतनी छुट्टियां मिलेंगी कि मन भर जाएगा!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>भारत 2030 तक 30 प्रतिशत भूमि और जल संरक्षित करने का लक्ष्य हासिल कर सकता है : सीओपी15 प्रतिनिधि</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-2030-30-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 04:36:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-2030-30-/</guid>
      <description>भारत 2030 तक 30 प्रतिशत भूमि और जल संरक्षित करने का लक्ष्य हासिल कर सकता है : सीओपी15 प्रतिनिधि (शकूर राठेर) मॉन्ट्रियल (कनाडा), 13 दिसंबर (भाषा) कनाडा में सीओपी15 जैव विविधता सम्मेलन में भारत की नुमाइंदगी कर रहे एक वरिष्ठ अधिकारी ने कहा कि भारत का करीब 27 फीसदी क्षेत्र संरक्षित है और वह 2030 तक 30 प्रतिशत भूमि और जल की रक्षा के लक्ष्य को आसानी से हासिल कर सकता है। कनाडा के मॉन्ट्रियल में जैव विविधता पर संयुक्त राष्ट्र की संधि के लिए पक्षकारों के सम्मेलन की 15वीं बैठक (सीओपी15) चल रही है। राष्ट्रीय जैव विविधता प्राधिकरण (एनबीए) के सचिव जे.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maharashtra government to invest Rs 36,000 crore in textile industry; generate 10 lakh jobs</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/maharashtra-government-to-invest-rs-36000-crore-in-textile-industry-gener/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 10:09:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/maharashtra-government-to-invest-rs-36000-crore-in-textile-industry-gener/</guid>
      <description>Maharashtra government to invest Rs 36,000 crore in textile industry; generate 10 lakh jobs Maharashtra government to invest Rs 36,000 crore in textile industry; generate 10 lakh jobs</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBI hikes benchmark lending rate by 35 basis points to tame inflation</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-hikes-benchmark-lending-rate-by-35-basis-points-to-tame-inflation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 05:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-hikes-benchmark-lending-rate-by-35-basis-points-to-tame-inflation/</guid>
      <description>RBI hikes benchmark lending rate by 35 basis points to tame inflation This is the fifth consecutive rate hike after a 40 basis points increase in May and 50 basis points hike each in June, August and September</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overdraft Facility: Check how to borrow money when you have zero funds in your bank account</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/overdraft-facility-check-how-to-borrow-money-when-you-have-zero-funds-in-y/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 06:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/overdraft-facility-check-how-to-borrow-money-when-you-have-zero-funds-in-y/</guid>
      <description>Overdraft Facility: Check how to borrow money when you have zero funds in your bank account Overdraft Facility: Check how to borrow money when you have zero funds in your bank account</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dharmaj Crop Guard IPO Opens Today: Price Band, GMP, Listing; Key Details Investors Should Know</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dharmaj-crop-guard-ipo-opens-today-price-band-gmp-listing-key-details-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 04:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dharmaj-crop-guard-ipo-opens-today-price-band-gmp-listing-key-details-i/</guid>
      <description>Dharmaj Crop Guard IPO Opens Today: Price Band, GMP, Listing; Key Details Investors Should Know Dharmaj Crop Guard IPO will remain open for public subscription for three days between November 28 and 30; the price band has been fixed at Rs 216-237 per share</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rupee gains 16 paise to 81.54 against U.S. dollar</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rupee-gains-16-paise-to-8154-against-us-dollar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 05:53:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rupee-gains-16-paise-to-8154-against-us-dollar/</guid>
      <description>Rupee gains 16 paise to 81.54 against U.S. dollar At the interbank foreign exchange, the domestic unit opened at 81.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviews On Amazon, Flipkart: Govt Guidelines Come Into Effect; What Are These, Compliance?</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/reviews-on-amazon-flipkart-govt-guidelines-come-into-effect-what-are-the/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 05:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/reviews-on-amazon-flipkart-govt-guidelines-come-into-effect-what-are-the/</guid>
      <description>Reviews On Amazon, Flipkart: Govt Guidelines Come Into Effect; What Are These, Compliance?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>​​12वीं में कम नंबर आने पर न हों निराश, इन कोर्स को करके आप भी महीने के कमा सकते हैं लाखों रुपये</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/12-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 04:49:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/12-/</guid>
      <description>​​12वीं में कम नंबर आने पर न हों निराश, इन कोर्स को करके आप भी महीने के कमा सकते हैं लाखों रुपये ​Career After 12th: यदि आपके 12वीं क्लास में ज्यादा अच्छे नंबर नहीं आए हैं तो आपको निराश होने की जरूरत नहीं है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five Star Business Finance Shares List At 5% Discount to IPO Price; Buy, Sell or Hold?</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/five-star-business-finance-shares-list-at-5-discount-to-ipo-price-buy-se/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 04:45:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/five-star-business-finance-shares-list-at-5-discount-to-ipo-price-buy-se/</guid>
      <description>Five Star Business Finance Shares List At 5% Discount to IPO Price; Buy, Sell or Hold?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hinduja Group news: 60 साल तक ईरान रहा हिंदुजा ग्रुप का हेडक्वार्टर, इस्लामी क्रांति के बाद छोड़ना पड़ा था ठिकाना</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hinduja-group-news-60-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 07:53:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hinduja-group-news-60-/</guid>
      <description>Hinduja Group news: 60 साल तक ईरान रहा हिंदुजा ग्रुप का हेडक्वार्टर, इस्लामी क्रांति के बाद छोड़ना पड़ा था ठिकाना दुनिया के सबसे रईस परिवारों में से एक हिंदुजा फैमिली (Hinduja Family) बंटवारे के करीब पहुंच गई है। इस ग्रुप की स्थापना 1914 में परमानंद दीपचंद हिंदुजा ने की थी। 1919 में कंपनी ने ईरान में अपना इंटरनेशनल ऑफिस खोला और अगले 60 साल तक वही ग्रुप का ठिकाना रहा।</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New ETF from ICICI Prudential AMC enables you to benefit from growing financial services; details here</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-etf-from-icici-prudential-amc-enables-you-to-benefit-from-growing-finan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 06:29:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-etf-from-icici-prudential-amc-enables-you-to-benefit-from-growing-finan/</guid>
      <description>New ETF from ICICI Prudential AMC enables you to benefit from growing financial services; details here New ETF from ICICI Prudential AMC enables you to benefit from growing financial services; details here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Air India news: रतन टाटा का बड़ा दांव, एक झटके में दूसरी सबसे बड़ी एयरलाइन बन जाएगी एयर इंडिया</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/air-india-news-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 03:02:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/air-india-news-/</guid>
      <description>Air India news: रतन टाटा का बड़ा दांव, एक झटके में दूसरी सबसे बड़ी एयरलाइन बन जाएगी एयर इंडिया टाटा ग्रुप (Tata Group) एयरलाइन सेक्टर में बड़ा दांव खेलने जा रहा है। टाटा ग्रुप (Tata Group) के पास अभी चार एयरलाइन कंपनियां हैं। इनमें एयर इंडिया (Air India), विस्तारा (Vistara), एयर एशिया (Air Asia) और एयर इंडिया एक्सप्रेस (Air India Express) शामिल हैं। अब इन सभी को एयर इंडिया के अंडर लाने की तैयारी है।</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Buying: घर या फ्लैट खरीदने के लिए इन बातों का रखें विशेष ध्यान, वर्ना हो सकता है बड़ा नुकसान</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/home-buying-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 03:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/home-buying-/</guid>
      <description>Home Buying: घर या फ्लैट खरीदने के लिए इन बातों का रखें विशेष ध्यान, वर्ना हो सकता है बड़ा नुकसान Buy House Real Estate: अगर आप घर खरीदने (Buying Home) के बारे में प्लान बना रहे हैं, तो ये खबर आपके काम की साबित होगी.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical view: Will Nifty be able to hit new highs this week?</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/technical-view-will-nifty-be-able-to-hit-new-highs-this-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 04:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/technical-view-will-nifty-be-able-to-hit-new-highs-this-week/</guid>
      <description>Technical view: Will Nifty be able to hit new highs this week?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India A Fastest-Growing Major Economy, To Be Among Top-3 Economic Powers In 10-15 Years: Nirmala Sitharaman</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-a-fastest-growing-major-economy-to-be-among-top-3-economic-powers-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 06:35:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-a-fastest-growing-major-economy-to-be-among-top-3-economic-powers-in/</guid>
      <description>India A Fastest-Growing Major Economy, To Be Among Top-3 Economic Powers In 10-15 Years: Nirmala Sitharaman The finance minister says global economic outlook remains challenging and the Indian economy is not insulated from the impact of global economic developments</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk Twitter News: एलन मस्‍क को ट्विटर के दिवालिया होने की सता रही चिंता, जानें क्या हैं वजह</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-twitter-news-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 06:32:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-twitter-news-/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk Twitter News: एलन मस्‍क को ट्विटर के दिवालिया होने की सता रही चिंता, जानें क्या हैं वजह Elon Musk&#39;s Twitter Bankruptcy Fear : दुनिया के सबसे अमीर शख्‍स एलन मस्‍क (Elon Musk) सोशल मीडिया कंपनी ट्विटर (Twitter) के जब से मालिक बने है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian Medicines Pharmaceutical pays &lt;span class=&#39;webrupee&#39;&gt;₹&lt;/span&gt;10 cr dividend to Centre, Uttarakhand</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indian-medicines-pharmaceutical-pays-span-classwebrupeespan10-cr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 07:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indian-medicines-pharmaceutical-pays-span-classwebrupeespan10-cr/</guid>
      <description>Indian Medicines Pharmaceutical pays ₹10 cr dividend to Centre, Uttarakhand The company manufactures 656 classical ayurvedic, 332 unani and 71 proprietary ayurvedic medicines for various diseases and supplies to states under National Ayush Mission</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&lt;span class=&#39;webrupee&#39;&gt;₹&lt;/span&gt;10 to &lt;span class=&#39;webrupee&#39;&gt;₹&lt;/span&gt;53: SME stock turns multibagger in 2 years. Rallies over 400%</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/span-classwebrupeespan10-to-span-classwebrupeespan53/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 07:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/span-classwebrupeespan10-to-span-classwebrupeespan53/</guid>
      <description>₹10 to ₹53: SME stock turns multibagger in 2 years. Rallies over 400% Multibagger stock: Before profit-booking trigger in September 2022, this small-cap stock surged from ₹10 to ₹104.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metropolis Healthcare’s non-covid business growth is encouraging</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/metropolis-healthcares-non-covid-business-growth-is-encouraging/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 07:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/metropolis-healthcares-non-covid-business-growth-is-encouraging/</guid>
      <description>Metropolis Healthcare’s non-covid business growth is encouraging Expansion, acquisition of HiTech, growing digital revenue and shift to organized players would support Metropolis’ growth</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bullet train project: Godrej &amp; Boyce refutes allegations of causing delay</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bullet-train-project-godrej-boyce-refutes-allegations-of-causing-delay/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 07:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bullet-train-project-godrej-boyce-refutes-allegations-of-causing-delay/</guid>
      <description>Bullet train project: Godrej &amp;amp; Boyce refutes allegations of causing delay Godrej &amp; Boyce has discarded allegations of causing delay in bullet train project in the Bombay High Court.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian bank stocks&#39; continue to record high as balance sheet strengthens</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indian-bank-stocks-continue-to-record-high-as-balance-sheet-strengthens/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 07:24:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indian-bank-stocks-continue-to-record-high-as-balance-sheet-strengthens/</guid>
      <description>Indian bank stocks&#39; continue to record high as balance sheet strengthens The Nifty public sector bank index has jumped about 50% so far this year and the bank index has risen roughly 17%, handily outperforming the benchmark Nifty 50 index&#39;s approximately 4% gain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FIFA World Cup 2022: Demand for private jets from India to Qatar soars, airlines charging Rs 50 lakh for round-trip</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/fifa-world-cup-2022-demand-for-private-jets-from-india-to-qatar-soars-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 07:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/fifa-world-cup-2022-demand-for-private-jets-from-india-to-qatar-soars-air/</guid>
      <description>FIFA World Cup 2022: Demand for private jets from India to Qatar soars, airlines charging Rs 50 lakh for round-trip According to ANI, India&#39;s HNIs are set for an unprecedented presence at the FIFA event in Qatar this year as the charter planes are being mostly sold out in spite of deals being exorbitant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archean Chemical Industries IPO; Check GMP, Price band, and other key details</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/archean-chemical-industries-ipo-check-gmp-price-band-and-other-key-detai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/archean-chemical-industries-ipo-check-gmp-price-band-and-other-key-detai/</guid>
      <description>Archean Chemical Industries IPO; Check GMP, Price band, and other key details According to the red herring prospectus, the company has fixed the price band in the range of Rs 386 to Rs 407 per share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WATCH: IAF Air Chief Marshal VR Chaudhari takes sortie in Rafale fighter jet during GARUDA 2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/watch-iaf-air-chief-marshal-vr-chaudhari-takes-sortie-in-rafale-fighter-je/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 07:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/watch-iaf-air-chief-marshal-vr-chaudhari-takes-sortie-in-rafale-fighter-je/</guid>
      <description>WATCH: IAF Air Chief Marshal VR Chaudhari takes sortie in Rafale fighter jet during GARUDA 2022 The IAF is participating in Garuda 2022 with Su-30 MKI, Rafale, LCA Tejas and Jaguar fighter aircraft, as well as the Light Combat Helicopter (LCH) and Mi-17 helicopters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abu Dhabi Fintech Startup Raises $20 Million in Series B Funding Round</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/abu-dhabi-fintech-startup-raises-20-million-in-series-b-funding-round/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 07:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/abu-dhabi-fintech-startup-raises-20-million-in-series-b-funding-round/</guid>
      <description>Abu Dhabi Fintech Startup Raises $20 Million in Series B Funding Round Abu Dhabi-based fintech, Pyypl, announced on Nov.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Zuckerberg led Meta begins MASSIVE lay off from today, largest of year to date in tech sector</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mark-zuckerberg-led-meta-begins-massive-lay-off-from-today-largest-of-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 06:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mark-zuckerberg-led-meta-begins-massive-lay-off-from-today-largest-of-year/</guid>
      <description>Mark Zuckerberg led Meta begins MASSIVE lay off from today, largest of year to date in tech sector The company is expected to cut thousands of employees beginning Wednesday, and this will likely be the largest of the year to date in the tech sector, the Wall Street Journal reported, citing people in the know about the matter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monsoon CreditTech raises funds from investors led by HDFC Capital</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/monsoon-credittech-raises-funds-from-investors-led-by-hdfc-capital/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 06:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/monsoon-credittech-raises-funds-from-investors-led-by-hdfc-capital/</guid>
      <description>Monsoon CreditTech raises funds from investors led by HDFC Capital This fundraise also saw the participation of several existing and new investors including DMI Alternative Investment Fund and US-based Top Shelf Equity Partners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk&#39;s net worth dropped below $200 bn as new Twitter boss sells nearly $4 bn worth shares in Tesla</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musks-net-worth-dropped-below-200-bn-as-new-twitter-boss-sells-nearl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 04:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musks-net-worth-dropped-below-200-bn-as-new-twitter-boss-sells-nearl/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s net worth dropped below $200 bn as new Twitter boss sells nearly $4 bn worth shares in Tesla Twitter CEO Elon Musk&#39;s net worth dropped below $200 billion as investors dumped Tesla Inc (TSLA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top cryptocurrency news on November 09: Binance acquires FTX, Cryptos witness blood bath, Germany#39;s financial authority regulates Coinbase, and more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/top-cryptocurrency-news-on-november-09-binance-acquires-ftx-cryptos-witne/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 03:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/top-cryptocurrency-news-on-november-09-binance-acquires-ftx-cryptos-witne/</guid>
      <description>Top cryptocurrency news on November 09: Binance acquires FTX, Cryptos witness blood bath, Germany#39;s financial authority regulates Coinbase, and more A daily round-up of the most interesting articles on cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin, Ethereum and Tether to help jump-start the day</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oil PSUs suffer loss of Rs 2,749 cr in Q2</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oil-psus-suffer-loss-of-rs-2749-cr-in-q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 03:41:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oil-psus-suffer-loss-of-rs-2749-cr-in-q2/</guid>
      <description>Oil PSUs suffer loss of Rs 2,749 cr in Q2 New Delhi, November 8 State-owned oil marketing companies — IOC, BPCL and HPCL — posted a second consecutive quarterly loss totalling Rs 2,748.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rate hikes unlikely to impact asset quality of home loan portfolios: ICRA</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rate-hikes-unlikely-to-impact-asset-quality-of-home-loan-portfolios-icra/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 13:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rate-hikes-unlikely-to-impact-asset-quality-of-home-loan-portfolios-icra/</guid>
      <description>Rate hikes unlikely to impact asset quality of home loan portfolios: ICRA thehindu</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Formula E: Mahindra Racing Announces Frederic Bertrand As New CEO</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/formula-e-mahindra-racing-announces-frederic-bertrand-as-new-ceo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 16:38:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/formula-e-mahindra-racing-announces-frederic-bertrand-as-new-ceo/</guid>
      <description>Formula E: Mahindra Racing Announces Frederic Bertrand As New CEO null</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paytm Q2 consolidated net loss widens to ₹571.5 crore</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/paytm-q2-consolidated-net-loss-widens-to-5715-crore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 16:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/paytm-q2-consolidated-net-loss-widens-to-5715-crore/</guid>
      <description>Paytm Q2 consolidated net loss widens to ₹571.5 crore Contribution profit surges 224% to ₹ 843 crore</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India Plans To Return To Once-A-Month Releases Of Import And Export Data</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-plans-to-return-to-once-a-month-releases-of-import-and-export-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-plans-to-return-to-once-a-month-releases-of-import-and-export-data/</guid>
      <description>India Plans To Return To Once-A-Month Releases Of Import And Export Data Due to wide discrepancies in twice-monthly trade data, India could soon return to a once-a-month government release of data and scrap an early preliminary release of imports and exports, Bloomberg reported on Monday, quoting sources with knowledge of the plans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oil Prices Slide As China Reaffirms Covid Containment Strategy</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oil-prices-slide-as-china-reaffirms-covid-containment-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 07:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oil-prices-slide-as-china-reaffirms-covid-containment-strategy/</guid>
      <description>Oil Prices Slide As China Reaffirms Covid Containment Strategy Crude oil started the week down as the latest updates from China, which included a reiteration of Beijing’s commitment to zero Covid tolerance and weaker-than-expected October exports, added to bearish sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petrol, diesel prices today in Hyderabad, Delhi, Chennai and Mumbai on 07 November 2022, check here</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-diesel-prices-today-in-hyderabad-delhi-chennai-and-mumbai-on-07-n/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 05:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-diesel-prices-today-in-hyderabad-delhi-chennai-and-mumbai-on-07-n/</guid>
      <description>Petrol, diesel prices today in Hyderabad, Delhi, Chennai and Mumbai on 07 November 2022, check here Petrol and Diesel prices today, 07 November 2022: Petrol price in Hyderabad is Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sensex crosses 61,000-mark in early trade</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sensex-crosses-61000-mark-in-early-trade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 04:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sensex-crosses-61000-mark-in-early-trade/</guid>
      <description>Sensex crosses 61,000-mark in early trade Mumbai, November 7Equity benchmark Sensex climbed over 360 points to breach the 61,000-mark in early trade on Monday, led by strong gains in banking, auto and financial stocks amid a firm trend in global markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tirupati Temple richer than Wipro, Nestle, ONGC, IOC, has net worth of over Rs 2.5 lakh crore</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tirupati-temple-richer-than-wipro-nestle-ongc-ioc-has-net-worth-of-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 04:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tirupati-temple-richer-than-wipro-nestle-ongc-ioc-has-net-worth-of-over/</guid>
      <description>Tirupati Temple richer than Wipro, Nestle, ONGC, IOC, has net worth of over Rs 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Baroda Q2 Results Review - Strong Performance; Lower Provisions Drive Earnings: Motilal Oswal</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bank-of-baroda-q2-results-review-strong-performance-lower-provisions-dri/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 04:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bank-of-baroda-q2-results-review-strong-performance-lower-provisions-dri/</guid>
      <description>Bank of Baroda Q2 Results Review - Strong Performance; Lower Provisions Drive Earnings: Motilal Oswal Bank reported a strong performance with healthy NII growth (resulting in margin expansion), lower provisions, driving net earnings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank Of Baroda Jumps Over 11% To Record High After All-Round Q2 Beat</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bank-of-baroda-jumps-over-11-to-record-high-after-all-round-q2-beat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 04:29:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bank-of-baroda-jumps-over-11-to-record-high-after-all-round-q2-beat/</guid>
      <description>Bank Of Baroda Jumps Over 11% To Record High After All-Round Q2 Beat The stock witnessed high trading volume, over 18.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petrol, Diesel Price today, November 6: Check latest fuel rates in your city</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-diesel-price-today-november-6-check-latest-fuel-rates-in-your-cit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 04:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-diesel-price-today-november-6-check-latest-fuel-rates-in-your-cit/</guid>
      <description>Petrol, Diesel Price today, November 6: Check latest fuel rates in your city Petrol costs Rs 96.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assembly Bypoll Results Live: Counting Underway For Seven Seats In Six States</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/assembly-bypoll-results-live-counting-underway-for-seven-seats-in-six-stat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 04:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/assembly-bypoll-results-live-counting-underway-for-seven-seats-in-six-stat/</guid>
      <description>Assembly Bypoll Results Live: Counting Underway For Seven Seats In Six States Catch all the live coverage of the assembly bypoll results here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petrol, diesel prices today in Hyderabad, Delhi, Chennai and Mumbai on 06 November 2022, check here</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-diesel-prices-today-in-hyderabad-delhi-chennai-and-mumbai-on-06-n/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 04:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-diesel-prices-today-in-hyderabad-delhi-chennai-and-mumbai-on-06-n/</guid>
      <description>Petrol, diesel prices today in Hyderabad, Delhi, Chennai and Mumbai on 06 November 2022, check here Petrol and Diesel prices today, 06 November 2022: Petrol price in Hyderabad is Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold rates today in Delhi, Chennai, Kolkata, Mumbai - 06 November 2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-rates-today-in-delhi-chennai-kolkata-mumbai-06-november-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 04:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-rates-today-in-delhi-chennai-kolkata-mumbai-06-november-2022/</guid>
      <description>Gold rates today in Delhi, Chennai, Kolkata, Mumbai - 06 November 2022 Gold rates today, 06 November 2022: Gold rates in Delhi per 10 grams of 22 carats is at Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Centre notifies scheme for funding PPP projects&#39; development</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/centre-notifies-scheme-for-funding-ppp-projects-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 13:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/centre-notifies-scheme-for-funding-ppp-projects-development/</guid>
      <description>Centre notifies scheme for funding PPP projects&#39; development The IIPDF Scheme will aid the development of quality PPP projects by providing necessary funding support to the project sponsoring authorities</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>European Telcos demand from big tech companies to pay for &#39;network cost&#39; following Australia&#39;s example</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/european-telcos-demand-from-big-tech-companies-to-pay-for-network-cost-fo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 13:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/european-telcos-demand-from-big-tech-companies-to-pay-for-network-cost-fo/</guid>
      <description>European Telcos demand from big tech companies to pay for &amp;lsquo;network cost&amp;rsquo; following Australia&amp;rsquo;s example The proposal comes ahead of the 27-country bloc&#39;s consultation on a so-called &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian stock indices largely steady today after the decline</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indian-stock-indices-largely-steady-today-after-the-decline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 13:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indian-stock-indices-largely-steady-today-after-the-decline/</guid>
      <description>Indian stock indices largely steady today after the decline The US Fed raised the key policy rate by 75 basis points to over a decade high at 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SBI posts highest ever quarterly profit at ₹13,265 crore in Q2</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sbi-posts-highest-ever-quarterly-profit-at-13265-crore-in-q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 13:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sbi-posts-highest-ever-quarterly-profit-at-13265-crore-in-q2/</guid>
      <description>SBI posts highest ever quarterly profit at ₹13,265 crore in Q2 Revises loan growth guidance for this fiscal to 14-16% from 10-12%</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Startups Join Mastercard Program to Make Cryptocurrency More Accessible</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/7-startups-join-mastercard-program-to-make-cryptocurrency-more-accessible/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 04:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/7-startups-join-mastercard-program-to-make-cryptocurrency-more-accessible/</guid>
      <description>7 Startups Join Mastercard Program to Make Cryptocurrency More Accessible Payments giant Mastercard has added seven startups to its Start Path program to make cryptocurrencies more accessible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter’s advertisers pull back as layoffs sweep through company</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitters-advertisers-pull-back-as-layoffs-sweep-through-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 03:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitters-advertisers-pull-back-as-layoffs-sweep-through-company/</guid>
      <description>Twitter’s advertisers pull back as layoffs sweep through company The pullback of advertisers from Twitter gathered steam Friday amid growing fear that misinformation and hate speech would be allowed to proliferate on the platform under Elon Musk’s leadership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why CCI&#39;s Decision Against Makemytrip-GoIbibo-Oyo Redefines Platform Markets</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/why-ccis-decision-against-makemytrip-goibibo-oyo-redefines-platform-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 03:53:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/why-ccis-decision-against-makemytrip-goibibo-oyo-redefines-platform-market/</guid>
      <description>Why CCI&amp;rsquo;s Decision Against Makemytrip-GoIbibo-Oyo Redefines Platform Markets The CCI’s market definition holds the key to its analysis and eventual finding of infringement against MakeMyTrip-GoIbibo and Oyo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mutual Fund Show: What&#39;s The Ideal Portfolio For High Risk Investors?</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-mutual-fund-show-whats-the-ideal-portfolio-for-high-risk-investors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 03:52:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-mutual-fund-show-whats-the-ideal-portfolio-for-high-risk-investors/</guid>
      <description>The Mutual Fund Show: What&amp;rsquo;s The Ideal Portfolio For High Risk Investors?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TVS Motor Misses Q2 Profit Estimates On Weak Exports</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tvs-motor-misses-q2-profit-estimates-on-weak-exports/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 03:49:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tvs-motor-misses-q2-profit-estimates-on-weak-exports/</guid>
      <description>TVS Motor Misses Q2 Profit Estimates On Weak Exports TVS reported a lower-than-expected rise in second-quarter profit, hurt by higher expenses and an economic slowdown in a few of its key markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Government Not Considering Minimum Work Threshold Under MGNREGA, Says Ministry</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/government-not-considering-minimum-work-threshold-under-mgnrega-says-minis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 16:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/government-not-considering-minimum-work-threshold-under-mgnrega-says-minis/</guid>
      <description>Government Not Considering Minimum Work Threshold Under MGNREGA, Says Ministry The government has spent over Rs 60,000 crore under the scheme against the budgeted Rs 73,000 crore so far this fiscal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter ‘sued by staff’ as layoffs begin; Sizewell new nuclear plant under review – business live</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-sued-by-staff-as-layoffs-begin-sizewell-new-nuclear-plant-un/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 07:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-sued-by-staff-as-layoffs-begin-sizewell-new-nuclear-plant-un/</guid>
      <description>Twitter ‘sued by staff’ as layoffs begin; Sizewell new nuclear plant under review – business live Rolling coverage of the latest economic and financial newsElon Musk announces Twitter mass layoffs to begin FridayThe Sizewell C nuclear power plant in Suffolk is reportedly under review as the Government looks to cut spending to fill the UK’s fiscal ‘black hole’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most Asian markets rise as China hopes boost Hong Kong</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/most-asian-markets-rise-as-china-hopes-boost-hong-kong/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 07:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/most-asian-markets-rise-as-china-hopes-boost-hong-kong/</guid>
      <description>Most Asian markets rise as China hopes boost Hong Kong Fed boss Jerome Powell&#39;s pushback against expectations of a softer approach to monetary tightening sent shivers through trading floors and ramped up fears of a global recession.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nissan Says Talks With Renault Focused On Better Competing In Electric Cars</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nissan-says-talks-with-renault-focused-on-better-competing-in-electric-cars/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 07:22:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nissan-says-talks-with-renault-focused-on-better-competing-in-electric-cars/</guid>
      <description>Nissan Says Talks With Renault Focused On Better Competing In Electric Cars Nissan&#39;s CEO said the company&#39;s talks with Renault are focused on optimising their investment in electric vehicles and strengthening their competitiveness as equal partners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The G7 Will Set A Fixed Price On Russian Oil</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-g7-will-set-a-fixed-price-on-russian-oil/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 07:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-g7-will-set-a-fixed-price-on-russian-oil/</guid>
      <description>The G7 Will Set A Fixed Price On Russian Oil Members of the G7 have agreed to set a fixed price for Russian oil exports as a cap rather than a price set as a discount to a benchmark, Reuters has reported, citing an unnamed source familiar with the discussions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyderabad, Delhi, Bengaluru Top Choices For NRIs Buying Homes: Survey</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hyderabad-delhi-bengaluru-top-choices-for-nris-buying-homes-survey/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 07:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hyderabad-delhi-bengaluru-top-choices-for-nris-buying-homes-survey/</guid>
      <description>Hyderabad, Delhi, Bengaluru Top Choices For NRIs Buying Homes: Survey The top picks for most NRIs in the survey for the first six months (H1) of 2021 were Bengaluru, Pune and Chennai.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Servotech Power Systems bags Rs 46 crore order from BPCL</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/servotech-power-systems-bags-rs-46-crore-order-from-bpcl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 07:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/servotech-power-systems-bags-rs-46-crore-order-from-bpcl/</guid>
      <description>Servotech Power Systems bags Rs 46 crore order from BPCL The project to supply and install 800 units of DC fast EV Chargers has already been initiated from Delhi and is expected to be completed by March 31, 2023, a company statement said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top cryptocurrency news on November 04: ApeCoin DAO approves $4.4M to identify bugs in staking mechanism, JP Morgan forays into DeFi, and more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/top-cryptocurrency-news-on-november-04-apecoin-dao-approves-44m-to-ident/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 04:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/top-cryptocurrency-news-on-november-04-apecoin-dao-approves-44m-to-ident/</guid>
      <description>Top cryptocurrency news on November 04: ApeCoin DAO approves $4.4M to identify bugs in staking mechanism, JP Morgan forays into DeFi, and more A daily round-up of the most interesting articles on cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin, Ethereum and Tether to help jump-start the day</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BYJU#39;S ropes in Lionel Messi as global brand ambassador for social initiative EFA</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/byju39s-ropes-in-lionel-messi-as-global-brand-ambassador-for-social-initi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 04:29:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/byju39s-ropes-in-lionel-messi-as-global-brand-ambassador-for-social-initi/</guid>
      <description>BYJU#39;S ropes in Lionel Messi as global brand ambassador for social initiative EFA Lionel Messi, who plays for Paris Saint-Germain and captains the Argentinian football team, has signed an agreement with BYJU#39;S to promote the cause of equitable education, BYJU#39;S said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold rates today in Delhi, Chennai, Kolkata, Mumbai - 04 November 2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-rates-today-in-delhi-chennai-kolkata-mumbai-04-november-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 04:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-rates-today-in-delhi-chennai-kolkata-mumbai-04-november-2022/</guid>
      <description>Gold rates today in Delhi, Chennai, Kolkata, Mumbai - 04 November 2022 Gold rates today, 04 November 2022: Gold rates in Delhi per 10 grams of 22 carats is at Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bharat Electronics joins hands with Motorola in broadband, push-to-talk service field</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bharat-electronics-joins-hands-with-motorola-in-broadband-push-to-talk-ser/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 04:24:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bharat-electronics-joins-hands-with-motorola-in-broadband-push-to-talk-ser/</guid>
      <description>Bharat Electronics joins hands with Motorola in broadband, push-to-talk service field The MoU aims at leveraging the complementary strengths and capabilities of BEL and Motorola, the Bengaluru-headquartered company said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon is offering six-months Spotify subscription for free; Here&#39;s what you need to do</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/amazon-is-offering-six-months-spotify-subscription-for-free-heres-what-yo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/amazon-is-offering-six-months-spotify-subscription-for-free-heres-what-yo/</guid>
      <description>Amazon is offering six-months Spotify subscription for free; Here&amp;rsquo;s what you need to do However, there are some terms and conditions in case you are planning to become the eligible contender for a win.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine Nuclear Plant Running On Backup Generators After Russian Shelling</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ukraine-nuclear-plant-running-on-backup-generators-after-russian-shelling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ukraine-nuclear-plant-running-on-backup-generators-after-russian-shelling/</guid>
      <description>Ukraine Nuclear Plant Running On Backup Generators After Russian Shelling Russian shelling damaged on Wednesday the last two operational power lines at the Zaporizhzhya nuclear power plant in Ukraine, Europe’s largest, which is now running on backup diesel generators, Ukrainian state nuclear power company Energoatom said on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Rs 14 lakh in 5 years with THIS Senior Citizen Post office scheme; Check return calculator, interest rate &amp; more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/make-rs-14-lakh-in-5-years-with-this-senior-citizen-post-office-scheme-che/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/make-rs-14-lakh-in-5-years-with-this-senior-citizen-post-office-scheme-che/</guid>
      <description>Make Rs 14 lakh in 5 years with THIS Senior Citizen Post office scheme; Check return calculator, interest rate &amp;amp; more Continue reading to find out the details of the scheme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medanta Hospital Operator Global Health’s IPO - Reputed Brand In Hospitals Space: ICICI Direct</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/medanta-hospital-operator-global-healths-ipo-reputed-brand-in-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 06:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/medanta-hospital-operator-global-healths-ipo-reputed-brand-in-hospital/</guid>
      <description>Medanta Hospital Operator Global Health’s IPO - Reputed Brand In Hospitals Space: ICICI Direct It provides healthcare services in over 30 medical specialties and engage over 1,300 doctors spanning an area of 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bikaji Foods IPO - Large Play In Ethnic Snacks Industry: ICICI Direct</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bikaji-foods-ipo-large-play-in-ethnic-snacks-industry-icici-direct/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 06:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bikaji-foods-ipo-large-play-in-ethnic-snacks-industry-icici-direct/</guid>
      <description>Bikaji Foods IPO - Large Play In Ethnic Snacks Industry: ICICI Direct Bikaji Foods is expanding across geographies and trying to emerge as a dominant pan-India player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bikaji Foods IPO - Leading Snacks Player With Pan India Presence: Reliance Securities</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bikaji-foods-ipo-leading-snacks-player-with-pan-india-presence-reliance-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 05:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bikaji-foods-ipo-leading-snacks-player-with-pan-india-presence-reliance-/</guid>
      <description>Bikaji Foods IPO - Leading Snacks Player With Pan India Presence: Reliance Securities The company is coming out with an IPO of Rs 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kajaria Ceramics Q2 Results Review - Margins To Improve From H2: Yes Securities</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/kajaria-ceramics-q2-results-review-margins-to-improve-from-h2-yes-securi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 05:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/kajaria-ceramics-q2-results-review-margins-to-improve-from-h2-yes-securi/</guid>
      <description>Kajaria Ceramics Q2 Results Review - Margins To Improve From H2: Yes Securities On margins, management is confident that worst seems to behind as gas cost have started to tapper-down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dalmia Bharat Q2 Results Review - Healthy Volumes Coupled With Cost Discipline: ICICI Securities</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dalmia-bharat-q2-results-review-healthy-volumes-coupled-with-cost-discipl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 05:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dalmia-bharat-q2-results-review-healthy-volumes-coupled-with-cost-discipl/</guid>
      <description>Dalmia Bharat Q2 Results Review - Healthy Volumes Coupled With Cost Discipline: ICICI Securities Volumes grew at a strong rate of 14% YoY (on a low base, ramping-up its newly commissioned plants), implying a 3-year CAGR of 9%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adani Ports Q2 Results Review - Bulk Expected To Grow Ahead Of Container Volumes: ICICI Direct</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/adani-ports-q2-results-review-bulk-expected-to-grow-ahead-of-container-vo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 05:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/adani-ports-q2-results-review-bulk-expected-to-grow-ahead-of-container-vo/</guid>
      <description>Adani Ports Q2 Results Review - Bulk Expected To Grow Ahead Of Container Volumes: ICICI Direct For H2, volume boost expected from five new services at Mundra and Hazira; four bulk contract wins at Gangavaram and Dhamra.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fusion MicroFinance IPO Subscription Status: Day 2 Live Updates</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/fusion-microfinance-ipo-subscription-status-day-2-live-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 05:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/fusion-microfinance-ipo-subscription-status-day-2-live-updates/</guid>
      <description>Fusion MicroFinance IPO Subscription Status: Day 2 Live Updates The IPO was subscribed 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bikaji Foods IPO Subscription Status: Day 1 Live Updates</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bikaji-foods-ipo-subscription-status-day-1-live-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 05:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bikaji-foods-ipo-subscription-status-day-1-live-updates/</guid>
      <description>Bikaji Foods IPO Subscription Status: Day 1 Live Updates The IPO was subscribed 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medanta Operator Global Health IPO Subscription Status: Day 1 Live Updates</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/medanta-operator-global-health-ipo-subscription-status-day-1-live-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 05:50:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/medanta-operator-global-health-ipo-subscription-status-day-1-live-updates/</guid>
      <description>Medanta Operator Global Health IPO Subscription Status: Day 1 Live Updates The IPO was subscribed 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Share Market Live: Sensex, Nifty Set To Fall; Adani Transmission, P&amp;G Hygiene, LIC, Dalmia Bharat In Focus</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/share-market-live-sensex-nifty-set-to-fall-adani-transmission-pg-hygie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 03:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/share-market-live-sensex-nifty-set-to-fall-adani-transmission-pg-hygie/</guid>
      <description>Share Market Live: Sensex, Nifty Set To Fall; Adani Transmission, P&amp;amp;G Hygiene, LIC, Dalmia Bharat In Focus Follow the latest market updates here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Fed Reserve hikes interest rates by 75 basis points, Indian markets and rupee to be hit</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/us-fed-reserve-hikes-interest-rates-by-75-basis-points-indian-markets-and-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 02:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/us-fed-reserve-hikes-interest-rates-by-75-basis-points-indian-markets-and-/</guid>
      <description>US Fed Reserve hikes interest rates by 75 basis points, Indian markets and rupee to be hit US Fed`s rate hike actions have a direct bearing on Indian markets and the rupee, as higher interest rates in the US take the sheen off Indian equities, weaning away foreign investors, say market analysts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Big SUV Launches Expected At 2023 Auto Expo</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/7-big-suv-launches-expected-at-2023-auto-expo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 02:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/7-big-suv-launches-expected-at-2023-auto-expo/</guid>
      <description>7 Big SUV Launches Expected At 2023 Auto Expo GaadiWaadi - The upcoming Delhi Auto Expo 2023 will start on 13th January 2023 and will witness the launch of many new cars and two-wheelers With all the carmakers gearing up to unveil their new offerings at the upcoming Auto Expo 2023, a number of reports are surfacing online giving us hints of what to expect in […] The post 7 Big SUV Launches Expected At 2023 Auto Expo appeared first on Gaadiwaadi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moneygram Enables Customers to Buy and Sell Cryptocurrency via Its Money Transfer App</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/moneygram-enables-customers-to-buy-and-sell-cryptocurrency-via-its-money-tr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 02:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/moneygram-enables-customers-to-buy-and-sell-cryptocurrency-via-its-money-tr/</guid>
      <description>Moneygram Enables Customers to Buy and Sell Cryptocurrency via Its Money Transfer App Moneygram has launched a new crypto service to allow customers to buy, sell, and store cryptocurrencies using its mobile money transfer app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New ITR form seeks more data, need to relearn e-filing: Experts</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-itr-form-seeks-more-data-need-to-relearn-e-filing-experts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 02:22:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-itr-form-seeks-more-data-need-to-relearn-e-filing-experts/</guid>
      <description>New ITR form seeks more data, need to relearn e-filing: Experts toi</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India aims to end urea imports from 2025; pegs FY23 fertilisers subsidy at $27.2 bn</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-aims-to-end-urea-imports-from-2025-pegs-fy23-fertilisers-subsidy-at-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 16:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-aims-to-end-urea-imports-from-2025-pegs-fy23-fertilisers-subsidy-at-/</guid>
      <description>India aims to end urea imports from 2025; pegs FY23 fertilisers subsidy at $27.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mining giant Glencore flew cash bribes to Africa via private jet, UK court hears</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mining-giant-glencore-flew-cash-bribes-to-africa-via-private-jet-uk-court-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 16:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mining-giant-glencore-flew-cash-bribes-to-africa-via-private-jet-uk-court-/</guid>
      <description>Mining giant Glencore flew cash bribes to Africa via private jet, UK court hears Corruption at FTSE 100 firm described as endemic at sentence hearingGlencore flew cash bribes to officials in Africa via private jet amid “endemic” corruption within the mining company, a London court has heard, in sentencing of the first ever UK corporate conviction on charges of bribing another person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fusion Micro Finance IPO - Investment Rationale, Strengths, Key Strategies, Risks, Financials: Anand Rathi</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/fusion-micro-finance-ipo-investment-rationale-strengths-key-strategies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 07:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/fusion-micro-finance-ipo-investment-rationale-strengths-key-strategies/</guid>
      <description>Fusion Micro Finance IPO - Investment Rationale, Strengths, Key Strategies, Risks, Financials: Anand Rathi Fusion Micro Finance provides financial services to unserved and underserved women in rural and peri-rural areas across India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inflation in UK shops hits record high as food prices soar – business live</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/inflation-in-uk-shops-hits-record-high-as-food-prices-soar-business-liv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 07:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/inflation-in-uk-shops-hits-record-high-as-food-prices-soar-business-liv/</guid>
      <description>Inflation in UK shops hits record high as food prices soar – business live Rolling coverage of the latest economic and financial news, as food prices rise at fastest rate since at least 2005 Government tests energy blackout emergency plans as supply fears growSupermarkets need to offer good value this Christmas to win business from cash-strapped customers, adds Mike Watkins, Head of Retailer and Business Insight at NielsenIQ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBI launches Digital currency pilot project: What is Digital Rupee how different it is from other cryptocurrency</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-launches-digital-currency-pilot-project-what-is-digital-rupee-how-diff/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 03:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-launches-digital-currency-pilot-project-what-is-digital-rupee-how-diff/</guid>
      <description>RBI launches Digital currency pilot project: What is Digital Rupee how different it is from other cryptocurrency RBI has said that the first pilot in Digital Rupee - Retail segment (e₹-R) is planned for launch within a month in select locations in closed user groups comprising customers and merchants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia’s October Oil Production Millions Of Bpd Below Quota: Novak</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/russias-october-oil-production-millions-of-bpd-below-quota-novak/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/russias-october-oil-production-millions-of-bpd-below-quota-novak/</guid>
      <description>Russia’s October Oil Production Millions Of Bpd Below Quota: Novak Russia’s oil production, excluding condensate, for October came in well below its production quota for the month, at just 9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windfall Tax On Crude Cut, Levy On Diesel Export, ATF Hiked</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/windfall-tax-on-crude-cut-levy-on-diesel-export-atf-hiked/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 17:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/windfall-tax-on-crude-cut-levy-on-diesel-export-atf-hiked/</guid>
      <description>Windfall Tax On Crude Cut, Levy On Diesel Export, ATF Hiked New Delhi, Nov 1 (PTI) The government on Tuesday cut the windfall tax on domestically produced crude oil while increasing the rate on export of diesel and jet fuel (ATF) in line with rise in international oil prices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia And Iran To Sign Free Trade Agreement With The Eurasian Economic Union</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/russia-and-iran-to-sign-free-trade-agreement-with-the-eurasian-economic-uni/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/russia-and-iran-to-sign-free-trade-agreement-with-the-eurasian-economic-uni/</guid>
      <description>Russia And Iran To Sign Free Trade Agreement With The Eurasian Economic Union Russia and Iran have agreed to sign a free trade agreement with the Eurasian Economic Union, Russian Deputy Prime Minister Alexander Novak said on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Karnataka ban: Uber may restrict auto services to certain parts of Bengaluru</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/karnataka-ban-uber-may-restrict-auto-services-to-certain-parts-of-bengalur/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 17:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/karnataka-ban-uber-may-restrict-auto-services-to-certain-parts-of-bengalur/</guid>
      <description>Karnataka ban: Uber may restrict auto services to certain parts of Bengaluru The company said that the current fixed metered fare does not adequately compensate drivers for the additional distance traveled and time spent in picking up a passenger from their doorstep</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ICICI, Indian Bank Hike Benchmark Lending Rates</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/icici-indian-bank-hike-benchmark-lending-rates/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 17:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/icici-indian-bank-hike-benchmark-lending-rates/</guid>
      <description>ICICI, Indian Bank Hike Benchmark Lending Rates ICICI Bank increased the Marginal Cost of Funds based Lending Rates across tenure by 20 basis points effective Nov.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp Banned 26.85 Lakh Accounts In India In September</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-banned-2685-lakh-accounts-in-india-in-september/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 17:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-banned-2685-lakh-accounts-in-india-in-september/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp Banned 26.85 Lakh Accounts In India In September According to the latest WhatsApp report, the platform received 666 grievances in September but took action only against 23.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two-Wheeler Sales October 2022: Royal Enfield Sales Grow 86 Per Cent</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/two-wheeler-sales-october-2022-royal-enfield-sales-grow-86-per-cent/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:37:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/two-wheeler-sales-october-2022-royal-enfield-sales-grow-86-per-cent/</guid>
      <description>Two-Wheeler Sales October 2022: Royal Enfield Sales Grow 86 Per Cent Driven by strong festive season demand, Royal Enfield has reported sales of over 80,000 motorcycles in October 2022, with domestic market sales accounting for over 76,000 units.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiring in IT sector falls by 18% in October compared to last year: Naukri report</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hiring-in-it-sector-falls-by-18-in-october-compared-to-last-year-naukri-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hiring-in-it-sector-falls-by-18-in-october-compared-to-last-year-naukri-r/</guid>
      <description>Hiring in IT sector falls by 18% in October compared to last year: Naukri report JobsApart from IT, other sectors that recorded a notable decline in hiring sentiments included telecom and healthcare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vetsa Ramakrishna Gupta takes charge as BPCL&#39;s interim chief</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/vetsa-ramakrishna-gupta-takes-charge-as-bpcls-interim-chief/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:21:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/vetsa-ramakrishna-gupta-takes-charge-as-bpcls-interim-chief/</guid>
      <description>Vetsa Ramakrishna Gupta takes charge as BPCL&amp;rsquo;s interim chief Vetsa Ramakrishna Gupta on Tuesday assumed additional charge as chairman and managing director of Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd (BPCL) -- the second &#39;Maharatna&#39; oil PSU to get an interim head in the absence of a regular appointment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. And UAE Sign A $100 Billion Clean Energy Pact</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-us-and-uae-sign-a-100-billion-clean-energy-pact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:19:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-us-and-uae-sign-a-100-billion-clean-energy-pact/</guid>
      <description>The U.S. And UAE Sign A $100 Billion Clean Energy Pact The United States and the United Arab Emirates (UEA) signed on Tuesday a partnership expected to attract $100 billion in investment in clean energy projects worldwide, the White House said today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two-Wheeler Sales October 2022: Okinawa Achieves New Monthly Record With 17,531 Retail Sales</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/two-wheeler-sales-october-2022-okinawa-achieves-new-monthly-record-with-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/two-wheeler-sales-october-2022-okinawa-achieves-new-monthly-record-with-17/</guid>
      <description>Two-Wheeler Sales October 2022: Okinawa Achieves New Monthly Record With 17,531 Retail Sales Okinawa&#39;s volumes nearly doubled in October with 17,531 units sold, when compared to September this year when the company sold 8,494 units (as per Vahan data).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insurtech startup Cover Genius raises $70 million in Series D funding</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/insurtech-startup-cover-genius-raises-70-million-in-series-d-funding/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/insurtech-startup-cover-genius-raises-70-million-in-series-d-funding/</guid>
      <description>Insurtech startup Cover Genius raises $70 million in Series D funding The startup says the funding would assist in the business growth of its global insurance distribution platform, XCover</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two-Wheeler Sales October 2022: TVS Sales Grow By 2 Per Cent</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/two-wheeler-sales-october-2022-tvs-sales-grow-by-2-per-cent/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/two-wheeler-sales-october-2022-tvs-sales-grow-by-2-per-cent/</guid>
      <description>Two-Wheeler Sales October 2022: TVS Sales Grow By 2 Per Cent TVS Motor Company’s domestic market sales grew by 7 per cent in October 2022, powered by motorcycle and scooter sales, as well as EV sales from the TVS iQube.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DCX Systems IPO: Check today&#39;s GMP, listing and other details</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dcx-systems-ipo-check-todays-gmp-listing-and-other-details/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 06:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dcx-systems-ipo-check-todays-gmp-listing-and-other-details/</guid>
      <description>DCX Systems IPO: Check today&amp;rsquo;s GMP, listing and other details The issue, with a price band of Rs 197 to Rs 207 per share, will likely list on BSE and NSE on November 11.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastercard Study: African Fintech Sector Had One of the Highest Year-on-Year Growth Rates in Funding in 2021</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mastercard-study-african-fintech-sector-had-one-of-the-highest-year-on-yea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 06:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mastercard-study-african-fintech-sector-had-one-of-the-highest-year-on-yea/</guid>
      <description>Mastercard Study: African Fintech Sector Had One of the Highest Year-on-Year Growth Rates in Funding in 2021 In 2021, African fintech startups accounted for 61% of the $2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saietta VNA Ramps Up Its eDrive ‘Make In India’ Strategy; To Set Up New Plant In Delhi</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/saietta-vna-ramps-up-its-edrive-make-in-india-strategy-to-set-up-new/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 06:29:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/saietta-vna-ramps-up-its-edrive-make-in-india-strategy-to-set-up-new/</guid>
      <description>Saietta VNA Ramps Up Its eDrive ‘Make In India’ Strategy; To Set Up New Plant In Delhi Saietta VNA will be setting up a new manufacturing facility in Delhi to begin volume production of a range of radial- and axial-flux electric motors for e-two-wheeler and e-three-wheeler applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Auto Sales October 2022: MG Motor India Sells 4367 Units; Posts Month-On-Month Growth Of 14.67%</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/auto-sales-october-2022-mg-motor-india-sells-4367-units-posts-month-on-mo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 06:27:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/auto-sales-october-2022-mg-motor-india-sells-4367-units-posts-month-on-mo/</guid>
      <description>Auto Sales October 2022: MG Motor India Sells 4367 Units; Posts Month-On-Month Growth Of 14.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk ropes in Indian-origin tech executive amid changes in Twitter</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-ropes-in-indian-origin-tech-executive-amid-changes-in-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 06:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-ropes-in-indian-origin-tech-executive-amid-changes-in-twitter/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk ropes in Indian-origin tech executive amid changes in Twitter Sriram Krishnan, a general partner at Silicon Valley venture capital firm Andreessen Horowitz (a16z), tweeted that he is helping Elon Musk revamp Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stella Moto Enters Electric Two-Wheeler Space In India</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/stella-moto-enters-electric-two-wheeler-space-in-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 06:14:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/stella-moto-enters-electric-two-wheeler-space-in-india/</guid>
      <description>Stella Moto Enters Electric Two-Wheeler Space In India Stella Moto, a new electric two-wheeler company, has announced its entry into the Indian market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Former Tata Steel MD Jamshed J Irani dead</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/former-tata-steel-md-jamshed-j-irani-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 06:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/former-tata-steel-md-jamshed-j-irani-dead/</guid>
      <description>Former Tata Steel MD Jamshed J Irani dead Irani, 83, retired from the board of Tata Steel back in June 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk dissolves Twitter board after takeover, named sole director</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-dissolves-twitter-board-after-takeover-named-sole-director/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 02:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-dissolves-twitter-board-after-takeover-named-sole-director/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk dissolves Twitter board after takeover, named sole director Out of the many changes that Musk made to the social media platform, the dissolution of the board of directors is a major step as Twitter`s board members which included Bret Taylor, Parag Agrawal, Omid Kordestani, David Rosenblatt, Martha Lane Fox, Patrick Pichette, Egon Durban, Fei-Fei Li, and Mimi Alemayehou will now no longer serve on the board, according to the company`s statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huge relief for LPG customers! OMCs announce huge cut in LPG cylinder price --Check how much you need to pay in your city</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/huge-relief-for-lpg-customers-omcs-announce-huge-cut-in-lpg-cylinder-price/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/huge-relief-for-lpg-customers-omcs-announce-huge-cut-in-lpg-cylinder-price/</guid>
      <description>Huge relief for LPG customers! OMCs announce huge cut in LPG cylinder price &amp;ndash;Check how much you need to pay in your city Effective from 1 November 2022, the rates of of 19-kg commercial LPG cylinder has been slashed by Rs 115.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use asset sale to trim debt for best stimulus: CEA</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/use-asset-sale-to-trim-debt-for-best-stimulus-cea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 01:43:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/use-asset-sale-to-trim-debt-for-best-stimulus-cea/</guid>
      <description>Use asset sale to trim debt for best stimulus: CEA toi</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBI launches first pilot project for digital rupee</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-launches-first-pilot-project-for-digital-rupee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 01:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-launches-first-pilot-project-for-digital-rupee/</guid>
      <description>RBI launches first pilot project for digital rupee toi</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sensex at 10-month high, recovers 9k points in 4 months</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sensex-at-10-month-high-recovers-9k-points-in-4-months/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 01:24:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sensex-at-10-month-high-recovers-9k-points-in-4-months/</guid>
      <description>Sensex at 10-month high, recovers 9k points in 4 months toi</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>‘India to beat Germany as 4th largest economy by FY26’</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-to-beat-germany-as-4th-largest-economy-by-fy26/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 01:14:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-to-beat-germany-as-4th-largest-economy-by-fy26/</guid>
      <description>‘India to beat Germany as 4th largest economy by FY26’ toi</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBI DG Patra says banks to soon submit only two quarterly BSR reports</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-dg-patra-says-banks-to-soon-submit-only-two-quarterly-bsr-reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-dg-patra-says-banks-to-soon-submit-only-two-quarterly-bsr-reports/</guid>
      <description>RBI DG Patra says banks to soon submit only two quarterly BSR reports This is to reduce the reporting burden on banks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volkswagen To Turn R Performance Into Electric-Only Sub-Brand By 2030: Report</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/volkswagen-to-turn-r-performance-into-electric-only-sub-brand-by-2030-repo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/volkswagen-to-turn-r-performance-into-electric-only-sub-brand-by-2030-repo/</guid>
      <description>Volkswagen To Turn R Performance Into Electric-Only Sub-Brand By 2030: Report There are reportedly several electric R models at different planning stages but a timeline for the launch of these models is yet to be revealed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Heartbreaking&#39;: Byju CEO Raveendran announces 2,500 job cuts to avoid role duplication</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/heartbreaking-byju-ceo-raveendran-announces-2500-job-cuts-to-avoid-role/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/heartbreaking-byju-ceo-raveendran-announces-2500-job-cuts-to-avoid-role/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;Heartbreaking&amp;rsquo;: Byju CEO Raveendran announces 2,500 job cuts to avoid role duplication Raveendran said Byju&#39;s had scaled up quickly and massively across the world in the last four years, including through acquisitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OPEC Raises Long-Term Oil Demand View, Calls For Investment</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/opec-raises-long-term-oil-demand-view-calls-for-investment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/opec-raises-long-term-oil-demand-view-calls-for-investment/</guid>
      <description>OPEC Raises Long-Term Oil Demand View, Calls For Investment The view from the Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries, in its 2022 World Oil Outlook, contrasts with that of other forecasters which see oil demand reaching a plateau before 2030 due to the rise of renewable energy and electric cars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hero Lectro Launches H3 And H5 e-Cycles, Prices Start At Rs. 27,499</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hero-lectro-launches-h3-and-h5-e-cycles-prices-start-at-rs-27499/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hero-lectro-launches-h3-and-h5-e-cycles-prices-start-at-rs-27499/</guid>
      <description>Hero Lectro Launches H3 And H5 e-Cycles, Prices Start At Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oil Falls On China COVID Curbs And Weak Factory Data</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oil-falls-on-china-covid-curbs-and-weak-factory-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oil-falls-on-china-covid-curbs-and-weak-factory-data/</guid>
      <description>Oil Falls On China COVID Curbs And Weak Factory Data Oil prices fell on Monday after weaker than expected factory activity data out of China and on concerns that the country&#39;s widening COVID-19 curbs will curtail demand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Patterns Q2 standalone net leaps 63% to ₹21 cr.</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/data-patterns-q2-standalone-net-leaps-63-to-21-cr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/data-patterns-q2-standalone-net-leaps-63-to-21-cr/</guid>
      <description>Data Patterns Q2 standalone net leaps 63% to ₹21 cr. thehindu</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PM Narendra Modi flags off Asarva-Udaipur City Express train services in Gujarat</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/pm-narendra-modi-flags-off-asarva-udaipur-city-express-train-services-in-gu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/pm-narendra-modi-flags-off-asarva-udaipur-city-express-train-services-in-gu/</guid>
      <description>PM Narendra Modi flags off Asarva-Udaipur City Express train services in Gujarat PM Narendra Modi flags off Asarva-Udaipur City Express train services in Gujarat; Check full schedule of the new train HERE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kotak Mutual Funds CIO Harsha Upadhyaya#39;s top stock sectoral picks</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/kotak-mutual-funds-cio-harsha-upadhyaya39s-top-stock-sectoral-picks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 09:29:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/kotak-mutual-funds-cio-harsha-upadhyaya39s-top-stock-sectoral-picks/</guid>
      <description>Kotak Mutual Funds CIO Harsha Upadhyaya#39;s top stock sectoral picks He is overweight on banking, auto, and the industrial segment, and underweight on IT, which he feels will decline as go into 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dove, Tresemme dry shampoos cause cancer; Should Indian consumers worry? Check what Unilever says</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dove-tresemme-dry-shampoos-cause-cancer-should-indian-consumers-worry-ch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 06:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dove-tresemme-dry-shampoos-cause-cancer-should-indian-consumers-worry-ch/</guid>
      <description>Dove, Tresemme dry shampoos cause cancer; Should Indian consumers worry? Check what Unilever says Unilever Dry Shampoo Recall: According to reports, the products were recalled in US and Canada and were produced before October 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Business Stalwarts React To Elon Musk&#39;s Twitter Takeover</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/global-business-stalwarts-react-to-elon-musks-twitter-takeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 06:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/global-business-stalwarts-react-to-elon-musks-twitter-takeover/</guid>
      <description>Global Business Stalwarts React To Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s Twitter Takeover According to the Wall Street Journal, about a dozen brands have offered to pause advertising on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collapsed Morbi Bridge Reopened Five Days Ago Without &#39;Fitness&#39; Certificate</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/collapsed-morbi-bridge-reopened-five-days-ago-without-fitness-certificate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 06:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/collapsed-morbi-bridge-reopened-five-days-ago-without-fitness-certificate/</guid>
      <description>Collapsed Morbi Bridge Reopened Five Days Ago Without &amp;lsquo;Fitness&amp;rsquo; Certificate The suspension bridge which collapsed killing at least 132 people was reopened for the public just five days back after seven months of repair work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DCX Systems IPO Subscription: Day 1 Live Updates</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dcx-systems-ipo-subscription-day-1-live-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 05:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dcx-systems-ipo-subscription-day-1-live-updates/</guid>
      <description>DCX Systems IPO Subscription: Day 1 Live Updates Follow the latest subscription updates from day 1 of DCX Systems IPO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank Holidays in November 2022: Banks in Telangana to be closed for 7 days</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bank-holidays-in-november-2022-banks-in-telangana-to-be-closed-for-7-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 05:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bank-holidays-in-november-2022-banks-in-telangana-to-be-closed-for-7-days/</guid>
      <description>Bank Holidays in November 2022: Banks in Telangana to be closed for 7 days In November 2022, all the banks across Telangana will remain closed for seven days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top cryptocurrency news on October 31: Now trade NFTs by tweeting, Binance invests $500 million in Twitter and more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/top-cryptocurrency-news-on-october-31-now-trade-nfts-by-tweeting-binance-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 05:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/top-cryptocurrency-news-on-october-31-now-trade-nfts-by-tweeting-binance-/</guid>
      <description>Top cryptocurrency news on October 31: Now trade NFTs by tweeting, Binance invests $500 million in Twitter and more A daily round-up of the most interesting articles on cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin, Ethereum and Tether to help jump-start the day</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petrol, diesel prices today in Hyderabad, Delhi, Chennai and Mumbai on 31 October 2022, check here</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-diesel-prices-today-in-hyderabad-delhi-chennai-and-mumbai-on-31-o/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 05:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-diesel-prices-today-in-hyderabad-delhi-chennai-and-mumbai-on-31-o/</guid>
      <description>Petrol, diesel prices today in Hyderabad, Delhi, Chennai and Mumbai on 31 October 2022, check here Petrol and Diesel prices today, 31 October 2022: Petrol price in Hyderabad is Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nitin Gadkari says Nagpur to Pune journey will be possible in eight hours now</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nitin-gadkari-says-nagpur-to-pune-journey-will-be-possible-in-eight-hours-n/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 05:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nitin-gadkari-says-nagpur-to-pune-journey-will-be-possible-in-eight-hours-n/</guid>
      <description>Nitin Gadkari says Nagpur to Pune journey will be possible in eight hours now In a series of tweets, Nitin Gadkari -- the minister for road, transport and highways -- said Samridhi Mahamarg road will be undertaken for construction with a completely new alignment by NHAI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPI free, but banks fix limits as norms clash</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/upi-free-but-banks-fix-limits-as-norms-clash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 01:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/upi-free-but-banks-fix-limits-as-norms-clash/</guid>
      <description>UPI free, but banks fix limits as norms clash toi</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shocker! A delivery person ate food of customer &amp; texts &#39;This food is very tasty. I ate it; Netizen reacts</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/shocker-a-delivery-person-ate-food-of-customer-texts-this-food-is-very-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/shocker-a-delivery-person-ate-food-of-customer-texts-this-food-is-very-/</guid>
      <description>Shocker! A delivery person ate food of customer &amp;amp; texts &amp;lsquo;This food is very tasty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UN-brokered Black Sea Grain Deal: Why Russia pulls back from deal and how it will impact Global food crisis - Explained</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/un-brokered-black-sea-grain-deal-why-russia-pulls-back-from-deal-and-how-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/un-brokered-black-sea-grain-deal-why-russia-pulls-back-from-deal-and-how-i/</guid>
      <description>UN-brokered Black Sea Grain Deal: Why Russia pulls back from deal and how it will impact Global food crisis - Explained Russia-Ukraine conflict led to the hamper of the transportation of grain from the Ukraine ports around the globe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold Price Today, October 30, 2022: Check gold rates in your city before buying</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-price-today-october-30-2022-check-gold-rates-in-your-city-before-bu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-price-today-october-30-2022-check-gold-rates-in-your-city-before-bu/</guid>
      <description>Gold Price Today, October 30, 2022: Check gold rates in your city before buying In Bengaluru, the standard gold of 99.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBI first time will submit report to Govt on failure to keep inflation below 6 per cent for 3 consecutive quarters</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-first-time-will-submit-report-to-govt-on-failure-to-keep-inflation-belo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-first-time-will-submit-report-to-govt-on-failure-to-keep-inflation-belo/</guid>
      <description>RBI first time will submit report to Govt on failure to keep inflation below 6 per cent for 3 consecutive quarters In case of failure to maintain the inflation target for three consecutive quarters, the central bank, under section 45ZN of the RBI Act, is required to submit a report to the government explaining the reasons and spelling out the remedial actions it would be taking to check the price rise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time To Leave Behind Old Challenges, Benefit From New Possibilities: PM Modi To J&amp;K Youth</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/time-to-leave-behind-old-challenges-benefit-from-new-possibilities-pm-mod/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 10:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/time-to-leave-behind-old-challenges-benefit-from-new-possibilities-pm-mod/</guid>
      <description>Time To Leave Behind Old Challenges, Benefit From New Possibilities: PM Modi To J&amp;amp;K Youth He also informed that efforts are on to strengthen the health and education infrastructure in Jammu and Kashmir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maruti Suzuki recalls over 9,000 units of Wagon R, Celerio and Ignis; Here&#39;s the reason WHY?</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/maruti-suzuki-recalls-over-9000-units-of-wagon-r-celerio-and-ignis-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 09:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/maruti-suzuki-recalls-over-9000-units-of-wagon-r-celerio-and-ignis-here/</guid>
      <description>Maruti Suzuki recalls over 9,000 units of Wagon R, Celerio and Ignis; Here&amp;rsquo;s the reason WHY?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telangana Withdraws General Consent To CBI: Additional AG Informs High Court</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/telangana-withdraws-general-consent-to-cbi-additional-ag-informs-high-cour/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 09:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/telangana-withdraws-general-consent-to-cbi-additional-ag-informs-high-cour/</guid>
      <description>Telangana Withdraws General Consent To CBI: Additional AG Informs High Court Three persons, who allegedly tried to &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bima Sugam To Be Game Changer For Insurance Sector: IRDAI Chairman</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bima-sugam-to-be-game-changer-for-insurance-sector-irdai-chairman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 09:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bima-sugam-to-be-game-changer-for-insurance-sector-irdai-chairman/</guid>
      <description>Bima Sugam To Be Game Changer For Insurance Sector: IRDAI Chairman He further said all the insurance intermediaries including individual agents, web aggregators will have access to this portal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Market Outlook: Earnings, U.S. Fed Interest Rate Decision Major Factors To Watch Out For</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/market-outlook-earnings-us-fed-interest-rate-decision-major-factors-to-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 09:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/market-outlook-earnings-us-fed-interest-rate-decision-major-factors-to-/</guid>
      <description>Market Outlook: Earnings, U.S. Fed Interest Rate Decision Major Factors To Watch Out For The ongoing quarterly earnings season, the Reserve Bank&#39;s special meeting of its rate-setting committee and the US Fed interest rate decision are the major events that would dictate trends in the equity market this week, analysts said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maruti Suzuki Recalls 9,925 Units Of 3 Models To Rectify Possible Defect In Brake Assembly</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/maruti-suzuki-recalls-9925-units-of-3-models-to-rectify-possible-defect-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 09:50:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/maruti-suzuki-recalls-9925-units-of-3-models-to-rectify-possible-defect-in/</guid>
      <description>Maruti Suzuki Recalls 9,925 Units Of 3 Models To Rectify Possible Defect In Brake Assembly The three models are Wagon R, Celerio and Ignis that are found to have a possible defect in rear brake assembly pin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Total Lunar Eclipse On Nov. 8</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/total-lunar-eclipse-on-nov-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 09:49:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/total-lunar-eclipse-on-nov-8/</guid>
      <description>Total Lunar Eclipse On Nov. 8 On Nov. 8, the partial eclipse of the moon will begin at around 14:39 hours and will reach its totality phase around 15:46 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk confirms Twitter to soon expand 280-Character limit on the platform</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-confirms-twitter-to-soon-expand-280-character-limit-on-the-platfo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 09:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-confirms-twitter-to-soon-expand-280-character-limit-on-the-platfo/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk confirms Twitter to soon expand 280-Character limit on the platform Musk, who has acquired Twitter for $44 billion after a bitter battle, said in April this year that the micro-blogging platform needs long-form tweets which is &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rahul Sprints, Others Try To Catch Up As Bharat Jodo Yatra Enters Day 5 In Telangana</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rahul-sprints-others-try-to-catch-up-as-bharat-jodo-yatra-enters-day-5-in-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 09:46:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rahul-sprints-others-try-to-catch-up-as-bharat-jodo-yatra-enters-day-5-in-/</guid>
      <description>Rahul Sprints, Others Try To Catch Up As Bharat Jodo Yatra Enters Day 5 In Telangana The Gandhi scion-led yatra completed over 20 km on Saturday, before halting at Jadcherla X Road Junction for the night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maruti Suzuki Recalls 9,925 Units Of Wagon R, Celerio And Ignis Due To Possible Defect In Rear Brake Assembly Pin</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/maruti-suzuki-recalls-9925-units-of-wagon-r-celerio-and-ignis-due-to-poss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 09:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/maruti-suzuki-recalls-9925-units-of-wagon-r-celerio-and-ignis-due-to-poss/</guid>
      <description>Maruti Suzuki Recalls 9,925 Units Of Wagon R, Celerio And Ignis Due To Possible Defect In Rear Brake Assembly Pin It is suspected that there is a possible defect in the rear brake assembly pin, which in a certain case, may break and cause a peculiar noise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unilever’s Health Data Shows Junk-Food Metrics Are Up For Debate</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/unilevers-health-data-shows-junk-food-metrics-are-up-for-debate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 07:23:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/unilevers-health-data-shows-junk-food-metrics-are-up-for-debate/</guid>
      <description>Unilever’s Health Data Shows Junk-Food Metrics Are Up For Debate Unilever said Friday it’s now aiming for 85% of its servings to meet its own science-based nutrition criteria by 2028.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musk’s Twitter Roils With Hate Speech As Trolls Test New Limits</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/musks-twitter-roils-with-hate-speech-as-trolls-test-new-limits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 07:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/musks-twitter-roils-with-hate-speech-as-trolls-test-new-limits/</guid>
      <description>Musk’s Twitter Roils With Hate Speech As Trolls Test New Limits Hateful and racist rhetoric swelled on the network as some politicians rejoiced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Bima Sugam will be a UPI moment for the insurance industry&#39;: IRDAI Chairman says on incubating one-stop platform</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bima-sugam-will-be-a-upi-moment-for-the-insurance-industry-irdai-chairma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 06:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bima-sugam-will-be-a-upi-moment-for-the-insurance-industry-irdai-chairma/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;Bima Sugam will be a UPI moment for the insurance industry&amp;rsquo;: IRDAI Chairman says on incubating one-stop platform Bima Sugam will be a one-stop shop for buying and selling insurance, for policy servicing, and also for claim settlement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charting The Global Economy: ECB Boosts Rates; Fed, BOE On Deck</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/charting-the-global-economy-ecb-boosts-rates-fed-boe-on-deck/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 06:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/charting-the-global-economy-ecb-boosts-rates-fed-boe-on-deck/</guid>
      <description>Charting The Global Economy: ECB Boosts Rates; Fed, BOE On Deck Here are some of the charts that appeared this week on the latest developments in the global economy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Mining Bill Permitting Cross-Border Crypto Payments Filed in Russian Parliament</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-mining-bill-permitting-cross-border-crypto-payments-filed-in-russian-pa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 18:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-mining-bill-permitting-cross-border-crypto-payments-filed-in-russian-pa/</guid>
      <description>New Mining Bill Permitting Cross-Border Crypto Payments Filed in Russian Parliament A draft law designed to regulate the mining of digital coins in Russia is also legalizing the use of cryptocurrencies in international settlements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Registrations open for BLoC Boardroom Challenge 2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/registrations-open-for-bloc-boardroom-challenge-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 17:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/registrations-open-for-bloc-boardroom-challenge-2022/</guid>
      <description>Registrations open for BLoC Boardroom Challenge 2022 In 2017, the first year of the challenge, LIBA Chennai won, followed by ISB Hyderabad in 2018, IIM Ranchi in 2019, SIBM Pune in 2020, and IIM Shillong in 2021</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian Railways goes International; Delivers 75 utility vehicles to Bhutan from Chennai for the first time</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indian-railways-goes-international-delivers-75-utility-vehicles-to-bhutan-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 15:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indian-railways-goes-international-delivers-75-utility-vehicles-to-bhutan-/</guid>
      <description>Indian Railways goes International; Delivers 75 utility vehicles to Bhutan from Chennai for the first time Delivering the utility vehicles is a first-of-its-kind initiative for Indian Railways and more goods would be delivered in the future based on demand from Bhutan, based on PTI&#39;s report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MG Air EV to debut at G20 Summit, unveiled as brand&#39;s first mass electric car ahead of India LAUNCH</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mg-air-ev-to-debut-at-g20-summit-unveiled-as-brands-first-mass-electric-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 10:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mg-air-ev-to-debut-at-g20-summit-unveiled-as-brands-first-mass-electric-c/</guid>
      <description>MG Air EV to debut at G20 Summit, unveiled as brand&amp;rsquo;s first mass electric car ahead of India LAUNCH MG Motor (Morris Garages) has unveiled the MG Air EV as the automaker&#39;s first mass-market electric car, which is expected to launch in India early next year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian Bank fixed deposits interest rates hiked by up to 90 bps for THESE tenures</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indian-bank-fixed-deposits-interest-rates-hiked-by-up-to-90-bps-for-these-t/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 10:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indian-bank-fixed-deposits-interest-rates-hiked-by-up-to-90-bps-for-these-t/</guid>
      <description>Indian Bank fixed deposits interest rates hiked by up to 90 bps for THESE tenures Indian Bank Fixed Deposit Rate 2022: For deposits less than Rs 2 crore, the Indian Bank has hiked interest rates for FD maturing in one year to 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sumangala Steel to install modern scrap shredder at Puducherry</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sumangala-steel-to-install-modern-scrap-shredder-at-puducherry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 10:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sumangala-steel-to-install-modern-scrap-shredder-at-puducherry/</guid>
      <description>Sumangala Steel to install modern scrap shredder at Puducherry “The modern scrap shredder will be imported to process end of life vehicles, white goods and light scrap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MG Air EV India Launch Details Revealed</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mg-air-ev-india-launch-details-revealed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 10:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mg-air-ev-india-launch-details-revealed/</guid>
      <description>MG Air EV India Launch Details Revealed The new MG Air EV is based on the Wuling Air EV, manufactured by SAIC-GM-Wuling since 2020, and is also the best-selling electric car in China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morning Digest | IndiGo plane grounded after engine catches fire at Delhi airport; Coimbatore car blast accused conducted reconnaissance of targets before attack, and more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/morning-digest-indigo-plane-grounded-after-engine-catches-fire-at-delhi-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 02:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/morning-digest-indigo-plane-grounded-after-engine-catches-fire-at-delhi-a/</guid>
      <description>Morning Digest | IndiGo plane grounded after engine catches fire at Delhi airport; Coimbatore car blast accused conducted reconnaissance of targets before attack, and more A select list of stories to read before you start your day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credit card spend jumps 14% in Sept</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/credit-card-spend-jumps-14-in-sept/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 02:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/credit-card-spend-jumps-14-in-sept/</guid>
      <description>Credit card spend jumps 14% in Sept toi</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petrol-Diesel Price Today, 29 October 2022: Check fuel rates in your city</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-diesel-price-today-29-october-2022-check-fuel-rates-in-your-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 02:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-diesel-price-today-29-october-2022-check-fuel-rates-in-your-city/</guid>
      <description>Petrol-Diesel Price Today, 29 October 2022: Check fuel rates in your city As on October 29, Petrol costs Rs 96.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rane Holdings posts 41% increase in Q2 consolidated net profit at ₹23 crore</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rane-holdings-posts-41-increase-in-q2-consolidated-net-profit-at-23-cro/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 16:46:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rane-holdings-posts-41-increase-in-q2-consolidated-net-profit-at-23-cro/</guid>
      <description>Rane Holdings posts 41% increase in Q2 consolidated net profit at ₹23 crore Total revenue rose 27% to ₹884 crore, while group aggregate sales increased 21% to ₹1,639 crore, the company said in a statement</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hero MotoCorp Registers 20 Per Cent Retail Growth YoY During Festive Period</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hero-motocorp-registers-20-per-cent-retail-growth-yoy-during-festive-period/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 16:44:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hero-motocorp-registers-20-per-cent-retail-growth-yoy-during-festive-period/</guid>
      <description>Hero MotoCorp Registers 20 Per Cent Retail Growth YoY During Festive Period Starting from the first day of Navratras till the day after Bhai Dooj, the two-wheeler giant announced that it managed to register a significant gain in its market share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Appalling”: Antony Blinken Blasts Russia’s Use Of Iranian Drones</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/appalling-antony-blinken-blasts-russias-use-of-iranian-drones/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/appalling-antony-blinken-blasts-russias-use-of-iranian-drones/</guid>
      <description>“Appalling”: Antony Blinken Blasts Russia’s Use Of Iranian Drones U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken says Russia&#39;s use of Iranian drones in Ukraine is &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEBI suspends license of Satellite Corporate for 3 months for ‘irregularities’</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sebi-suspends-license-of-satellite-corporate-for-3-months-for-irregulari/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 14:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sebi-suspends-license-of-satellite-corporate-for-3-months-for-irregulari/</guid>
      <description>SEBI suspends license of Satellite Corporate for 3 months for ‘irregularities’ thehindu</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carborundum Universal Q2 net rises 14% to ₹72 cr. on improved sales</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/carborundum-universal-q2-net-rises-14-to-72-cr-on-improved-sales/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 14:32:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/carborundum-universal-q2-net-rises-14-to-72-cr-on-improved-sales/</guid>
      <description>Carborundum Universal Q2 net rises 14% to ₹72 cr. on improved sales thehindu</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natural Gas Storage Site In The UK Reopens Ahead Of A Difficult Winter</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/natural-gas-storage-site-in-the-uk-reopens-ahead-of-a-difficult-winter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/natural-gas-storage-site-in-the-uk-reopens-ahead-of-a-difficult-winter/</guid>
      <description>Natural Gas Storage Site In The UK Reopens Ahead Of A Difficult Winter UK energy firm Centrica reopened its Rough natural gas storage site on Friday — which was closed five years ago — to boost storage capacity by 50% for this winter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBI governor Shaktikanta Das cautions on backdoor entry of fintechs</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-governor-shaktikanta-das-cautions-on-backdoor-entry-of-fintechs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-governor-shaktikanta-das-cautions-on-backdoor-entry-of-fintechs/</guid>
      <description>RBI governor Shaktikanta Das cautions on backdoor entry of fintechs Although some number of complaints is expected from such a large financial system, the concerning fact is much of the complaints pertain to traditional banking</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Google plans legal challenge to India&#39;s antitrust crackdown on Android&#39;</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-plans-legal-challenge-to-indias-antitrust-crackdown-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 14:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-plans-legal-challenge-to-indias-antitrust-crackdown-on-android/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;Google plans legal challenge to India&amp;rsquo;s antitrust crackdown on Android&amp;rsquo; The Alphabet Inc unit has been fined $275 million in two Indian antitrust decisions since last week - one for its policies of charging in-app commissions and another for abusing its position in the market for Android operating system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Slips Below $1 Trillion in Value After Bleak Outlook</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/amazon-slips-below-1-trillion-in-value-after-bleak-outlook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 14:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/amazon-slips-below-1-trillion-in-value-after-bleak-outlook/</guid>
      <description>Amazon Slips Below $1 Trillion in Value After Bleak Outlook The e-commerce giant joins a long list of US companies seeing their market values crumble.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delhi International Airport is world’s 10th busiest airport, Check top 10 LIST here</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/delhi-international-airport-is-worlds-10th-busiest-airport-check-top-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/delhi-international-airport-is-worlds-10th-busiest-airport-check-top-10/</guid>
      <description>Delhi International Airport is world’s 10th busiest airport, Check top 10 LIST here Delhi’s Indira Gandhi International airport is world’s 10th busiest airport, Hartsfield-Jackson Atlanta International Airport, Dubai international airport tops&#39; the list; Check top 10 list HERE, reports PTI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2023 KTM RC 8C Revealed; Only 200 Units Will Be Manufactured</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/2023-ktm-rc-8c-revealed-only-200-units-will-be-manufactured/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 10:10:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/2023-ktm-rc-8c-revealed-only-200-units-will-be-manufactured/</guid>
      <description>2023 KTM RC 8C Revealed; Only 200 Units Will Be Manufactured KTM took the wraps off the updated RC 8C sportbike and it will manufacture only 200 units of the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>European Union approves ban on new combustion-engine cars from 2035</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/european-union-approves-ban-on-new-combustion-engine-cars-from-2035/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 10:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/european-union-approves-ban-on-new-combustion-engine-cars-from-2035/</guid>
      <description>European Union approves ban on new combustion-engine cars from 2035 EU negotiators sealed the first agreement of the Bloc&#39;s “Fit for 55&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Police Received 631 Cryptocurrency Scam Reports in 2021, Government Says</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/singapore-police-received-631-cryptocurrency-scam-reports-in-2021-governme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 10:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/singapore-police-received-631-cryptocurrency-scam-reports-in-2021-governme/</guid>
      <description>Singapore Police Received 631 Cryptocurrency Scam Reports in 2021, Government Says The government of Singapore has revealed the number of crypto scams reported to the police in the past three years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBI reviewing regulation for governing non-core business of banks</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-reviewing-regulation-for-governing-non-core-business-of-banks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 09:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-reviewing-regulation-for-governing-non-core-business-of-banks/</guid>
      <description>RBI reviewing regulation for governing non-core business of banks The modifications in relation to banks&#39; non-core business could be made by amending the Banking Regulation Act</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foreign trade to be a defining feature in making India a USD 30 trillion economy: Piyush Goyal</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/foreign-trade-to-be-a-defining-feature-in-making-india-a-usd-30-trillion-ec/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 09:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/foreign-trade-to-be-a-defining-feature-in-making-india-a-usd-30-trillion-ec/</guid>
      <description>Foreign trade to be a defining feature in making India a USD 30 trillion economy: Piyush Goyal The Commerce Minister pointed out that the Indian economy grew 11.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delhi Traffic Police issues advisory to avoid Mehrauli-Badarpur road to SurajKund today due to THIS reason</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/delhi-traffic-police-issues-advisory-to-avoid-mehrauli-badarpur-road-to-sur/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 07:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/delhi-traffic-police-issues-advisory-to-avoid-mehrauli-badarpur-road-to-sur/</guid>
      <description>Delhi Traffic Police issues advisory to avoid Mehrauli-Badarpur road to SurajKund today due to THIS reason ALERT commuters!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Open National Pension Scheme (NPS) Account In Easy Steps? Details</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-open-national-pension-scheme-nps-account-in-easy-steps-details/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 07:19:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-to-open-national-pension-scheme-nps-account-in-easy-steps-details/</guid>
      <description>How To Open National Pension Scheme (NPS) Account In Easy Steps?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SBI Cards Q2 Review - Receivables Growth Strong, Revolver Mix Falling Again A Dampener: Prabhudas Lilladher</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sbi-cards-q2-review-receivables-growth-strong-revolver-mix-falling-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 07:12:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sbi-cards-q2-review-receivables-growth-strong-revolver-mix-falling-again/</guid>
      <description>SBI Cards Q2 Review - Receivables Growth Strong, Revolver Mix Falling Again A Dampener: Prabhudas Lilladher Yields fell as higher yielding revolver mix decreased to 24% from 26% in Q1 FY23 of overall receivables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oil Producers Likely To Stick To View Of Long-Term Oil Demand Rise</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oil-producers-likely-to-stick-to-view-of-long-term-oil-demand-rise/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 07:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oil-producers-likely-to-stick-to-view-of-long-term-oil-demand-rise/</guid>
      <description>Oil Producers Likely To Stick To View Of Long-Term Oil Demand Rise OPEC&#39;s view that world oil demand will keep rising for longer than many other forecasters predict is not expected to change much in its forthcoming major report, despite the growing role of renewables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Air India Express to launch Vijayawada-Sharjah direct flight from October 31, airfare starts at Rs 13,669</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/air-india-express-to-launch-vijayawada-sharjah-direct-flight-from-october-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/air-india-express-to-launch-vijayawada-sharjah-direct-flight-from-october-3/</guid>
      <description>Air India Express to launch Vijayawada-Sharjah direct flight from October 31, airfare starts at Rs 13,669 Air India Express is the only airline that offers international services in and out of Vijayawada, connecting it to Muscat and Kuwait with a B737-800 NG aircraft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SBI Cards Shares Decline As Q2 Profit Misses Estimates</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sbi-cards-shares-decline-as-q2-profit-misses-estimates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sbi-cards-shares-decline-as-q2-profit-misses-estimates/</guid>
      <description>SBI Cards Shares Decline As Q2 Profit Misses Estimates SBI Cards Q2 Results 2022-23: Net profit rose 28% year-on-year but dipped sequentially on higher operating spends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petrol, diesel prices today in Hyderabad, Delhi, Chennai and Mumbai on 28 October 2022, check here</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-diesel-prices-today-in-hyderabad-delhi-chennai-and-mumbai-on-28-o/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-diesel-prices-today-in-hyderabad-delhi-chennai-and-mumbai-on-28-o/</guid>
      <description>Petrol, diesel prices today in Hyderabad, Delhi, Chennai and Mumbai on 28 October 2022, check here Petrol and Diesel prices today, 28 October 2022: Petrol price in Hyderabad is Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BMW Makes 1,000 Deliveries Of G 310 RR In 100 Days Since Launch</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bmw-makes-1000-deliveries-of-g-310-rr-in-100-days-since-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bmw-makes-1000-deliveries-of-g-310-rr-in-100-days-since-launch/</guid>
      <description>BMW Makes 1,000 Deliveries Of G 310 RR In 100 Days Since Launch BMW Motorrad India has delivered 1,000 units of the BMW G 310 RR supersport motorcycle in just 100 days since it was launched on July 15, 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk Fires Twitter CEO Parag Agrawal, An Executive &#34;Escorted Out&#34; - NDTV</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-fires-twitter-ceo-parag-agrawal-an-executive-escorted-out-nd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-fires-twitter-ceo-parag-agrawal-an-executive-escorted-out-nd/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk Fires Twitter CEO Parag Agrawal, An Executive &amp;ldquo;Escorted Out&amp;rdquo; - NDTV Elon Musk Fires Twitter CEO Parag Agrawal, An Executive &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thai Airways to resume Hyderabad-Bangkok flight operations from October 30</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/thai-airways-to-resume-hyderabad-bangkok-flight-operations-from-october-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/thai-airways-to-resume-hyderabad-bangkok-flight-operations-from-october-30/</guid>
      <description>Thai Airways to resume Hyderabad-Bangkok flight operations from October 30 Telangana which houses many MNCs and is home to numerous industries and businesses is engaged actively in trade with Thailand and other nearby regions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commonwealth Secy Gen welcomes India’s offer to share UPI technology with member countries</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/commonwealth-secy-gen-welcomes-indias-offer-to-share-upi-technology-with/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/commonwealth-secy-gen-welcomes-indias-offer-to-share-upi-technology-with/</guid>
      <description>Commonwealth Secy Gen welcomes India’s offer to share UPI technology with member countries Payment through UPI crossed a milestone of ₹11 lakh crore in September, as per the data released by the National Payments Corporation of India</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Judge Orders Bitcoin Ponzi Operator Imprisoned for Ignoring Court Order to Pay SEC $40 Million</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/us-judge-orders-bitcoin-ponzi-operator-imprisoned-for-ignoring-court-order-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/us-judge-orders-bitcoin-ponzi-operator-imprisoned-for-ignoring-court-order-/</guid>
      <description>US Judge Orders Bitcoin Ponzi Operator Imprisoned for Ignoring Court Order to Pay SEC $40 Million A district judge has ordered a bitcoin Ponzi operator to be arrested and imprisoned after he ignored multiple court orders and failed to pay the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold rates today in Delhi, Chennai, Kolkata, Mumbai - 28 October 2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-rates-today-in-delhi-chennai-kolkata-mumbai-28-october-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 03:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-rates-today-in-delhi-chennai-kolkata-mumbai-28-october-2022/</guid>
      <description>Gold rates today in Delhi, Chennai, Kolkata, Mumbai - 28 October 2022 Gold rates today, 28 October 2022: Gold rates in Delhi per 10 grams of 22 carats is at Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk Takes Control Of Twitter, Fires Top Executives: Report - NDTV</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-takes-control-of-twitter-fires-top-executives-report-ndtv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 01:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-takes-control-of-twitter-fires-top-executives-report-ndtv/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk Takes Control Of Twitter, Fires Top Executives: Report - NDTV Elon Musk Takes Control Of Twitter, Fires Top Executives: Report NDTVDear Twitter advertisers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell Faces Political Pressure Over Interest Rate Hikes</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/federal-reserve-chairman-jerome-powell-faces-political-pressure-over-intere/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/federal-reserve-chairman-jerome-powell-faces-political-pressure-over-intere/</guid>
      <description>Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell Faces Political Pressure Over Interest Rate Hikes U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon set to report earnings after disappointing reports from Big Tech</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/amazon-set-to-report-earnings-after-disappointing-reports-from-big-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 16:35:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/amazon-set-to-report-earnings-after-disappointing-reports-from-big-tech/</guid>
      <description>Amazon set to report earnings after disappointing reports from Big Tech yahoo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musk-Twitter Countdown to Close $44 Billion Deal Begins</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/musk-twitter-countdown-to-close-44-billion-deal-begins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 16:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/musk-twitter-countdown-to-close-44-billion-deal-begins/</guid>
      <description>Musk-Twitter Countdown to Close $44 Billion Deal Begins After months of “will they or won’t they,” Elon Musk is running up against a court-ordered deadline to deliver on his promise to buy Twitter Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aramco Unveils $1.5B Mega VC Fund For Sustainability</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/aramco-unveils-15b-mega-vc-fund-for-sustainability/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/aramco-unveils-15b-mega-vc-fund-for-sustainability/</guid>
      <description>Aramco Unveils $1.5B Mega VC Fund For Sustainability Saudi Arabia’s national oil company Saudi Aramco has launched a $1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Repsol: Parts Of Europe Are Running Out Of Diesel</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/repsol-parts-of-europe-are-running-out-of-diesel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/repsol-parts-of-europe-are-running-out-of-diesel/</guid>
      <description>Repsol: Parts Of Europe Are Running Out Of Diesel The diesel crisis in Europe is heating up, with parts of Europe starting to run out of diesel, Repsol Chief Executive Officer Josu Jon Imaz said on Thursday’s earnings call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia: Commercial Satellites Could Be Targeted In Retaliatory Strikes</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/russia-commercial-satellites-could-be-targeted-in-retaliatory-strikes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/russia-commercial-satellites-could-be-targeted-in-retaliatory-strikes/</guid>
      <description>Russia: Commercial Satellites Could Be Targeted In Retaliatory Strikes A senior official from Russia&#39;s Foreign Ministry has warned that Western commercial satellites could become &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SBI Cards Q2 Results: Net Profit Rises But Misses Estimates</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sbi-cards-q2-results-net-profit-rises-but-misses-estimates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 15:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sbi-cards-q2-results-net-profit-rises-but-misses-estimates/</guid>
      <description>SBI Cards Q2 Results: Net Profit Rises But Misses Estimates SBI Cards&#39; net profit missed estimates and stood at Rs 526 crore in the second quarter on financial year 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walkaroo expands Karnataka plant to make PU footwear</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/walkaroo-expands-karnataka-plant-to-make-pu-footwear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 15:23:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/walkaroo-expands-karnataka-plant-to-make-pu-footwear/</guid>
      <description>Walkaroo expands Karnataka plant to make PU footwear thehindu</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meta shares are in free fall</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/meta-shares-are-in-free-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 15:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/meta-shares-are-in-free-fall/</guid>
      <description>Meta shares are in free fall yahoo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tamilnad Mercantile Bank H1 net rises 27% to ₹497 crore</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tamilnad-mercantile-bank-h1-net-rises-27-to-497-crore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 15:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tamilnad-mercantile-bank-h1-net-rises-27-to-497-crore/</guid>
      <description>Tamilnad Mercantile Bank H1 net rises 27% to ₹497 crore H1 net interest income grows 18% to ₹1,033 crore</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oil Companies Flee Venezuela, Leaving All Behind</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oil-companies-flee-venezuela-leaving-all-behind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oil-companies-flee-venezuela-leaving-all-behind/</guid>
      <description>Oil Companies Flee Venezuela, Leaving All Behind In a move reminiscent of the Hugo Chavez years when Venezuela nationalized its oil industry, stripping by default many foreign oil companies of their assets, oil companies are once again preparing to abandon operations in the nation that houses the largest oil reserves on the planet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBI to recall its nominee from RBL Board</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-to-recall-its-nominee-from-rbl-board/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 14:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-to-recall-its-nominee-from-rbl-board/</guid>
      <description>RBI to recall its nominee from RBL Board Yogesh Dayal RBI’s chief general manager, was appointed as an additional director on the RBL board in December 2021 for two years</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBI to hold additional MPC meet on Nov 3</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-to-hold-additional-mpc-meet-on-nov-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 14:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-to-hold-additional-mpc-meet-on-nov-3/</guid>
      <description>RBI to hold additional MPC meet on Nov 3 To discuss and draft report on inflation to be submitted to the Centre</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tamilnad Mercantile Bank posts 37.5% rise in net in Q2</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tamilnad-mercantile-bank-posts-375-rise-in-net-in-q2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 14:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tamilnad-mercantile-bank-posts-375-rise-in-net-in-q2/</guid>
      <description>Tamilnad Mercantile Bank posts 37.5% rise in net in Q2 For H1 FY23, Tamilnad Mercantile Bank’s net profit grew 27% to ₹496.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IEA: Renewable Energy Investment Needs To Triple By 2030</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/iea-renewable-energy-investment-needs-to-triple-by-2030/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:19:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/iea-renewable-energy-investment-needs-to-triple-by-2030/</guid>
      <description>IEA: Renewable Energy Investment Needs To Triple By 2030 Investment in renewables must more than triple to $1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBI Calls Additional Monetary Policy Committee Meeting On Nov. 3</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-calls-additional-monetary-policy-committee-meeting-on-nov-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-calls-additional-monetary-policy-committee-meeting-on-nov-3/</guid>
      <description>RBI Calls Additional Monetary Policy Committee Meeting On Nov. 3 The meeting will be held under Section 45ZN of the RBI Act, which spells out the course of action for missing inflation target.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morgan Stanley Downgrades Meta For First Time As Costs Soar</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/morgan-stanley-downgrades-meta-for-first-time-as-costs-soar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/morgan-stanley-downgrades-meta-for-first-time-as-costs-soar/</guid>
      <description>Morgan Stanley Downgrades Meta For First Time As Costs Soar Shares of the Facebook parent were down 20% in premarket trading after it gave a disappointing quarterly revenue outlook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Link Your PAN and Aadhaar Now By Paying A Fine Of ₹1000</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/link-your-pan-and-aadhaar-now-by-paying-a-fine-of-1000/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/link-your-pan-and-aadhaar-now-by-paying-a-fine-of-1000/</guid>
      <description>Link Your PAN and Aadhaar Now By Paying A Fine Of ₹1000 Find out the details related to linking you PAN and Aadhar card and the fine will one have to pay considering the deadline date</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shell To Hike Dividend After Another Very Strong Quarter</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/shell-to-hike-dividend-after-another-very-strong-quarter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/shell-to-hike-dividend-after-another-very-strong-quarter/</guid>
      <description>Shell To Hike Dividend After Another Very Strong Quarter Shell (NYSE: SHEL) intends to lift its dividend and is launching a new share buyback program after reporting its second-highest quarterly earnings for Q3, second only to the record profit for the previous quarter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SoftBank-backed tech unicorn Kavak expands in Middle East</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/softbank-backed-tech-unicorn-kavak-expands-in-middle-east/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 09:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/softbank-backed-tech-unicorn-kavak-expands-in-middle-east/</guid>
      <description>SoftBank-backed tech unicorn Kavak expands in Middle East Kavak plans to invest $130 million over the next two years in the three Middle-Eastern countries, which are set to represent 7-10% of its business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Russian Oil Price Cap Could Be Set Between $63 And $64 Per Barrel</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-russian-oil-price-cap-could-be-set-between-63-and-64-per-barrel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-russian-oil-price-cap-could-be-set-between-63-and-64-per-barrel/</guid>
      <description>The Russian Oil Price Cap Could Be Set Between $63 And $64 Per Barrel Western governments are in the final stages of preparing for the implementation of a price cap on Russian oil exports, Reuters has reported, noting that the price range for the cap has yet to be set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyundai&#39;s Air Taxi Unit Picks Honeywell As Avionics Supplier</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hyundais-air-taxi-unit-picks-honeywell-as-avionics-supplier/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 06:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hyundais-air-taxi-unit-picks-honeywell-as-avionics-supplier/</guid>
      <description>Hyundai&amp;rsquo;s Air Taxi Unit Picks Honeywell As Avionics Supplier Under the collaboration, Honeywell will work with Supernal, Hyundai&#39;s U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Housing sales in top 7 cities gain momentum in the ongoing Diwali festive period</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/housing-sales-in-top-7-cities-gain-momentum-in-the-ongoing-diwali-festive-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 06:37:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/housing-sales-in-top-7-cities-gain-momentum-in-the-ongoing-diwali-festive-p/</guid>
      <description>Housing sales in top 7 cities gain momentum in the ongoing Diwali festive period As per the latest research by real estate consultancy firm Anarock, total sales in the top seven cities can exceed 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tesla faces criminal probe in the United States over self-driving electric vehicle claims: Report</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tesla-faces-criminal-probe-in-the-united-states-over-self-driving-electric-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 06:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tesla-faces-criminal-probe-in-the-united-states-over-self-driving-electric-/</guid>
      <description>Tesla faces criminal probe in the United States over self-driving electric vehicle claims: Report Elon Musk, the CEO of Tesla Inc, electric vehicle automaker once described the Tesla&#39;s autopilot as “probably better” than a human driver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian Government receives dividends worth Rs 361 cr from Public Sector Undertakings (PSUs)</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indian-government-receives-dividends-worth-rs-361-cr-from-public-sector-und/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 06:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indian-government-receives-dividends-worth-rs-361-cr-from-public-sector-und/</guid>
      <description>Indian Government receives dividends worth Rs 361 cr from Public Sector Undertakings (PSUs) Secretary in the department of investment and public asset management (DIPAM) Tuhin Kanta Pandey tweeted the details on his official Twitter account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEBI: Know More About The Securities And Exchange Board Of India</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sebi-know-more-about-the-securities-and-exchange-board-of-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 06:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sebi-know-more-about-the-securities-and-exchange-board-of-india/</guid>
      <description>SEBI: Know More About The Securities And Exchange Board Of India Learn about SEBI, what it does, its structure, and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine To Impose Electricity Supply Restrictions</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ukraine-to-impose-electricity-supply-restrictions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 06:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ukraine-to-impose-electricity-supply-restrictions/</guid>
      <description>Ukraine To Impose Electricity Supply Restrictions Ukraine has started restricting electricity supplies across the country after Russia knocked out more power plants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Q2 Review: How Sustainable Is Route Mobile&#39;s Strong Earnings Growth?</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/q2-review-how-sustainable-is-route-mobiles-strong-earnings-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 06:29:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/q2-review-how-sustainable-is-route-mobiles-strong-earnings-growth/</guid>
      <description>Q2 Review: How Sustainable Is Route Mobile&amp;rsquo;s Strong Earnings Growth? Continue Reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Q2 Review: Why Nazara Tech Focuses On Growth At Cost Of Margins</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/q2-review-why-nazara-tech-focuses-on-growth-at-cost-of-margins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 06:29:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/q2-review-why-nazara-tech-focuses-on-growth-at-cost-of-margins/</guid>
      <description>Q2 Review: Why Nazara Tech Focuses On Growth At Cost Of Margins Continue Reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second largest cryptocurrency Ethereum&#39;s dominance in crypto market up 20% after the &#39;Merge&#39;</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/second-largest-cryptocurrency-ethereums-dominance-in-crypto-market-up-20-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 06:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/second-largest-cryptocurrency-ethereums-dominance-in-crypto-market-up-20-/</guid>
      <description>Second largest cryptocurrency Ethereum&amp;rsquo;s dominance in crypto market up 20% after the &amp;lsquo;Merge&amp;rsquo; The ‘Merge’ last month will create a more energy-efficient network based on the second largest cryptocurrency with a promise to save the environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slovakia&#39;s InoBat Eyes Electric Car Battery Plant In Spain</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/slovakias-inobat-eyes-electric-car-battery-plant-in-spain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 06:22:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/slovakias-inobat-eyes-electric-car-battery-plant-in-spain/</guid>
      <description>Slovakia&amp;rsquo;s InoBat Eyes Electric Car Battery Plant In Spain The declaration is not a finalised agreement and other locations, including the United Kingdom, remain under consideration for its Western European gigafactory, the company added in a statement, explaining that it plans to make a decision on the location before the end of the year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TotalEnergies Takes Temporary Control Of Offshore Gas Block In Lebanon</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/totalenergies-takes-temporary-control-of-offshore-gas-block-in-lebanon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 06:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/totalenergies-takes-temporary-control-of-offshore-gas-block-in-lebanon/</guid>
      <description>TotalEnergies Takes Temporary Control Of Offshore Gas Block In Lebanon The Lebanese caretaker government has awarded TotalEnergies temporary control of an offshore gas block after the exit of Russian Novatek last month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JSW Steel Expects Margins To Revive After Surprise Loss</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/jsw-steel-expects-margins-to-revive-after-surprise-loss/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 06:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/jsw-steel-expects-margins-to-revive-after-surprise-loss/</guid>
      <description>JSW Steel Expects Margins To Revive After Surprise Loss India’s JSW Steel Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Ginger not cockroach&#39; Vistara defends in-flight meal after testing food in laboratory</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ginger-not-cockroach-vistara-defends-in-flight-meal-after-testing-food-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 03:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ginger-not-cockroach-vistara-defends-in-flight-meal-after-testing-food-in/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;Ginger not cockroach&amp;rsquo; Vistara defends in-flight meal after testing food in laboratory A Vistara airline passenger shared a post on Twitter with a picture of a in-flight meal showing a small cockroach in it, which was later defended by Jet Airways CEO who believes the post to be bogus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Share Market Live: Sensex, Nifty Set To Gain; DLF, M&amp;M In Focus</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/share-market-live-sensex-nifty-set-to-gain-dlf-mm-in-focus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 03:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/share-market-live-sensex-nifty-set-to-gain-dlf-mm-in-focus/</guid>
      <description>Share Market Live: Sensex, Nifty Set To Gain; DLF, M&amp;amp;M In Focus Live updates from India&#39;s equity markets on Oct.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyundai &amp; WeRide Plan To Have Self Driving Cars Propelled By Hydrogen In China</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hyundai-weride-plan-to-have-self-driving-cars-propelled-by-hydrogen-in-ch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 02:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hyundai-weride-plan-to-have-self-driving-cars-propelled-by-hydrogen-in-ch/</guid>
      <description>Hyundai &amp;amp; WeRide Plan To Have Self Driving Cars Propelled By Hydrogen In China Hyundai is pushing ahead with developing hydrogen fuel cell-based self-driving vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indians Have Good Reason To Celebrate Rishi Sunak</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indians-have-good-reason-to-celebrate-rishi-sunak/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 02:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indians-have-good-reason-to-celebrate-rishi-sunak/</guid>
      <description>Indians Have Good Reason To Celebrate Rishi Sunak If, next year, Rishi Sunak cheerfully puts Diwali candles outside the house that once was Winston Churchill’s, you’re not Indian if you don’t smile a little.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Overpaying&#39; Musk on deadline to close Twitter deal</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/overpaying-musk-on-deadline-to-close-twitter-deal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 02:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/overpaying-musk-on-deadline-to-close-twitter-deal/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;Overpaying&amp;rsquo; Musk on deadline to close Twitter deal Musk signaled the deal was on track Wednesday by changing his Twitter profile to &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archer Aviation Plans To Build 250 Air Taxis In 2025</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/archer-aviation-plans-to-build-250-air-taxis-in-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 02:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/archer-aviation-plans-to-build-250-air-taxis-in-2025/</guid>
      <description>Archer Aviation Plans To Build 250 Air Taxis In 2025 Archer Aviation aims to make about 250 battery-electric air taxis in 2025 and scale up production in the following years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oil Prices Drop As China Demand Data Disappoints</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oil-prices-drop-as-china-demand-data-disappoints/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 02:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oil-prices-drop-as-china-demand-data-disappoints/</guid>
      <description>Oil Prices Drop As China Demand Data Disappoints Oil prices slid 2% after Chinese data showed that demand from the world&#39;s largest crude importer remained lacklustre in September as strict COVID-19 policies and fuel export curbs depressed consumption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>French Government: On Right Track Over Further Easing Petrol Supply Problems</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/french-government-on-right-track-over-further-easing-petrol-supply-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 02:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/french-government-on-right-track-over-further-easing-petrol-supply-problem/</guid>
      <description>French Government: On Right Track Over Further Easing Petrol Supply Problems The French government said France was on the right track over further easing the problem of petrol service stations not having enough petrol due to strikes at oil refineries, which had hit motorists around the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toyota Scrambles For EV Reboot With Eye On Tesla</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/toyota-scrambles-for-ev-reboot-with-eye-on-tesla/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 02:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/toyota-scrambles-for-ev-reboot-with-eye-on-tesla/</guid>
      <description>Toyota Scrambles For EV Reboot With Eye On Tesla Toyota is considering a reboot of its electric-car strategy to better compete in a booming market it has been slow to enter, and has halted some work on existing EV projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flying Car By California Startup Alef Attracts Early Tesla Investor</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/flying-car-by-california-startup-alef-attracts-early-tesla-investor/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 02:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/flying-car-by-california-startup-alef-attracts-early-tesla-investor/</guid>
      <description>Flying Car By California Startup Alef Attracts Early Tesla Investor Inventors have been trying to add wings to wheeled motor vehicles for decades, with only limited success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terawatt Plans Electric Truck Charging Stations From LA To El Paso</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/terawatt-plans-electric-truck-charging-stations-from-la-to-el-paso/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 02:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/terawatt-plans-electric-truck-charging-stations-from-la-to-el-paso/</guid>
      <description>Terawatt Plans Electric Truck Charging Stations From LA To El Paso Terawatt will develop a U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Battery Giant CATL Profit Jumps As It Ramps Up Output</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/chinese-battery-giant-catl-profit-jumps-as-it-ramps-up-output/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 02:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/chinese-battery-giant-catl-profit-jumps-as-it-ramps-up-output/</guid>
      <description>Chinese Battery Giant CATL Profit Jumps As It Ramps Up Output CATL&#39;s third-quarter profit nearly tripled year-on-year, buoyed by rapid expansion in production to power the growth of EVs worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India&#39;s ONGC Eyes Stake In Russian Entity Managing Sakhalin 1 - Report</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indias-ongc-eyes-stake-in-russian-entity-managing-sakhalin-1-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 02:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indias-ongc-eyes-stake-in-russian-entity-managing-sakhalin-1-report/</guid>
      <description>India&amp;rsquo;s ONGC Eyes Stake In Russian Entity Managing Sakhalin 1 - Report Oil and Natural Gas Corp (ONGC) plans to take a stake in the new Russian entity that will manage the Sakhalin 1 project in the far east.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>French Refinery Strike Further Hits Petrol Supplies, Says PM</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/french-refinery-strike-further-hits-petrol-supplies-says-pm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 02:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/french-refinery-strike-further-hits-petrol-supplies-says-pm/</guid>
      <description>French Refinery Strike Further Hits Petrol Supplies, Says PM Petrol supplies at French service stations fell further over the weekend due to a weeks-long strike at oil major TotalEnergies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India Raises Windfall Tax On Crude Oil Output</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-raises-windfall-tax-on-crude-oil-output/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 02:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-raises-windfall-tax-on-crude-oil-output/</guid>
      <description>India Raises Windfall Tax On Crude Oil Output India has raised a windfall tax on domestically produced crude oil to 11,000 Indian rupees per tonne from 8,000 rupees per tonne.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High Energy Prices Force The World’s Largest Chemicals Company To Downsize</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/high-energy-prices-force-the-worlds-largest-chemicals-company-to-downsiz/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/high-energy-prices-force-the-worlds-largest-chemicals-company-to-downsiz/</guid>
      <description>High Energy Prices Force The World’s Largest Chemicals Company To Downsize The world’s biggest chemicals company, Germany-based BASF, will seek permanent cost-saving measures in Europe due to the high energy prices endangering its competitiveness, chief executive Martin Brudermüller said on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man buys TVS scooter by paying Rs 50,000 in coins; dealership staff goes BONKERS counting</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/man-buys-tvs-scooter-by-paying-rs-50000-in-coins-dealership-staff-goes-bo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/man-buys-tvs-scooter-by-paying-rs-50000-in-coins-dealership-staff-goes-bo/</guid>
      <description>Man buys TVS scooter by paying Rs 50,000 in coins; dealership staff goes BONKERS counting A TVS Jupiter was recently bought in Rudrapur, Uttarakhand, with coins of Rs 10, totalling to Rs 50,000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>J&amp;K Bank to complete transfer of Rs 960 cr NPAs to NARCL by October-end</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/jk-bank-to-complete-transfer-of-rs-960-cr-npas-to-narcl-by-october-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/jk-bank-to-complete-transfer-of-rs-960-cr-npas-to-narcl-by-october-end/</guid>
      <description>J&amp;amp;K Bank to complete transfer of Rs 960 cr NPAs to NARCL by October-end Jammu and Kashmir Bank will put up for sale non-performing assets to the tune of Rs 960 crore, as part of its efforts to improve its balance sheet, sources in the bank said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biggest Movers: DOGE Hits 2-Month High, ADA Rallies by 10%</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/biggest-movers-doge-hits-2-month-high-ada-rallies-by-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/biggest-movers-doge-hits-2-month-high-ada-rallies-by-10/</guid>
      <description>Biggest Movers: DOGE Hits 2-Month High, ADA Rallies by 10% A day after hitting a one-week high, dogecoin raced to a two-month high earlier in today’s session.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India to see highest salary hike in 2023, Pakistan in bottom five: Report</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-to-see-highest-salary-hike-in-2023-pakistan-in-bottom-five-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-to-see-highest-salary-hike-in-2023-pakistan-in-bottom-five-report/</guid>
      <description>India to see highest salary hike in 2023, Pakistan in bottom five: Report Soaring inflation is set to put a major dent in salary increases for the second year running in 2023, according to a new survey that sees just 37% of countries globally expecting to report real-term wage hikes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India will not impose anti-dumping duty on Chinese chemical: Finance Ministry</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-will-not-impose-anti-dumping-duty-on-chinese-chemical-finance-minist/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 12:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-will-not-impose-anti-dumping-duty-on-chinese-chemical-finance-minist/</guid>
      <description>India will not impose anti-dumping duty on Chinese chemical: Finance Ministry The duty is imposed only after a thorough investigation by a quasi-judicial body, such as DGTR, in India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2023 Yamaha MT-07 Turns Modern, MT-125 Gets Safer</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/2023-yamaha-mt-07-turns-modern-mt-125-gets-safer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 12:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/2023-yamaha-mt-07-turns-modern-mt-125-gets-safer/</guid>
      <description>2023 Yamaha MT-07 Turns Modern, MT-125 Gets Safer Yamaha has given the MT-07 and MT-125 a TFT colour display with connectivity for the new model year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hero MotoCorp Announces Entry Into South-East Asian Market With Philippines</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hero-motocorp-announces-entry-into-south-east-asian-market-with-philippines/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 12:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hero-motocorp-announces-entry-into-south-east-asian-market-with-philippines/</guid>
      <description>Hero MotoCorp Announces Entry Into South-East Asian Market With Philippines Hero MotoCorp plans to set up an assembly facility of 29,000 sq.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK Bonds Fall After Government Delays Fiscal Plan To Next Month</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/uk-bonds-fall-after-government-delays-fiscal-plan-to-next-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 10:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/uk-bonds-fall-after-government-delays-fiscal-plan-to-next-month/</guid>
      <description>UK Bonds Fall After Government Delays Fiscal Plan To Next Month UK bonds fell as the government delayed its fiscal plan due next week, prolonging uncertainty weighing on the nation’s fragile markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mandate To Show PUC Certificate To Refuel In Delhi Put On Hold; Government Launches ‘Red Light On, Gaadi Off’ Campaign</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mandate-to-show-puc-certificate-to-refuel-in-delhi-put-on-hold-government-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 10:33:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mandate-to-show-puc-certificate-to-refuel-in-delhi-put-on-hold-government-/</guid>
      <description>Mandate To Show PUC Certificate To Refuel In Delhi Put On Hold; Government Launches ‘Red Light On, Gaadi Off’ Campaign Announcing the launch of the &#39;Red Light On, Gaadi Off’ campaign from October 28, Delhi Environment Minister, Gopal Rai said that the notification that required vehicle owners to produce a valid PUC certificate to refuel at a petrol pump has been put on hold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dabur Q2 profit slips 2.8% to Rs 491 crore; revenue up 6%</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dabur-q2-profit-slips-28-to-rs-491-crore-revenue-up-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 10:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dabur-q2-profit-slips-28-to-rs-491-crore-revenue-up-6/</guid>
      <description>Dabur Q2 profit slips 2.8% to Rs 491 crore; revenue up 6% Dabur India&#39;s total expenses increased 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gland Pharma Q2 Results: Profit Falls Missing Estimates</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gland-pharma-q2-results-profit-falls-missing-estimates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 10:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gland-pharma-q2-results-profit-falls-missing-estimates/</guid>
      <description>Gland Pharma Q2 Results: Profit Falls Missing Estimates Gland Pharma&#39;s Q2 profit fell 20% year-on-year to Rs 241 crore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>As EV Sales Grow, Battle Over U.S. Road Weight Limits Heats Up</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/as-ev-sales-grow-battle-over-us-road-weight-limits-heats-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 09:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/as-ev-sales-grow-battle-over-us-road-weight-limits-heats-up/</guid>
      <description>As EV Sales Grow, Battle Over U.S. Road Weight Limits Heats Up Even before a recent spike in EV sales, U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audi Set To Enter Formula 1 As A Full Works Team From 2026</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/audi-set-to-enter-formula-1-as-a-full-works-team-from-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 09:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/audi-set-to-enter-formula-1-as-a-full-works-team-from-2026/</guid>
      <description>Audi Set To Enter Formula 1 As A Full Works Team From 2026 Audi will acquire a stake in the Sauber (Alfa Romeo) F1 team, and will also develop its own engines for a full works entry from the 2026 season onwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musk, Twitter Could Reach Deal To End Court Battle, Close Buyout Soon: Report</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/musk-twitter-could-reach-deal-to-end-court-battle-close-buyout-soon-repo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 08:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/musk-twitter-could-reach-deal-to-end-court-battle-close-buyout-soon-repo/</guid>
      <description>Musk, Twitter Could Reach Deal To End Court Battle, Close Buyout Soon: Report Musk, who is also chief executive officer of electric car maker Tesla Inc, proposed to Twitter late on Monday he would change course and abide by his April agreement to buy the company for $54.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honda To Cut Car Output At Two Japanese Plants In October</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/honda-to-cut-car-output-at-two-japanese-plants-in-october/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 08:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/honda-to-cut-car-output-at-two-japanese-plants-in-october/</guid>
      <description>Honda To Cut Car Output At Two Japanese Plants In October Two lines at Honda&#39;s Suzuka plant in western Japan will cut production by about 20% in October, while its assembly plant in Saitama prefecture, north of Tokyo, will lower production plans by about 40% for the month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Explainer-What Is An &#39;Everything App&#39; And Why Does Elon Musk Want To Make One?</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/explainer-what-is-an-everything-app-and-why-does-elon-musk-want-to-make-o/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 08:42:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/explainer-what-is-an-everything-app-and-why-does-elon-musk-want-to-make-o/</guid>
      <description>Explainer-What Is An &amp;lsquo;Everything App&amp;rsquo; And Why Does Elon Musk Want To Make One?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sequoia India may invest $50 mn in homegrown edtech startup</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sequoia-india-may-invest-50-mn-in-homegrown-edtech-startup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 08:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sequoia-india-may-invest-50-mn-in-homegrown-edtech-startup/</guid>
      <description>Sequoia India may invest $50 mn in homegrown edtech startup According to a TechCrunch report on Tuesday, K12 Techno Services which has raised more than $75 million in previous rounds and also engaged with TPG and Accel decided to go with existing backer Sequoia India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7th Pay Commission: Big update on fitment factor after hike in DA, salary likely to increase by Rs 49,420</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/7th-pay-commission-big-update-on-fitment-factor-after-hike-in-da-salary-l/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 08:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/7th-pay-commission-big-update-on-fitment-factor-after-hike-in-da-salary-l/</guid>
      <description>7th Pay Commission: Big update on fitment factor after hike in DA, salary likely to increase by Rs 49,420 If the government increases the fitment factor 3 times, then the salary of the employees excluding allowances will be 18,000 X 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eco-Activists Storm Paris Motor Show And Vandalise Supercars Including A $180,000 Ferrari</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/eco-activists-storm-paris-motor-show-and-vandalise-supercars-including-a-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 08:03:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/eco-activists-storm-paris-motor-show-and-vandalise-supercars-including-a-1/</guid>
      <description>Eco-Activists Storm Paris Motor Show And Vandalise Supercars Including A $180,000 Ferrari In addition to holding up banners and chanting slogans, four out of the near dozen protesters glued their hands to a few supercars and smeared black paint on their bonnets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Royal Enfield Hunter 350 Beats Honda CB350 In Sep 2022 Sales</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/royal-enfield-hunter-350-beats-honda-cb350-in-sep-2022-sales/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 07:53:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/royal-enfield-hunter-350-beats-honda-cb350-in-sep-2022-sales/</guid>
      <description>Royal Enfield Hunter 350 Beats Honda CB350 In Sep 2022 Sales GaadiWaadi - Royal Enfield Hunter 350 has an aggressive starting price of Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zee Auto Awards 2022: A preview - Check all categories and nominations HERE</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/zee-auto-awards-2022-a-preview-check-all-categories-and-nominations-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 07:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/zee-auto-awards-2022-a-preview-check-all-categories-and-nominations-here/</guid>
      <description>Zee Auto Awards 2022: A preview - Check all categories and nominations HERE After a stupendous first edition, the Zee Auto Awards are back to business to honour the best launches from the Indian automotive industry in the past one year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk Admits That Tesla Will Not Get Approval For Self-Driving Cars</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-admits-that-tesla-will-not-get-approval-for-self-driving-cars/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 06:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/elon-musk-admits-that-tesla-will-not-get-approval-for-self-driving-cars/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk Admits That Tesla Will Not Get Approval For Self-Driving Cars Elon Musk has finally admitted that Tesla wouldn&#39;t be getting a driverless car permit anytime soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Europe’s Gas Glut to Help Ease Winter LNG Supply Crunch in Asia</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/europes-gas-glut-to-help-ease-winter-lng-supply-crunch-in-asia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 06:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/europes-gas-glut-to-help-ease-winter-lng-supply-crunch-in-asia/</guid>
      <description>Europe’s Gas Glut to Help Ease Winter LNG Supply Crunch in Asia Europe’s near-term natural gas supply glut means more fuel for Asia this winter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2023 Honda Accord Teased Ahead Of Debut</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/2023-honda-accord-teased-ahead-of-debut/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 06:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/2023-honda-accord-teased-ahead-of-debut/</guid>
      <description>2023 Honda Accord Teased Ahead Of Debut The new-gen Honda Accord will make its debut in November and the teaser images give us an idea of what to expect in terms of design and features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Proposes Ban on Borrowing to Fund Cryptocurrency Purchases</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/singapore-proposes-ban-on-borrowing-to-fund-cryptocurrency-purchases/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 06:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/singapore-proposes-ban-on-borrowing-to-fund-cryptocurrency-purchases/</guid>
      <description>Singapore Proposes Ban on Borrowing to Fund Cryptocurrency Purchases Singapore proposed to ban retail investors from borrowing to fund cryptocurrency purchases, moving to tighten regulatory regime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attention SBI customers! SBI Utsav special fixed deposit (FD) scheme ends in two days, Check details</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/attention-sbi-customers-sbi-utsav-special-fixed-deposit-fd-scheme-ends-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 06:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/attention-sbi-customers-sbi-utsav-special-fixed-deposit-fd-scheme-ends-i/</guid>
      <description>Attention SBI customers! SBI Utsav special fixed deposit (FD) scheme ends in two days, Check details The State Bank of India (SBI) started a limited period offer term deposit called ‘Utsav Deposit’ starting 15 August.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australia inflation races to 32-year high, sounds rates alarm</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/australia-inflation-races-to-32-year-high-sounds-rates-alarm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 06:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/australia-inflation-races-to-32-year-high-sounds-rates-alarm/</guid>
      <description>Australia inflation races to 32-year high, sounds rates alarm Data from the Australian Bureau of Statistics (ABS) on Wednesday showed the consumer price index (CPI) jumped 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diwali 2022: Passenger Vehicles Sales Paces Up During Dhanteras – Report</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/diwali-2022-passenger-vehicles-sales-paces-up-during-dhanteras-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 02:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/diwali-2022-passenger-vehicles-sales-paces-up-during-dhanteras-report/</guid>
      <description>Diwali 2022: Passenger Vehicles Sales Paces Up During Dhanteras – Report Sales of passenger vehicles went up by nearly a tenth in in the two days of Dhanteras.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morning Digest | Mallikarjun Kharge to officially take charge as Congress president today; UNSC members to pay tributes at Mumbai 26/11 memorial on Friday, and more</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/morning-digest-mallikarjun-kharge-to-officially-take-charge-as-congress-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 02:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/morning-digest-mallikarjun-kharge-to-officially-take-charge-as-congress-p/</guid>
      <description>Morning Digest | Mallikarjun Kharge to officially take charge as Congress president today; UNSC members to pay tributes at Mumbai 26/11 memorial on Friday, and more A select list of stories to read before you start your day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google parent Alphabet&#39;s profits fall short at $14 billion</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-parent-alphabets-profits-fall-short-at-14-billion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 02:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/google-parent-alphabets-profits-fall-short-at-14-billion/</guid>
      <description>Google parent Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s profits fall short at $14 billion Alphabet said it made a profit of $14 billion in the third quarter on ad revenue that grew just 6 percent to $69 billion when compared with the same period of last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rishi Sunak Becomes UK Prime Minister — He Wants to Make Britain a Global Crypto Investment Hub</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rishi-sunak-becomes-uk-prime-minister-he-wants-to-make-britain-a-global/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 02:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rishi-sunak-becomes-uk-prime-minister-he-wants-to-make-britain-a-global/</guid>
      <description>Rishi Sunak Becomes UK Prime Minister — He Wants to Make Britain a Global Crypto Investment Hub Britain’s former Chancellor of the Exchequer Rishi Sunak has become the country’s new prime minister, succeeding Liz Truss who resigned after 44 days in office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen: US Financial Stability Risks Could Materialize, Cites ‘Dangerous and Volatile Environment’</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/treasury-secretary-janet-yellen-us-financial-stability-risks-could-materia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/treasury-secretary-janet-yellen-us-financial-stability-risks-could-materia/</guid>
      <description>Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen: US Financial Stability Risks Could Materialize, Cites ‘Dangerous and Volatile Environment’ Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen has warned that financial stability risks could materialize in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro Stalls In Polls After Ally Clashes With Police</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bolsonaro-stalls-in-polls-after-ally-clashes-with-police/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bolsonaro-stalls-in-polls-after-ally-clashes-with-police/</guid>
      <description>Bolsonaro Stalls In Polls After Ally Clashes With Police Leftist challenger Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva, 76, would take 54% of valid votes, which exclude null and blank ballots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ye’s Antisemitic Rants Wreck Path To Multibillion-Dollar Fortune</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/yes-antisemitic-rants-wreck-path-to-multibillion-dollar-fortune/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/yes-antisemitic-rants-wreck-path-to-multibillion-dollar-fortune/</guid>
      <description>Ye’s Antisemitic Rants Wreck Path To Multibillion-Dollar Fortune The rapper lost out on a lucrative deal with Adidas, which said it would end the Yeezy line after facing blowback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine Says Russia Is Deliberately Delaying UN-Brokered Grain Shipments</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ukraine-says-russia-is-deliberately-delaying-un-brokered-grain-shipments/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ukraine-says-russia-is-deliberately-delaying-un-brokered-grain-shipments/</guid>
      <description>Ukraine Says Russia Is Deliberately Delaying UN-Brokered Grain Shipments Kyiv has accused Russia of delaying more than 165 cargo ships heading to Ukrainian Black Sea ports to load up with grain under a deal brokered by the United Nations and Turkey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Utkarsh Small Finance Bank gets Sebi&#39;s go ahead to float Rs 500-crore IPO</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/utkarsh-small-finance-bank-gets-sebis-go-ahead-to-float-rs-500-crore-ipo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/utkarsh-small-finance-bank-gets-sebis-go-ahead-to-float-rs-500-crore-ipo/</guid>
      <description>Utkarsh Small Finance Bank gets Sebi&amp;rsquo;s go ahead to float Rs 500-crore IPO The lender may consider issue of securities aggregating up to Rs 100 crore in a pre-IPO placement round</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diwali&#39;s impact on economy: Retail business may cross 1.5 lakh crore, gold sales 20% higher</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/diwalis-impact-on-economy-retail-business-may-cross-15-lakh-crore-gold-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/diwalis-impact-on-economy-retail-business-may-cross-15-lakh-crore-gold-/</guid>
      <description>Diwali&amp;rsquo;s impact on economy: Retail business may cross 1.5 lakh crore, gold sales 20% higher As India celebrates the festive season of Diwali, take a look at its impact on the economy of the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rising Sea Levels Spell Disaster For America’s Coastal Nuclear Plants</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rising-sea-levels-spell-disaster-for-americas-coastal-nuclear-plants/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rising-sea-levels-spell-disaster-for-americas-coastal-nuclear-plants/</guid>
      <description>Rising Sea Levels Spell Disaster For America’s Coastal Nuclear Plants It’s easy to forget that the United States is the largest nuclear power producer in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Ground-Breaking Milestone&#39;: World Leaders On Sunak Becoming U.K. PM</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ground-breaking-milestone-world-leaders-on-sunak-becoming-uk-pm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 16:46:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ground-breaking-milestone-world-leaders-on-sunak-becoming-uk-pm/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;Ground-Breaking Milestone&amp;rsquo;: World Leaders On Sunak Becoming U.K. PM Sunak is the third U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEBI Fines Six Entities In Deutsche Mutual Fund Front-Running Case</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sebi-fines-six-entities-in-deutsche-mutual-fund-front-running-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 16:42:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sebi-fines-six-entities-in-deutsche-mutual-fund-front-running-case/</guid>
      <description>SEBI Fines Six Entities In Deutsche Mutual Fund Front-Running Case SEBI noted that the noticees cannot be absolved absolutely for their &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Did Terra Luna Crash? Understand How UST And LUNA Lost All Value</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/why-did-terra-luna-crash-understand-how-ust-and-luna-lost-all-value/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 16:04:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/why-did-terra-luna-crash-understand-how-ust-and-luna-lost-all-value/</guid>
      <description>Why Did Terra Luna Crash? Understand How UST And LUNA Lost All Value Let’s try and understand why this popular coin lost all of its value in just a few days</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Minister Says Sour Relations With The U.S. Will Improve</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/saudi-minister-says-sour-relations-with-the-us-will-improve/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/saudi-minister-says-sour-relations-with-the-us-will-improve/</guid>
      <description>Saudi Minister Says Sour Relations With The U.S. Will Improve The United States and Saudi Arabia will overcome the recent rift in relations created by the OPEC+ group’s decision to reduce its oil production target by the most since 2020, according to Saudi Arabia’s Investment Minister Khalid al-Falih.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brand new Skoda Slavia replaced for FREE, automaker receives praises from sedan owner</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/brand-new-skoda-slavia-replaced-for-free-automaker-receives-praises-from-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/brand-new-skoda-slavia-replaced-for-free-automaker-receives-praises-from-s/</guid>
      <description>Brand new Skoda Slavia replaced for FREE, automaker receives praises from sedan owner Soon after a brand new Skoda Slavia caught fire while being parked, the Czech automaker delivered a brand new car to the aggrieved customer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Over 25 crore e-KYC transactions carried out using Aadhaar in September</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/over-25-crore-e-kyc-transactions-carried-out-using-aadhaar-in-september/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/over-25-crore-e-kyc-transactions-carried-out-using-aadhaar-in-september/</guid>
      <description>Over 25 crore e-KYC transactions carried out using Aadhaar in September In September, 175.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunak’s ‘Dullness Dividend’ Might Not Last</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sunaks-dullness-dividend-might-not-last/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sunaks-dullness-dividend-might-not-last/</guid>
      <description>Sunak’s ‘Dullness Dividend’ Might Not Last Britain’s new prime minister is an improvement over his predecessors — but keeping his promises won’t be easy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Want to know about income of UK Prime Minister Rishi Sunak&#39;s wife Akshata? Check THIS</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/want-to-know-about-income-of-uk-prime-minister-rishi-sunaks-wife-akshata-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/want-to-know-about-income-of-uk-prime-minister-rishi-sunaks-wife-akshata-/</guid>
      <description>Want to know about income of UK Prime Minister Rishi Sunak&amp;rsquo;s wife Akshata?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Texas Natural Gas Prices Go Negative</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/texas-natural-gas-prices-go-negative/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/texas-natural-gas-prices-go-negative/</guid>
      <description>Texas Natural Gas Prices Go Negative Yesterday, Waha natural gas sank to near zero levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Too Much Gas. Europe’s Energy Crisis Takes A Surprise Turn</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/too-much-gas-europes-energy-crisis-takes-a-surprise-turn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 14:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/too-much-gas-europes-energy-crisis-takes-a-surprise-turn/</guid>
      <description>Too Much Gas. Europe’s Energy Crisis Takes A Surprise Turn Europe suddenly has more gas than it can use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World is in its &#39;first truly global energy crisis:&#39; IEA&#39;s Birol</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/world-is-in-its-first-truly-global-energy-crisis-ieas-birol/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 14:44:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/world-is-in-its-first-truly-global-energy-crisis-ieas-birol/</guid>
      <description>World is in its &amp;lsquo;first truly global energy crisis:&amp;rsquo; IEA&amp;rsquo;s Birol Soaring global prices across a number of energy sources, including oil, natural gas and coal, are hammering consumers at the same time they are already dealing with rising food and services inflation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>‘India’s exports to China rising faster than imports’</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indias-exports-to-china-rising-faster-than-imports/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 14:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indias-exports-to-china-rising-faster-than-imports/</guid>
      <description>‘India’s exports to China rising faster than imports’ India’s trade equation with China has been improving in recent years with outbound shipments rising faster than imports, whose growth is being driven largely by vital raw materials or to meet demand from high-growth sectors such as telecom and power, a senior government official said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canara Bank customers ATTENTION! Bank offers up to 7.71% return on THIS fixed deposit; Check return calculator</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/canara-bank-customers-attention-bank-offers-up-to-771-return-on-this-fix/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/canara-bank-customers-attention-bank-offers-up-to-771-return-on-this-fix/</guid>
      <description>Canara Bank customers ATTENTION! Bank offers up to 7.71% return on THIS fixed deposit; Check return calculator Canara Bank customers can now earn a better return on fixed deposits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian Railways to set up four more &#39;Restaurant on Wheels&#39; in THESE cities of Maharashtra</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indian-railways-to-set-up-four-more-restaurant-on-wheels-in-these-cities-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indian-railways-to-set-up-four-more-restaurant-on-wheels-in-these-cities-/</guid>
      <description>Indian Railways to set up four more &amp;lsquo;Restaurant on Wheels&amp;rsquo; in THESE cities of Maharashtra To give passengers a unique experience, Indian Railways is planning to set up four more &#39;Restaurant on Wheels&#39; in THESE cities og Maharashtra, reports PTI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rishi Sunak&#39;s Wife Earned Rs 126.6 Crore Dividend From Infosys In 2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rishi-sunaks-wife-earned-rs-1266-crore-dividend-from-infosys-in-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:44:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rishi-sunaks-wife-earned-rs-1266-crore-dividend-from-infosys-in-2022/</guid>
      <description>Rishi Sunak&amp;rsquo;s Wife Earned Rs 126.6 Crore Dividend From Infosys In 2022 Akshata Murty, wife of Britain&#39;s incoming Prime Minister Rishi Sunak, earned Rs 126.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How many Infosys shares Rishi Sunak&#39;s wife Akshata has and how much dividend she earned</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-many-infosys-shares-rishi-sunaks-wife-akshata-has-and-how-much-dividen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/how-many-infosys-shares-rishi-sunaks-wife-akshata-has-and-how-much-dividen/</guid>
      <description>How many Infosys shares Rishi Sunak&amp;rsquo;s wife Akshata has and how much dividend she earned Rishi Sunak&#39;s wife Akshata Murthy earned over ₹125 crore as dividend income from Infosys this year</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devastated to lose my husband: Biocon founder Kiran Mazumdar-Shaw</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/devastated-to-lose-my-husband-biocon-founder-kiran-mazumdar-shaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/devastated-to-lose-my-husband-biocon-founder-kiran-mazumdar-shaw/</guid>
      <description>Devastated to lose my husband: Biocon founder Kiran Mazumdar-Shaw Bengaluru, October 25Biocon founder Kiran Mazumdar-Shaw said she was devastated to lose her husband and will miss him profoundly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delhi Residents Defy Diwali Firecracker Ban, Pollution Spikes</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/delhi-residents-defy-diwali-firecracker-ban-pollution-spikes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:39:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/delhi-residents-defy-diwali-firecracker-ban-pollution-spikes/</guid>
      <description>Delhi Residents Defy Diwali Firecracker Ban, Pollution Spikes Many residents of New Delhi defied a firecracker ban as political parties traded blame on who was responsible for the Indian capital&#39;s foul air.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tata Steel Signs MOU To Supply Ford With Green Steel</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tata-steel-signs-mou-to-supply-ford-with-green-steel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tata-steel-signs-mou-to-supply-ford-with-green-steel/</guid>
      <description>Tata Steel Signs MOU To Supply Ford With Green Steel Tata Steel&#39;s Dutch arm plans to supply Ford plants in Europe with &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Report: Billionaire Says Britain May Be Forced to Seek Bailout From IMF if It Does Not Renegotiate Brexit Deal</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/report-billionaire-says-britain-may-be-forced-to-seek-bailout-from-imf-if-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/report-billionaire-says-britain-may-be-forced-to-seek-bailout-from-imf-if-/</guid>
      <description>Report: Billionaire Says Britain May Be Forced to Seek Bailout From IMF if It Does Not Renegotiate Brexit Deal British billionaire investor Guy Hands has reckoned that Britain will become “the sick man of Europe” and may be forced to seek a bailout from the International Monetary Fund (IMF) if it does not renegotiate its Brexit deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toyota To Produce Electric Car Powered By BYD Batteries In China</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/toyota-to-produce-electric-car-powered-by-byd-batteries-in-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/toyota-to-produce-electric-car-powered-by-byd-batteries-in-china/</guid>
      <description>Toyota To Produce Electric Car Powered By BYD Batteries In China Toyota announced the launch of a small electric sedan, which will be powered by BYD batteries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp Outage: Users Unable To Send Or Receive Messages</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-outage-users-unable-to-send-or-receive-messages/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/whatsapp-outage-users-unable-to-send-or-receive-messages/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp Outage: Users Unable To Send Or Receive Messages The world&#39;s largest messaging service, WhatsApp, is facing an outage with several users unable to send or receive messages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IEA: The World Needs Russian Oil To Flow Regardless Of The Price Cap</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/iea-the-world-needs-russian-oil-to-flow-regardless-of-the-price-cap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/iea-the-world-needs-russian-oil-to-flow-regardless-of-the-price-cap/</guid>
      <description>IEA: The World Needs Russian Oil To Flow Regardless Of The Price Cap The global oil market will still need Russian oil to flow even with the planned price cap, Fatih Birol, the Executive Director of the International Energy Agency (IEA), said on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank Strike: Banking services across India to get affected on November 19 amidst nationwide protests</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bank-strike-banking-services-across-india-to-get-affected-on-november-19-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bank-strike-banking-services-across-india-to-get-affected-on-november-19-a/</guid>
      <description>Bank Strike: Banking services across India to get affected on November 19 amidst nationwide protests The members will strike work in protest against targeted victimisation of bankers for being active in the union.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samvat 2079: What Market Experts Make Of The Year Ahead</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samvat-2079-what-market-experts-make-of-the-year-ahead/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 01:44:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/samvat-2079-what-market-experts-make-of-the-year-ahead/</guid>
      <description>Samvat 2079: What Market Experts Make Of The Year Ahead While risks remain amid geopolitical strife and liquidity tightening, Indian markets are expected to fare well in Samvat 2079.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Stock Picks For Samvat 2079: Brokerages</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/top-stock-picks-for-samvat-2079-brokerages/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 01:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/top-stock-picks-for-samvat-2079-brokerages/</guid>
      <description>Top Stock Picks For Samvat 2079: Brokerages Here’s a list of top Diwali stock picks by brokerages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JPMorgan Chase President: Fed Isn’t Too Hawkish and Crypto Is ‘Kind of Irrelevant’</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/jpmorgan-chase-president-fed-isnt-too-hawkish-and-crypto-is-kind-of-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 01:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/jpmorgan-chase-president-fed-isnt-too-hawkish-and-crypto-is-kind-of-/</guid>
      <description>JPMorgan Chase President: Fed Isn’t Too Hawkish and Crypto Is ‘Kind of Irrelevant’ JPMorgan Chase’s president that crypto “is kind of irrelevant in the scheme of things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sensex makes biggest Muhurat gain in 14 years</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sensex-makes-biggest-muhurat-gain-in-14-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 01:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sensex-makes-biggest-muhurat-gain-in-14-years/</guid>
      <description>Sensex makes biggest Muhurat gain in 14 years Boosted by strong buying in banking and financial stocks, the sensex gained 525 points, or nearly 1%, to end at 59,832 during Monday’s special hour-long Muhurat trading session on the BSE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia Warns Europe: Natural Gas Price Cap Means Full Supply Cut-Off</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/russia-warns-europe-natural-gas-price-cap-means-full-supply-cut-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/russia-warns-europe-natural-gas-price-cap-means-full-supply-cut-off/</guid>
      <description>Russia Warns Europe: Natural Gas Price Cap Means Full Supply Cut-Off As Europe heads into winter, the threat of sharply rising gas prices and sustained supply failures increases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hope floats for stalled India-UK trade deal</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hope-floats-for-stalled-india-uk-trade-deal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 23:46:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hope-floats-for-stalled-india-uk-trade-deal/</guid>
      <description>Hope floats for stalled India-UK trade deal Choosing Sunak as PM will give a much-needed boost to UK-India ties and might unblock the stalled bilateral trade deal which was meant to have been signed by Diwali.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IRS Updates Crypto-Related Instructions for 2022 Tax Filing</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/irs-updates-crypto-related-instructions-for-2022-tax-filing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 23:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/irs-updates-crypto-related-instructions-for-2022-tax-filing/</guid>
      <description>IRS Updates Crypto-Related Instructions for 2022 Tax Filing The Internal Revenue Service (IRS) has updated the crypto section in the 2022 draft instructions for tax form 1040.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Biden Wants To Release More Oil From The SPR</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/why-biden-wants-to-release-more-oil-from-the-spr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/why-biden-wants-to-release-more-oil-from-the-spr/</guid>
      <description>Why Biden Wants To Release More Oil From The SPR Last week, the White House caused a splash by announcing that President Biden was ready to release more crude from the strategic petroleum reserve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK bonds see record gain with Sunak as PM</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/uk-bonds-see-record-gain-with-sunak-as-pm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 22:35:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/uk-bonds-see-record-gain-with-sunak-as-pm/</guid>
      <description>UK bonds see record gain with Sunak as PM The pound rallied off session lows on Monday and gilts bounced, as former chancellor Rishi Sunak won the premiership race, giving investors a greater sense of confidence in the robustness of Britain&#39;s finances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Americans See Another 10-Cent Drop In Gasoline Prices</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/americans-see-another-10-cent-drop-in-gasoline-prices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/americans-see-another-10-cent-drop-in-gasoline-prices/</guid>
      <description>Americans See Another 10-Cent Drop In Gasoline Prices Prices at the gas pump have declined 10 cents in a week, according to AAA, which says recession fears and further releases of America’s strategic petroleum reserve (SPR) have contributed to the further declines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World’s Top Oilfield Service Provider Schlumberger Rebrands To SLB</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/worlds-top-oilfield-service-provider-schlumberger-rebrands-to-slb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/worlds-top-oilfield-service-provider-schlumberger-rebrands-to-slb/</guid>
      <description>World’s Top Oilfield Service Provider Schlumberger Rebrands To SLB Schlumberger (NYSE: SLB) is known as of Monday under its new name—SLB—to reflect its transformation from an oilfield services provider to a global technology company helping the energy transition, the world’s largest oilfield services provider said in a statement today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oil Tanker Market In Disarray As EU Ban On Russian Crude Nears</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oil-tanker-market-in-disarray-as-eu-ban-on-russian-crude-nears/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oil-tanker-market-in-disarray-as-eu-ban-on-russian-crude-nears/</guid>
      <description>Oil Tanker Market In Disarray As EU Ban On Russian Crude Nears Six weeks before the EU embargo on Russian crude oil exports and the planned price cap on Russian oil enters into force, the global tanker and oil markets face increased uncertainty over who will ship Russia’s oil—and how—as of December 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rishi Sunak Is A New And Old-Fashioned Tory</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rishi-sunak-is-a-new-and-old-fashioned-tory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rishi-sunak-is-a-new-and-old-fashioned-tory/</guid>
      <description>Rishi Sunak Is A New And Old-Fashioned Tory The next UK prime minister is a fascinating mix of the new and the old in the world of the ruling Conservative Party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Muhurat trading: Samvat 2079 begins on an auspicious note</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/muhurat-trading-samvat-2079-begins-on-an-auspicious-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:38:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/muhurat-trading-samvat-2079-begins-on-an-auspicious-note/</guid>
      <description>Muhurat trading: Samvat 2079 begins on an auspicious note Equity indices began Samvat 2079 on a positive note on Monday with both sensex and Nifty registering gains across all sectors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rishi Sunak Tells UK Tories To Unite As He Strives To Fix ‘Crisis’</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rishi-sunak-tells-uk-tories-to-unite-as-he-strives-to-fix-crisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rishi-sunak-tells-uk-tories-to-unite-as-he-strives-to-fix-crisis/</guid>
      <description>Rishi Sunak Tells UK Tories To Unite As He Strives To Fix ‘Crisis’ Rishi Sunak called on his warring Conservative Party to unite as the UK’s incoming prime minister bids to fix the crisis facing the economy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Attacks On Energy Infrastructure Leave Millions Of Ukrainians Without Power</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-attacks-on-energy-infrastructure-leave-millions-of-ukrainians-without-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-attacks-on-energy-infrastructure-leave-millions-of-ukrainians-without-p/</guid>
      <description>New Attacks On Energy Infrastructure Leave Millions Of Ukrainians Without Power Russia has launched new, “wide-scale” missile strikes on Ukraine’s civilian energy sites, causing power outages nationwide, Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskiy said in his regular video address late on October 22.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold Price on Diwali: Check 22-carat yellow metal rate before buying today</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-price-on-diwali-check-22-carat-yellow-metal-rate-before-buying-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 06:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-price-on-diwali-check-22-carat-yellow-metal-rate-before-buying-today/</guid>
      <description>Gold Price on Diwali: Check 22-carat yellow metal rate before buying today Prices for 24-carat gold in the national capital Delhi increased to Rs 50,510 per 10 grams while 22-carat gold or ornamental gold was priced at Rs 48,100 per ten grams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>German Gas Giant Makes Headquarters Smaller And Colder To Save Energy</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/german-gas-giant-makes-headquarters-smaller-and-colder-to-save-energy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 05:58:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/german-gas-giant-makes-headquarters-smaller-and-colder-to-save-energy/</guid>
      <description>German Gas Giant Makes Headquarters Smaller And Colder To Save Energy Germany’s gas major Uniper will reduce the use of office space at its headquarters by half and maintain lower temperatures in the space remaining in use, German media reported, as quoted by Reuters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Presents Digital Currency Prototype, Project Aurum</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hong-kong-presents-digital-currency-prototype-project-aurum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 05:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hong-kong-presents-digital-currency-prototype-project-aurum/</guid>
      <description>Hong Kong Presents Digital Currency Prototype, Project Aurum Financial authorities in Hong Kong have unveiled a prototype of the Chinese autonomous territory’s own central bank digital currency called Project Aurum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LBank Exchange Will List VNX Gold (VNXAU) on October 25, 2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/lbank-exchange-will-list-vnx-gold-vnxau-on-october-25-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 05:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/lbank-exchange-will-list-vnx-gold-vnxau-on-october-25-2022/</guid>
      <description>LBank Exchange Will List VNX Gold (VNXAU) on October 25, 2022 PRESS RELEASE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petrol and diesel prices today in Hyderabad, Delhi, Chennai and Mumbai on 24 October 2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-and-diesel-prices-today-in-hyderabad-delhi-chennai-and-mumbai-on-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 04:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-and-diesel-prices-today-in-hyderabad-delhi-chennai-and-mumbai-on-2/</guid>
      <description>Petrol and diesel prices today in Hyderabad, Delhi, Chennai and Mumbai on 24 October 2022 Petrol and Diesel prices today, 24 October 2022: Petrol price in Hyderabad is Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Muhurat Trading 2022: Historic Sensex Performances on Muhurat Trading Day</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/muhurat-trading-2022-historic-sensex-performances-on-muhurat-trading-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 04:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/muhurat-trading-2022-historic-sensex-performances-on-muhurat-trading-day/</guid>
      <description>Muhurat Trading 2022: Historic Sensex Performances on Muhurat Trading Day Muhurat trading is a popular tradition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunak Edges Closer to UK Leadership Prize As Johnson Caves</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sunak-edges-closer-to-uk-leadership-prize-as-johnson-caves/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 04:49:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sunak-edges-closer-to-uk-leadership-prize-as-johnson-caves/</guid>
      <description>Sunak Edges Closer to UK Leadership Prize As Johnson Caves Boris Johnson pulled out of the race to lead the UK’s ruling Conservative Party and the nation, ending a bid to replace Liz Truss as prime minister.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Striking Benefits Of EHR Software For Healthcare Organizations</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/striking-benefits-of-ehr-software-for-healthcare-organizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 04:46:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/striking-benefits-of-ehr-software-for-healthcare-organizations/</guid>
      <description>Striking Benefits Of EHR Software For Healthcare Organizations Digitizing data is the key to more efficient patient treatment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold rates today in Delhi, Chennai, Kolkata, Mumbai - 24 October 2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-rates-today-in-delhi-chennai-kolkata-mumbai-24-october-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 04:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-rates-today-in-delhi-chennai-kolkata-mumbai-24-october-2022/</guid>
      <description>Gold rates today in Delhi, Chennai, Kolkata, Mumbai - 24 October 2022 Gold rates today, 24 October 2022: Gold rates in Delhi per 10 grams of 22 carats is at Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diwali 2022: MASSIVE crowd witnessed at Anand Vihar bus stand and metro stations due to festivities</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/diwali-2022-massive-crowd-witnessed-at-anand-vihar-bus-stand-and-metro-sta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 04:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/diwali-2022-massive-crowd-witnessed-at-anand-vihar-bus-stand-and-metro-sta/</guid>
      <description>Diwali 2022: MASSIVE crowd witnessed at Anand Vihar bus stand and metro stations due to festivities Diwali 2022: Heavy crowd gathered at Anand Vihar bus stand and metro station to travel home ahead of festivities, reports ANI.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
