<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Telangana on TechnoStreet</title>
    <link>https://technostreet.github.io/tags/telangana/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Telangana on TechnoStreet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 14:32:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://technostreet.github.io/tags/telangana/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>With record recruitment drives, 2022 ushered in new hope for Telangana’s youth</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/with-record-recruitment-drives-2022-ushered-in-new-hope-for-telanganas-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 14:32:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/with-record-recruitment-drives-2022-ushered-in-new-hope-for-telanganas-/</guid>
      <description>With record recruitment drives, 2022 ushered in new hope for Telangana’s youth The Year 2022 would be remembered for a long time to come as it ushered in a new hope for the unemployed youth and government job aspirants</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Young writer, once a catering steward, now has his poems taught in universities</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/young-writer-once-a-catering-steward-now-has-his-poems-taught-in-universi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 16:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/young-writer-once-a-catering-steward-now-has-his-poems-taught-in-universi/</guid>
      <description>Young writer, once a catering steward, now has his poems taught in universities Ramesh Karthik, who used to work as a steward in catering events to earn some money to publish his books, has been writing on the culture and lifestyle of Banjara communities, adding a dash of fiction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confusion over Saudi Tourist visa rules: Many Indians land in trouble</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/confusion-over-saudi-tourist-visa-rules-many-indians-land-in-trouble/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 16:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/confusion-over-saudi-tourist-visa-rules-many-indians-land-in-trouble/</guid>
      <description>Confusion over Saudi Tourist visa rules: Many Indians land in trouble The multiple-entry tourist visa is valid for one year from the date of issuance, and the permissible period of stay is 90 days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telangana: District Academic Task Force on FLN kept on hold</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/telangana-district-academic-task-force-on-fln-kept-on-hold/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 15:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/telangana-district-academic-task-force-on-fln-kept-on-hold/</guid>
      <description>Telangana: District Academic Task Force on FLN kept on hold The orders issued constituting the DATF on FLN were kept on hold due to administrative reasons</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telangana best among other Indian states in organ donation: Harish Rao</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/telangana-best-among-other-indian-states-in-organ-donation-harish-rao/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 13:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/telangana-best-among-other-indian-states-in-organ-donation-harish-rao/</guid>
      <description>Telangana best among other Indian states in organ donation: Harish Rao State government will use choppers to transport donated organs of the brain dead patients from districts hospitals to teaching hospitals</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSCHE to hold conclave on employability in Hyderabad on Nov 21</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tsche-to-hold-conclave-on-employability-in-hyderabad-on-nov-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 15:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tsche-to-hold-conclave-on-employability-in-hyderabad-on-nov-21/</guid>
      <description>TSCHE to hold conclave on employability in Hyderabad on Nov 21 State-level conclave on ‘Empowering Education to Augment Employability’ at Taj Deccan here on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telangana: Concern voiced over BJP’s misuse of central agencies</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/telangana-concern-voiced-over-bjps-misuse-of-central-agencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 13:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/telangana-concern-voiced-over-bjps-misuse-of-central-agencies/</guid>
      <description>Telangana: Concern voiced over BJP’s misuse of central agencies Nalgonda: Leaders of different organizations have in a single voice expressed strong concern over the misuse of central agencies including the Enforcement Directorate (ED) and the Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI) by the BJP government to target opposition parties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human killings by tigers in Adilabad trigger fake videos on social media</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/human-killings-by-tigers-in-adilabad-trigger-fake-videos-on-social-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 06:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/human-killings-by-tigers-in-adilabad-trigger-fake-videos-on-social-media/</guid>
      <description>Human killings by tigers in Adilabad trigger fake videos on social media A video of a tiger resting calmly on a tarred road was shared widely in WhatsApp groups on Wednesday and Thursday, triggering panic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telangana: Over 8.93 lakh tonnes paddy procured for Vaanakalam season</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/telangana-over-893-lakh-tonnes-paddy-procured-for-vaanakalam-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 16:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/telangana-over-893-lakh-tonnes-paddy-procured-for-vaanakalam-season/</guid>
      <description>Telangana: Over 8.93 lakh tonnes paddy procured for Vaanakalam season The paddy procurement for Vaanakalam (Kharif) season is being undertaken at a brisk pace, with around 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pressure mine planted by Maoists explodes, injures a cow in Kothagudem</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/pressure-mine-planted-by-maoists-explodes-injures-a-cow-in-kothagudem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 16:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/pressure-mine-planted-by-maoists-explodes-injures-a-cow-in-kothagudem/</guid>
      <description>Pressure mine planted by Maoists explodes, injures a cow in Kothagudem Cherla police, Kothagudem special party personnel and bomb disposal team found two more pressure mines at the incident site and defused them on the spot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women Safety Wing of Telangana police invites applications for various posts on contract basis</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/women-safety-wing-of-telangana-police-invites-applications-for-various-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 07:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/women-safety-wing-of-telangana-police-invites-applications-for-various-post/</guid>
      <description>Women Safety Wing of Telangana police invites applications for various posts on contract basis Hyderabad: Telangana police Women Safety Wing is inviting applications from eligible candidates for different posts on a contractual basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kothagudem: CI extends financial support to ailing man</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/kothagudem-ci-extends-financial-support-to-ailing-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/kothagudem-ci-extends-financial-support-to-ailing-man/</guid>
      <description>Kothagudem: CI extends financial support to ailing man Yellandu Inspector of Police, Banoth Raju extended financial assistance to an ailing private worker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BJP MP Laxman doesn’t see early polls in Telangana</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bjp-mp-laxman-doesnt-see-early-polls-in-telangana/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bjp-mp-laxman-doesnt-see-early-polls-in-telangana/</guid>
      <description>BJP MP Laxman doesn’t see early polls in Telangana Speaking at a Meet the Press programme at the Press Club at Somajiguda here, Laxman stated that even if the Chief Minister dissolves the state assembly, there is very less possibility of conducting early polls, as the entire decision lies with the Election Commission.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traffic diversions in view of Bharath Jodo Yatra in Telangana</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/traffic-diversions-in-view-of-bharath-jodo-yatra-in-telangana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:47:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/traffic-diversions-in-view-of-bharath-jodo-yatra-in-telangana/</guid>
      <description>Traffic diversions in view of Bharath Jodo Yatra in Telangana The Cyberabad traffic police in view of the &#39;Bharath Jodo Yatra&#39; have announced certain traffic diversions for four days starting Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
