<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Top Headlines on TechnoStreet</title>
    <link>https://technostreet.github.io/tags/top-headlines/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Top Headlines on TechnoStreet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 04:37:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://technostreet.github.io/tags/top-headlines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CM Himanta Biswa Sarma stresses need for Assam Medical College upgradation</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cm-himanta-biswa-sarma-stresses-need-for-assam-medical-college-upgradation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 04:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cm-himanta-biswa-sarma-stresses-need-for-assam-medical-college-upgradation/</guid>
      <description>CM Himanta Biswa Sarma stresses need for Assam Medical College upgradation Assam CM Himanta Biswa Sarma has said that the state government is keen to transform the Assam Medical College</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CM Himanta: Administrative efficiency is key to delivery of public services</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cm-himanta-administrative-efficiency-is-key-to-delivery-of-public-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 02:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cm-himanta-administrative-efficiency-is-key-to-delivery-of-public-services/</guid>
      <description>CM Himanta: Administrative efficiency is key to delivery of public services CM Himanta Biswa Sarma reminded the deputy commissioners and the superintendents of police that administrative efficiency is the key to ensuring the delivery of public services and work towards that end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NHIDCL to develop jet landing facility on bypass in Assam</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nhidcl-to-develop-jet-landing-facility-on-bypass-in-assam/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 02:52:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nhidcl-to-develop-jet-landing-facility-on-bypass-in-assam/</guid>
      <description>NHIDCL to develop jet landing facility on bypass in Assam In a first of its kind in Assam, NHIDCL will develop a 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyber fraudsters target pensioners: Ministry of Finance</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cyber-fraudsters-target-pensioners-ministry-of-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 02:52:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cyber-fraudsters-target-pensioners-ministry-of-finance/</guid>
      <description>Cyber fraudsters target pensioners: Ministry of Finance Cyber fraudsters have found a new way to target innocent people and cheat them of their hard-earned money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northeast has potential to be country&#39;s organic food basket: President Droupadi Murmu</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/northeast-has-potential-to-be-countrys-organic-food-basket-president-drou/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 02:51:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/northeast-has-potential-to-be-countrys-organic-food-basket-president-drou/</guid>
      <description>Northeast has potential to be country&amp;rsquo;s organic food basket: President Droupadi Murmu President Droupadi Murmu said that the entire northeast region has the potential to become the organic food basket of the country as the good quality agro and horticultural produce of Nagaland has great demand in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sexual assault under POCSO can&#39;t be attributed in mutual love: Meghalaya High Court</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sexual-assault-under-pocso-cant-be-attributed-in-mutual-love-meghalaya-hi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 02:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sexual-assault-under-pocso-cant-be-attributed-in-mutual-love-meghalaya-hi/</guid>
      <description>Sexual assault under POCSO can&amp;rsquo;t be attributed in mutual love: Meghalaya High Court The Meghalaya High Court has held that “sexual assault” under the Protection of Children from Sexual Offences (POCSO) Act cannot be attributed to an act where there is mutual love and affection between a young boyfriend and girlfriend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 28 violence damaging for Meghalaya&#39;s economy: Tourism body</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/october-28-violence-damaging-for-meghalayas-economy-tourism-body/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 02:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/october-28-violence-damaging-for-meghalayas-economy-tourism-body/</guid>
      <description>October 28 violence damaging for Meghalaya&amp;rsquo;s economy: Tourism body MTDF said that the October 28 rally which turned violent in Shillong created an atmosphere that might potentially damage the states economy and hamper job creation and growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily food items that can be helpful in improving eyesight</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/daily-food-items-that-can-be-helpful-in-improving-eyesight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 03:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/daily-food-items-that-can-be-helpful-in-improving-eyesight/</guid>
      <description>Daily food items that can be helpful in improving eyesight In order to have a healthy set of eyes you need to have eating habits that can improve eye problems while improving vision as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Bangladeshis deported via Sutarkandi border in Karimganj district</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/8-bangladeshis-deported-via-sutarkandi-border-in-karimganj-district/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 03:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/8-bangladeshis-deported-via-sutarkandi-border-in-karimganj-district/</guid>
      <description>8 Bangladeshis deported via Sutarkandi border in Karimganj district They were arrested from different parts of Assam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Chintan Shivir&#39;: PM Narendra Modi urges states to learn from each other</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/chintan-shivir-pm-narendra-modi-urges-states-to-learn-from-each-other/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 02:34:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/chintan-shivir-pm-narendra-modi-urges-states-to-learn-from-each-other/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;Chintan Shivir&amp;rsquo;: PM Narendra Modi urges states to learn from each other PM Narendra Modi on Friday advised all the states and the Union Territories to learn and take inspiration from each other and work for the betterment of the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 still evading arrest in GMC de-siltation scam</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/3-still-evading-arrest-in-gmc-de-siltation-scam/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 02:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/3-still-evading-arrest-in-gmc-de-siltation-scam/</guid>
      <description>3 still evading arrest in GMC de-siltation scam The Chief Minister’s Special Vigilance Cell doubts that two of the three accused evading arrest in the GMC de-siltation scam might have fled the state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CCI slaps Rs 935 crore fine on Google, 2nd penalty in a week</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cci-slaps-rs-935-crore-fine-on-google-2nd-penalty-in-a-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 02:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cci-slaps-rs-935-crore-fine-on-google-2nd-penalty-in-a-week/</guid>
      <description>CCI slaps Rs 935 crore fine on Google, 2nd penalty in a week CCI slapped its second penalty on Google within a week this time to the tune of around $113 million (Rs 936 crore) for abusing its dominant position with respect to its Play Store policies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ayurveda recognized as traditional medicines in more than 30 countries: Mahendra Munjpara</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ayurveda-recognized-as-traditional-medicines-in-more-than-30-countries-mah/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 02:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ayurveda-recognized-as-traditional-medicines-in-more-than-30-countries-mah/</guid>
      <description>Ayurveda recognized as traditional medicines in more than 30 countries: Mahendra Munjpara Ayurveda is currently recognized as a traditional medicine in more than 30 countries and its acceptance is fast increasing globally, said Mahendra Munjpara</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rishi Sunak becomes first Indian-origin Prime Minister of UK</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rishi-sunak-becomes-first-indian-origin-prime-minister-of-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 02:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rishi-sunak-becomes-first-indian-origin-prime-minister-of-uk/</guid>
      <description>Rishi Sunak becomes first Indian-origin Prime Minister of UK Britain&#39;s Conservative Party leader Rishi Sunak becomes the first Indian-origin and Hindu Prime Minister of the United Kingdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court sets aside high court order granting bail to accused arrested with morphine</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/supreme-court-sets-aside-high-court-order-granting-bail-to-accused-arrested/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 02:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/supreme-court-sets-aside-high-court-order-granting-bail-to-accused-arrested/</guid>
      <description>Supreme Court sets aside high court order granting bail to accused arrested with morphine The Supreme Court has set aside a Gauhati High Court order which granted bail to two men, accused of possessing about 13 kg of morphine in a motor vehicle.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
