<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics on TechnoStreet</title>
    <link>https://technostreet.github.io/tags/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics on TechnoStreet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 04:49:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://technostreet.github.io/tags/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>With Rahul, Kejriwal As Modi Challengers, Hindutva, UCC BJP&#39;s Trump Cards, 2023 Will Be A Build-Up Year</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/with-rahul-kejriwal-as-modi-challengers-hindutva-ucc-bjps-trump-cards-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 04:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/with-rahul-kejriwal-as-modi-challengers-hindutva-ucc-bjps-trump-cards-/</guid>
      <description>With Rahul, Kejriwal As Modi Challengers, Hindutva, UCC BJP&amp;rsquo;s Trump Cards, 2023 Will Be A Build-Up Year Congress is trying to improve its ‘product’ to make it acceptable but there is another challenger on the horizon in Arvind Kejriwal… As for BJP, nationalism and Hindutva remain its trump cards in 2023 year as well, in the run-up to the general elections</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>उत्तराखंड 500 मीट्रिक टन क्षमता वाली मोबाइल स्टोरेज यूनिट लगाने वाला देश का पहला राज्य बना</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-500-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 07:01:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-500-/</guid>
      <description>उत्तराखंड 500 मीट्रिक टन क्षमता वाली मोबाइल स्टोरेज यूनिट लगाने वाला देश का पहला राज्य बना देवभूमि मीडिया ब्यूरो — उत्तराखंड 500 मीट्रिक टन क्षमता वाली मोबाइल स्टोरेज यूनिट लगाने वाला देश का पहला राज्य बन गया है। यह कहना है खाद्य मंत्री रेखा आर्य का। उन्होंने यह बात सुभाष रोड स्थित होटल में खाद्य विभाग एवं विश्व खाद्य कार्यक्रम की ओर से आयोजित कार्यक्रम को बतौर मुख्य अतिथि संबोधित करते […] The post उत्तराखंड 500 मीट्रिक टन क्षमता वाली मोबाइल स्टोरेज यूनिट लगाने वाला देश का पहला राज्य बना appeared first on Devbhoomi Media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No woman candidate in UDP for 2023 Meghalaya assembly poll</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/no-woman-candidate-in-udp-for-2023-meghalaya-assembly-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 05:18:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/no-woman-candidate-in-udp-for-2023-meghalaya-assembly-poll/</guid>
      <description>No woman candidate in UDP for 2023 Meghalaya assembly poll thenewsmill</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cong Leadership Will Find Way to Resolve Rajasthan Infighting: Jairam Ramesh</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cong-leadership-will-find-way-to-resolve-rajasthan-infighting-jairam-rames/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 16:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cong-leadership-will-find-way-to-resolve-rajasthan-infighting-jairam-rames/</guid>
      <description>Cong Leadership Will Find Way to Resolve Rajasthan Infighting: Jairam Ramesh The party faces a tussle for power in Rajasthan between Chief Minister Ashok Gehlot and his former deputy Sachin Pilot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If Needed, Law Against &#39;Love Jihad&#39; to Be Made Stronger to Protect Interests of Tribal Women: MP CM</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/if-needed-law-against-love-jihad-to-be-made-stronger-to-protect-interest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 06:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/if-needed-law-against-love-jihad-to-be-made-stronger-to-protect-interest/</guid>
      <description>If Needed, Law Against &amp;lsquo;Love Jihad&amp;rsquo; to Be Made Stronger to Protect Interests of Tribal Women: MP CM Madhya Pradesh Chief Minister Shivraj Singh Chouhan was addressing a gathering of tribal people here on the death anniversary of tribal freedom fighter Tantya Bhil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WATCH: &#39;Those who give poll tickets to Muslim women are against Islam,&#39; says Ahmedabad Jama Masjid Shahi Imam</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/watch-those-who-give-poll-tickets-to-muslim-women-are-against-islam-say/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 14:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/watch-those-who-give-poll-tickets-to-muslim-women-are-against-islam-say/</guid>
      <description>WATCH: &amp;lsquo;Those who give poll tickets to Muslim women are against Islam,&amp;rsquo; says Ahmedabad Jama Masjid Shahi Imam WATCH: &#39;Those who give poll tickets to Muslim women are against Islam,&#39; says Ahmedabad Jama Masjid Shahi Imam</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AICC General Secretary KC Venugopal Injured After Bharat Jodo Yatra Stampede in Indore</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/aicc-general-secretary-kc-venugopal-injured-after-bharat-jodo-yatra-stamped/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 04:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/aicc-general-secretary-kc-venugopal-injured-after-bharat-jodo-yatra-stamped/</guid>
      <description>AICC General Secretary KC Venugopal Injured After Bharat Jodo Yatra Stampede in Indore The stampede reportedly occurred due to the police personnel&#39;s failure to control a huddle formed to meet Rahul Gandhi</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bharat Jodo Yatra Heads for Ujjain in MP; Rahul Gandhi Seen Riding Bicycle Briefly</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bharat-jodo-yatra-heads-for-ujjain-in-mp-rahul-gandhi-seen-riding-bicycle-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 04:27:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bharat-jodo-yatra-heads-for-ujjain-in-mp-rahul-gandhi-seen-riding-bicycle-/</guid>
      <description>Bharat Jodo Yatra Heads for Ujjain in MP; Rahul Gandhi Seen Riding Bicycle Briefly The yatra, a mass contact initiative of the Congress, will cover a distance of 380 km in the Malwa-Nimar region of western Madhya Pradesh in 12 days before entering Rajasthan on December 4</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assam CM to lead BJP’s poll campaign in Meghalaya</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/assam-cm-to-lead-bjps-poll-campaign-in-meghalaya/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 07:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/assam-cm-to-lead-bjps-poll-campaign-in-meghalaya/</guid>
      <description>Assam CM to lead BJP’s poll campaign in Meghalaya thenewsmill</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just a Small Chunk of Flesh, Says Lalu&#39;s Daughter Who Decides to Donate Her Kidney to RJD Chief</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/just-a-small-chunk-of-flesh-says-lalus-daughter-who-decides-to-donate-her/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 06:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/just-a-small-chunk-of-flesh-says-lalus-daughter-who-decides-to-donate-her/</guid>
      <description>Just a Small Chunk of Flesh, Says Lalu&amp;rsquo;s Daughter Who Decides to Donate Her Kidney to RJD Chief In her early 40s, the elder sister of Bihar Deputy Chief Minister Tejashwi Yadav, came out with a series of emotional tweets on Friday, a day after the world came to know about her willingness to donate a kidney to her ailing father.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BJP gets ready for Modi&#39;s visit to Ramagundam on Nov. 12</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bjp-gets-ready-for-modis-visit-to-ramagundam-on-nov-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 16:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bjp-gets-ready-for-modis-visit-to-ramagundam-on-nov-12/</guid>
      <description>BJP gets ready for Modi&amp;rsquo;s visit to Ramagundam on Nov. 12 deccanchronicle</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polling Underway for Zila Parishad, Panchayat Samitis in 9 Haryana Districts in 1st Phase</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/polling-underway-for-zila-parishad-panchayat-samitis-in-9-haryana-district/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 06:57:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/polling-underway-for-zila-parishad-panchayat-samitis-in-9-haryana-district/</guid>
      <description>Polling Underway for Zila Parishad, Panchayat Samitis in 9 Haryana Districts in 1st Phase As many as 49,67,092 voters in nine districts are eligible to exercise their vote in the first phase of polling, for which 6,019 polling booths have been set up</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Magnetism of Muthuramalinga Thevar, His Bond with Bose, And His Touch in Tamil Nadu Politics</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-magnetism-of-muthuramalinga-thevar-his-bond-with-bose-and-his-touch-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 02:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/the-magnetism-of-muthuramalinga-thevar-his-bond-with-bose-and-his-touch-i/</guid>
      <description>The Magnetism of Muthuramalinga Thevar, His Bond with Bose, And His Touch in Tamil Nadu Politics The annual Thevar Jayanti event is to be held on October 30 to celebrate the birth anniversary of the freedom fighter, Congress and Forward Bloc leader</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did NATO Plan A Pre-Emptive Strike On Russia</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/did-nato-plan-a-pre-emptive-strike-on-russia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 19:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/did-nato-plan-a-pre-emptive-strike-on-russia/</guid>
      <description>Did NATO Plan A Pre-Emptive Strike On Russia Polaris 21 - The French Maritime Exercise that saw participation of 24 ships, one submarine, 65 aircraft and 6000 personnel with partners from Europe and USA The post Did NATO Plan A Pre-Emptive Strike On Russia appeared first on N4M (News4masses).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BJP objects to massive crowd during Vikramaditya Singh’s nomination, approaches ECI</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bjp-objects-to-massive-crowd-during-vikramaditya-singhs-nomination-appr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 16:46:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bjp-objects-to-massive-crowd-during-vikramaditya-singhs-nomination-appr/</guid>
      <description>BJP objects to massive crowd during Vikramaditya Singh’s nomination, approaches ECI Shimla: Irked over witnessing a massive crowd during the nomination of former six-time Chief Minister Virbhadra Singh and MLA Vikramaditya Singh has made Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP), the party has approached the election commission and has filed a complaint against Singh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sonia, Rahul, Kharge on list of 40-star campaigners for Himachal poll</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sonia-rahul-kharge-on-list-of-40-star-campaigners-for-himachal-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 16:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sonia-rahul-kharge-on-list-of-40-star-campaigners-for-himachal-poll/</guid>
      <description>Sonia, Rahul, Kharge on list of 40-star campaigners for Himachal poll Shimla: Newly elected President of the All India Congress Committee (AICC), Mallikarjun Kharge, former Presidents Rahul Gandhi and Sonia Gandhi and Congress General Secretary Priyanka Gandhi Vadra will be the star campaigners of Congress in the state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Congress fields Jagat from Kinnaur, Gaur from Manali</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/congress-fields-jagat-from-kinnaur-gaur-from-manali/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 14:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/congress-fields-jagat-from-kinnaur-gaur-from-manali/</guid>
      <description>Congress fields Jagat from Kinnaur, Gaur from Manali Shimla: Indian National Congress has issued its third list of candidates for four Legislative Assembly Constituencies and once again has fielded four-time MLA Jagat Singh Negi (ST) as its candidate from Kinnaur.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
