<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>India on TechnoStreet</title>
    <link>https://technostreet.github.io/tags/india/</link>
    <description>Recent content in India on TechnoStreet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 04:17:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://technostreet.github.io/tags/india/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Delhi colleges facing fund crunch urge L-G to intervene</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/delhi-colleges-facing-fund-crunch-urge-l-g-to-intervene/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 04:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/delhi-colleges-facing-fund-crunch-urge-l-g-to-intervene/</guid>
      <description>Delhi colleges facing fund crunch urge L-G to intervene A delegation of Delhi University Principals Association met Delhi Lieutenant Governor V.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bharat Jodo Yatra resumes journey in Uttar Pradesh</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bharat-jodo-yatra-resumes-journey-in-uttar-pradesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 05:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bharat-jodo-yatra-resumes-journey-in-uttar-pradesh/</guid>
      <description>Bharat Jodo Yatra resumes journey in Uttar Pradesh Former party chief Rahul Gandhi reached the village from Delhi ahead of the resumption of the march, Congress Uttar Pradesh unit spokesperson Anshu Awasthi said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Congress Cut Expenses: कांग्रेस की पार्टी पदाधिकारियों को नसीहत- खर्च में करें कटौती, चाय-पानी से लेकर हवाई सफर तक का जिक्र</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/congress-cut-expenses-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 13:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/congress-cut-expenses-/</guid>
      <description>Congress Cut Expenses: कांग्रेस की पार्टी पदाधिकारियों को नसीहत- खर्च में करें कटौती, चाय-पानी से लेकर हवाई सफर तक का जिक्र कांग्रेस की पार्टी पदाधिकारियों को नसीहत- खर्च में करें कटौती, चाय-पानी से लेकर हवाई सफर तक का जिक्र</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>दिल्ली में कोहरा बना आफत! 100 फ्लाइट्स लेट, 2 डायवर्ट, 200 मीटर से भी कम हुई विजिबिलिटी</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-100-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 02:46:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-100-/</guid>
      <description>दिल्ली में कोहरा बना आफत! 100 फ्लाइट्स लेट, 2 डायवर्ट, 200 मीटर से भी कम हुई विजिबिलिटी दिल्ली में कोहरा बना आफत!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bharat Jodo Yatra: क्यों नहीं लगती राहुल गांधी को ठंड? लोगों ने बताया कांग्रेस नेता के भीषण सर्दी में भी टी-शर्ट पहनने का राज</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bharat-jodo-yatra-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 04:36:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bharat-jodo-yatra-/</guid>
      <description>Bharat Jodo Yatra: क्यों नहीं लगती राहुल गांधी को ठंड? लोगों ने बताया कांग्रेस नेता के भीषण सर्दी में भी टी-शर्ट पहनने का राज क्यों नहीं लगती राहुल गांधी को ठंड?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stopped from using mobile, 10-year-old ends life in UP</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/stopped-from-using-mobile-10-year-old-ends-life-in-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 04:28:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/stopped-from-using-mobile-10-year-old-ends-life-in-up/</guid>
      <description>Stopped from using mobile, 10-year-old ends life in UP In a shocking incident, a 10-year-old boy allegedly died by suicide in Lucknow after his mother took away the phone and did not let him play online games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uttarakhand: सुशासन दिवस पर CM धामी ने लगवाई पूरे प्रदेश में चौपाल</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/uttarakhand-cm-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 14:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/uttarakhand-cm-/</guid>
      <description>Uttarakhand: सुशासन दिवस पर CM धामी ने लगवाई पूरे प्रदेश में चौपाल Uttarakhand: इस वर्ष देश की आजादी के 75 वर्ष पूरे हुए। अब अमृत काल में प्रवेश कर गये हैं.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“We don’t want India, let it stay abroad .. ” – Controversy over the speech of Lalu party leader Asked My Children To Settle Abroad: Lalu Yadav’s Party Leader Sparks Row</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/we-dont-want-india-let-it-stay-abroad-controversy-over-th/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 06:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/we-dont-want-india-let-it-stay-abroad-controversy-over-th/</guid>
      <description>“We don’t want India, let it stay abroad .. ” – Controversy over the speech of Lalu party leader Asked My Children To Settle Abroad: Lalu Yadav’s Party Leader Sparks Row Lalu Prasad’s party leader Abdul Pari Siddiqui’s statement that he will settle my children abroad has sparked controversy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19: Ahead of New Year, Centre approves Nasal vaccine, to introduce new guidelines</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/covid-19-ahead-of-new-year-centre-approves-nasal-vaccine-to-introduce-ne/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 05:33:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/covid-19-ahead-of-new-year-centre-approves-nasal-vaccine-to-introduce-ne/</guid>
      <description>COVID-19: Ahead of New Year, Centre approves Nasal vaccine, to introduce new guidelines New Delhi: The Centre on Friday approved the Nasal vaccine which will be available in private hospitals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangladesh 82-2 on 1st morning of 2nd test against India</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bangladesh-82-2-on-1st-morning-of-2nd-test-against-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 06:19:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bangladesh-82-2-on-1st-morning-of-2nd-test-against-india/</guid>
      <description>Bangladesh 82-2 on 1st morning of 2nd test against India Following its 188-run defeat in the first test at Chattogram, Bangladesh made two changes with batter Mominul Haque and fast bowler Taskin Ahmed replacing Yasir Ali and Ebadot Hossain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIA charge sheets 5 CPI (Maoist) cadres for luring girls</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nia-charge-sheets-5-cpi-maoist-cadres-for-luring-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 07:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nia-charge-sheets-5-cpi-maoist-cadres-for-luring-girls/</guid>
      <description>NIA charge sheets 5 CPI (Maoist) cadres for luring girls The case was initially registered by Peddabayalu Police Station of Visakhapatnam and later re-registered by the NIA in June 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nation is always indebted to Armed Forces – PM Modi Tributes on Victory Day</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nation-is-always-indebted-to-armed-forces-pm-modi-tributes-on-victory-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 07:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/nation-is-always-indebted-to-armed-forces-pm-modi-tributes-on-victory-d/</guid>
      <description>Nation is always indebted to Armed Forces – PM Modi Tributes on Victory Day New Delhi: “Our nation is always indebted to the armed forces,” PM Modi tweeted on Victory Day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shraddha Murder Case: Aaftab Poonawala seeks bail, files petition in Delhi court</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/shraddha-murder-case-aaftab-poonawala-seeks-bail-files-petition-in-delhi-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 07:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/shraddha-murder-case-aaftab-poonawala-seeks-bail-files-petition-in-delhi-/</guid>
      <description>Shraddha Murder Case: Aaftab Poonawala seeks bail, files petition in Delhi court Aftab Poonawala, the suspect in the murder of Shraddha Walkar, filed a petition at Delhi&#39;s Saket Court asking for bail in the case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tawang Clash: तवांग झड़प को लेकर सरकार गंभीर, तीनों सेना प्रमुख के साथ राजनाथ ने बुलाई बैठक, संसद में दे सकते हैं बयान</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tawang-clash-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 04:38:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tawang-clash-/</guid>
      <description>Tawang Clash: तवांग झड़प को लेकर सरकार गंभीर, तीनों सेना प्रमुख के साथ राजनाथ ने बुलाई बैठक, संसद में दे सकते हैं बयान Rajnath Singh On Tawang Clash: अरुणाचल के तवांग सेक्टर में 9 दिसंबर को भारत और चीन की सेना के बीच हिंसक झड़प हुई.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confusion over Saudi Tourist visa rules: Many Indians land in trouble</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/confusion-over-saudi-tourist-visa-rules-many-indians-land-in-trouble/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 16:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/confusion-over-saudi-tourist-visa-rules-many-indians-land-in-trouble/</guid>
      <description>Confusion over Saudi Tourist visa rules: Many Indians land in trouble The multiple-entry tourist visa is valid for one year from the date of issuance, and the permissible period of stay is 90 days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delhi MCD Results 2022: केजरीवाल के पिता बोले- दिल्ली में आएगा &#39;मफलर मैन&#39;, MCD में सबसे पहले AAP करेगी ये काम</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/delhi-mcd-results-2022-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 05:19:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/delhi-mcd-results-2022-/</guid>
      <description>Delhi MCD Results 2022: केजरीवाल के पिता बोले- दिल्ली में आएगा &amp;lsquo;मफलर मैन&amp;rsquo;, MCD में सबसे पहले AAP करेगी ये काम Delhi MCD Election 2022 Results Reactions: दिल्ली नगर निगम चुनाव की मतगणना जारी है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian Railways increases train speed to avoid delays due to fog</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indian-railways-increases-train-speed-to-avoid-delays-due-to-fog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 16:29:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/indian-railways-increases-train-speed-to-avoid-delays-due-to-fog/</guid>
      <description>Indian Railways increases train speed to avoid delays due to fog Indian Railways is taking various measures to make train services safe from fog in northern parts of the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>‘Don’t know why Congress ignores Shashi Tharoor,’ says NCP leader</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dont-know-why-congress-ignores-shashi-tharoor-says-ncp-leader/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 06:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dont-know-why-congress-ignores-shashi-tharoor-says-ncp-leader/</guid>
      <description>‘Don’t know why Congress ignores Shashi Tharoor,’ says NCP leader New Delhi: The Nationalist Congress Party (NCP) president of Kerala unit, PC Chacko, raised questions at the Congress asking why the latter is ignoring party leader Shashi Tharoor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mehdi Hasan’s Intimidatory Batting – Bangladesh Defeat India in ‘Tik Tik’</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mehdi-hasans-intimidatory-batting-bangladesh-defeat-india-in-tik-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 14:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mehdi-hasans-intimidatory-batting-bangladesh-defeat-india-in-tik-/</guid>
      <description>Mehdi Hasan’s Intimidatory Batting – Bangladesh Defeat India in ‘Tik Tik’ Bangladesh won the match against India by 1 wicket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uttarakhand: उत्तराखंड में भारत-नेपाल बॉर्डर पर तनाव, भारतीय मजदूरों पर सीमापार से की गई पत्थरबाजी</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/uttarakhand-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 14:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/uttarakhand-/</guid>
      <description>Uttarakhand: उत्तराखंड में भारत-नेपाल बॉर्डर पर तनाव, भारतीय मजदूरों पर सीमापार से की गई पत्थरबाजी Nepal-India Border Dispute: उत्तराखंड के पिथौरागढ़ (Pithoragarh) में भारत-नेपाल सीमा पर रविवार (4 दिसंबर) को तनावपूर्ण स्थिति पैदा हो गई.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drugs Recovered: मुंबई एयरपोर्ट पर DRI ने विदेशी यात्रियों से बरामद की 18 करोड़ रुपये की कोकीन, दो गिरफ्तार</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/drugs-recovered-dri-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 15:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/drugs-recovered-dri-/</guid>
      <description>Drugs Recovered: मुंबई एयरपोर्ट पर DRI ने विदेशी यात्रियों से बरामद की 18 करोड़ रुपये की कोकीन, दो गिरफ्तार DRI Seized Drugs: महाराष्ट्र के मुंबई में छत्रपति शिवाजी महाराज इंटरनेशनल एयरपोर्ट पर डीआरआई को एक बड़ी कामयाबी हासिल हुई है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bharat Jodo Yatra: Swara Bhaskar, Ex-CM Harish Rawat walks briskly with Rahul Gandhi</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bharat-jodo-yatra-swara-bhaskar-ex-cm-harish-rawat-walks-briskly-with-rah/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 07:19:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bharat-jodo-yatra-swara-bhaskar-ex-cm-harish-rawat-walks-briskly-with-rah/</guid>
      <description>Bharat Jodo Yatra: Swara Bhaskar, Ex-CM Harish Rawat walks briskly with Rahul Gandhi New Delhi: Former Chief Minister of Uttarakhand Harish Rawat, ex-parliamentarian Prem Chand Guddu and actor Swara Bhaskar joined the ‘Bharat Jodo Yatra’ on Thursday in Madhya Pradesh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watch: Congress MLA Paresh Dhanani carries gas cylinder on his bicycle to cast vote</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/watch-congress-mla-paresh-dhanani-carries-gas-cylinder-on-his-bicycle-to-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 07:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/watch-congress-mla-paresh-dhanani-carries-gas-cylinder-on-his-bicycle-to-c/</guid>
      <description>Watch: Congress MLA Paresh Dhanani carries gas cylinder on his bicycle to cast vote Watch: Congress MLA Paresh Dhanani carries gas cylinder on his bicycle to cast vote</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t agree with Nadav Lapid&#39;s remarks on &#39;The Kashmir Files&#39;, says Israeli diplomat on IFFI row</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dont-agree-with-nadav-lapids-remarks-on-the-kashmir-files-says-israeli/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 06:53:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dont-agree-with-nadav-lapids-remarks-on-the-kashmir-files-says-israeli/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t agree with Nadav Lapid&amp;rsquo;s remarks on &amp;lsquo;The Kashmir Files&amp;rsquo;, says Israeli diplomat on IFFI row Don&#39;t agree with Nadav Lapid&#39;s remarks on &#39;The Kashmir Files&#39;, says Israeli diplomat on IFFI row</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shraddha murder case: Aaftab to undergo pending polygraph sessions this week, narco test likely on 5 December</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/shraddha-murder-case-aaftab-to-undergo-pending-polygraph-sessions-this-wee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 04:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/shraddha-murder-case-aaftab-to-undergo-pending-polygraph-sessions-this-wee/</guid>
      <description>Shraddha murder case: Aaftab to undergo pending polygraph sessions this week, narco test likely on 5 December Shraddha murder case: Aaftab to undergo pending polygraph sessions this week, narco test likely on 5 December</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second ODI: Indian batting needs fresh approach to save series against New Zealand</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/second-odi-indian-batting-needs-fresh-approach-to-save-series-against-new-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 15:45:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/second-odi-indian-batting-needs-fresh-approach-to-save-series-against-new-/</guid>
      <description>Second ODI: Indian batting needs fresh approach to save series against New Zealand Hamilton: India would expect a better approach from skipper Shikhar Dhawan and young Shubman Gill in the Powerplay overs when the team clashes with New Zealand in the do-or-die second One-Day International here Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PT Usha throws her hat into IOA ring, to fight for president’s post</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/pt-usha-throws-her-hat-into-ioa-ring-to-fight-for-presidents-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 15:45:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/pt-usha-throws-her-hat-into-ioa-ring-to-fight-for-presidents-post/</guid>
      <description>PT Usha throws her hat into IOA ring, to fight for president’s post The legendary P T Usha on Saturday announced that she will contest for the post of Indian Olympic Association</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India go down to Aussies despite Akashdeep treble</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-go-down-to-aussies-despite-akashdeep-treble/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 15:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-go-down-to-aussies-despite-akashdeep-treble/</guid>
      <description>India go down to Aussies despite Akashdeep treble Adelaide: Akashdeep Singh’s hat-trick went in vain as India conceded two late goals to lose 4-5 against Australia in the high-scoring first hockey Test of the five-match series here Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collegium system alien to constitution: Law Minister</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/collegium-system-alien-to-constitution-law-minister/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 03:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/collegium-system-alien-to-constitution-law-minister/</guid>
      <description>Collegium system alien to constitution: Law Minister No institution in a constitutional democracy, including collegium, is perfect: CJI Amid frequent run-ins between the government and the judiciary, Union Law Minister Kiren Rijiju on Friday pitched for fraternal ties between the two pillars of democracy, saying they are like brothers and should not fight each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 News: रेलवे से निकाले जा रहे भ्रष्ट अधिकारी, गहलोत-पायलट में दिखी दूरियां</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/top-10-news-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 04:45:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/top-10-news-/</guid>
      <description>Top 10 News: रेलवे से निकाले जा रहे भ्रष्ट अधिकारी, गहलोत-पायलट में दिखी दूरियां Today&#39;s Top 10 News: जेल में बंद आप नेता सत्येंद्र जैन के लीक वीडियो के मामले पर आज होगी सुनवाई.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jacqueline Fernandez arrives at Delhi court in money laundering case involving conman Sukesh Chandrashekhar</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/jacqueline-fernandez-arrives-at-delhi-court-in-money-laundering-case-involv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 04:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/jacqueline-fernandez-arrives-at-delhi-court-in-money-laundering-case-involv/</guid>
      <description>Jacqueline Fernandez arrives at Delhi court in money laundering case involving conman Sukesh Chandrashekhar On Thursday, November 24, actor Jacqueline Fernandez arrived at the Patiala House Court in Delhi in connection with the Rs 200 crore money laundering case involving conman Sukesh Chandrashekhar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PM Modi Rally LIVE: Prime Minister Narendra Modi to address four rallies in Gujarat today</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/pm-modi-rally-live-prime-minister-narendra-modi-to-address-four-rallies-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 04:43:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/pm-modi-rally-live-prime-minister-narendra-modi-to-address-four-rallies-in/</guid>
      <description>PM Modi Rally LIVE: Prime Minister Narendra Modi to address four rallies in Gujarat today PM Modi Rally LIVE: Prime Minister Narendra Modi to address four rallies in Gujarat today</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hindu Mahasabha plans to rename Meerut after Nathuram Godse, if elected</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hindu-mahasabha-plans-to-rename-meerut-after-nathuram-godse-if-elected/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 05:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hindu-mahasabha-plans-to-rename-meerut-after-nathuram-godse-if-elected/</guid>
      <description>Hindu Mahasabha plans to rename Meerut after Nathuram Godse, if elected Meerut: The Hindu Mahasabha promised that it will change the name of Meerut to Nathuram Godse Nagar if they comes to power in the upcoming civic polls in Uttar Pradesh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telangana: Concern voiced over BJP’s misuse of central agencies</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/telangana-concern-voiced-over-bjps-misuse-of-central-agencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 13:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/telangana-concern-voiced-over-bjps-misuse-of-central-agencies/</guid>
      <description>Telangana: Concern voiced over BJP’s misuse of central agencies Nalgonda: Leaders of different organizations have in a single voice expressed strong concern over the misuse of central agencies including the Enforcement Directorate (ED) and the Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI) by the BJP government to target opposition parties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terrorists use dark web to radicalise, funnel crypto currency: Amit Shah</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/terrorists-use-dark-web-to-radicalise-funnel-crypto-currency-amit-shah/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 07:52:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/terrorists-use-dark-web-to-radicalise-funnel-crypto-currency-amit-shah/</guid>
      <description>Terrorists use dark web to radicalise, funnel crypto currency: Amit Shah New Delhi: Union Home Minister Amit Shah Friday said terrorists are spreading radicalism among youth and using elements like dark web and virtual assests to hide their identities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid-19 Updates: India logs 635 new cases, 11 deaths in last 24 hours</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/covid-19-updates-india-logs-635-new-cases-11-deaths-in-last-24-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 06:25:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/covid-19-updates-india-logs-635-new-cases-11-deaths-in-last-24-hours/</guid>
      <description>Covid-19 Updates: India logs 635 new cases, 11 deaths in last 24 hours Covid-19 Updates: Even today, there is some good news for India in terms of the global pandemic Corona.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>नोएडा एक्सटेंशन के La Residentia सोसायटी की लिफ्ट में पेट डॉग ने बच्चे को काटा, लगे 4 इंजेक्शन</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-la-residentia-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 07:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-la-residentia-/</guid>
      <description>नोएडा एक्सटेंशन के La Residentia सोसायटी की लिफ्ट में पेट डॉग ने बच्चे को काटा, लगे 4 इंजेक्शन आमतौर पर बच्चों को पहले स्ट्रीट डॉग से खतरा हुआ करता था लेकिन अब तो पेट डॉग.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ब्रिटेन के PM बनने के बाद पहली बार पीएम मोदी से मिले ऋषि सुनक, ऐसी रही बातचीत</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-pm-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 08:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-pm-/</guid>
      <description>ब्रिटेन के PM बनने के बाद पहली बार पीएम मोदी से मिले ऋषि सुनक, ऐसी रही बातचीत बाली में जी20 शिखर सम्मेलन के पहले दिन प्रधानमंत्री नरेंद्र मोदी और ऋषि सुनक ने चर्चा की.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflections on 60 days of the Bharat Jodo Yatra</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/reflections-on-60-days-of-the-bharat-jodo-yatra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 15:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/reflections-on-60-days-of-the-bharat-jodo-yatra/</guid>
      <description>Reflections on 60 days of the Bharat Jodo Yatra Someone sarcastically asked me as to how much Bharat we have unified.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vice President Dhankhar meets Cambodian PM, discuss bilateral ties</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/vice-president-dhankhar-meets-cambodian-pm-discuss-bilateral-ties/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 06:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/vice-president-dhankhar-meets-cambodian-pm-discuss-bilateral-ties/</guid>
      <description>Vice President Dhankhar meets Cambodian PM, discuss bilateral ties Both leaders also witnessed the exchange of four agreements in the areas of culture, wildlife and health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musk&#39;s lawyer tells Twitter employees they won&#39;t go to jail</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/musks-lawyer-tells-twitter-employees-they-wont-go-to-jail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 06:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/musks-lawyer-tells-twitter-employees-they-wont-go-to-jail/</guid>
      <description>Musk&amp;rsquo;s lawyer tells Twitter employees they won&amp;rsquo;t go to jail A lawyer working for Elon Musk has reassured Twitter staff that they will not go to jail for being liable if the company violated the requirements of the Federal Trade Commission&#39;s (FTC) consent decree</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MCD Polls: AAP promises to end corruption in ‘Kejriwal Ki 10 Guarantees’</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mcd-polls-aap-promises-to-end-corruption-in-kejriwal-ki-10-guarantees/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 07:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mcd-polls-aap-promises-to-end-corruption-in-kejriwal-ki-10-guarantees/</guid>
      <description>MCD Polls: AAP promises to end corruption in ‘Kejriwal Ki 10 Guarantees’ New Delhi: Aam Aadmi Party (AAP) on Friday released its ‘Kejriwal ki 10 guarantee’ for Municipal Corporation of Delhi (MCD) polls scheduled for December 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attack on Owaisi in UP: SC quashes HC order granting bail to two accused</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/attack-on-owaisi-in-up-sc-quashes-hc-order-granting-bail-to-two-accused/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 07:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/attack-on-owaisi-in-up-sc-quashes-hc-order-granting-bail-to-two-accused/</guid>
      <description>Attack on Owaisi in UP: SC quashes HC order granting bail to two accused A bench of Justices M R Shah and M M Sundresh said the high court did not accord any reason while giving bail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WATCH: PM Modi unveils 108-feet-tall bronze statue of Bengaluru founder &#39;Nadaprabhu&#39; Kempegowda</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/watch-pm-modi-unveils-108-feet-tall-bronze-statue-of-bengaluru-founder-na/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 07:29:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/watch-pm-modi-unveils-108-feet-tall-bronze-statue-of-bengaluru-founder-na/</guid>
      <description>WATCH: PM Modi unveils 108-feet-tall bronze statue of Bengaluru founder &amp;lsquo;Nadaprabhu&amp;rsquo; Kempegowda On November 11, Prime Minister Narendra Modi unveiled a 108-feet-tall bronze statue of Bengaluru founder &#39;Nadaprabhu&#39; Kempegowda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>West Bengal: A suspected member of Al Qaeda in the Indian subcontinent arrested in Kolkata</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/west-bengal-a-suspected-member-of-al-qaeda-in-the-indian-subcontinent-arre/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 04:36:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/west-bengal-a-suspected-member-of-al-qaeda-in-the-indian-subcontinent-arre/</guid>
      <description>West Bengal: A suspected member of Al Qaeda in the Indian subcontinent arrested in Kolkata Kolkata: A suspected member of the terror outfit, Al Qaeda in the Indian subcontinent (AQIS) and Ansarullah Bangla Team, was arrested in West Bengal&#39;s South 24 Parganas district, a senior officer told news agency PTI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now Meta plans to lay off &#39;thousands&#39; of employees this week: Report</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/now-meta-plans-to-lay-off-thousands-of-employees-this-week-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/now-meta-plans-to-lay-off-thousands-of-employees-this-week-report/</guid>
      <description>Now Meta plans to lay off &amp;lsquo;thousands&amp;rsquo; of employees this week: Report After mass layoffs at Twitter, it is another Big Tech company&#39;s turn as the Mark Zuckerberg-led Meta is reportedly set to lay off &#39;thousands&#39; of employees this week</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Which teams have qualified in T20 World Cup semi final: Which team will India play against in semi final of 2022 World Cup?</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/which-teams-have-qualified-in-t20-world-cup-semi-final-which-team-will-ind/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 11:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/which-teams-have-qualified-in-t20-world-cup-semi-final-which-team-will-ind/</guid>
      <description>Which teams have qualified in T20 World Cup semi final: Which team will India play against in semi final of 2022 World Cup?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contractors who repaired Morbi bridge not qualified: Prosecution tells court</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/contractors-who-repaired-morbi-bridge-not-qualified-prosecution-tells-cour/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 07:04:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/contractors-who-repaired-morbi-bridge-not-qualified-prosecution-tells-cour/</guid>
      <description>Contractors who repaired Morbi bridge not qualified: Prosecution tells court While the bridge flooring was replaced, its cable was not replaced and it could not take the weight of the changed flooring</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delhi Police raids residential premises of editors of The Wire</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/delhi-police-raids-residential-premises-of-editors-of-the-wire/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:37:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/delhi-police-raids-residential-premises-of-editors-of-the-wire/</guid>
      <description>Delhi Police raids residential premises of editors of The Wire As per a news agency, the police seized electronic devices including mobile phones and laptops from the homes of Siddharth Varadarajan and M.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DU admission 2022: More than 8,100 students allotted seats in second round</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/du-admission-2022-more-than-8100-students-allotted-seats-in-second-round/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/du-admission-2022-more-than-8100-students-allotted-seats-in-second-round/</guid>
      <description>DU admission 2022: More than 8,100 students allotted seats in second round New Delhi: Over 8,100 new student applicants have been allotted seats in second round of college and programme allocation of Delhi University (DU), a DU registrar has informed PTI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stubble burning share in Delhi&#39;s pollution rises to 26%, the highest this year</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/stubble-burning-share-in-delhis-pollution-rises-to-26-the-highest-this-y/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/stubble-burning-share-in-delhis-pollution-rises-to-26-the-highest-this-y/</guid>
      <description>Stubble burning share in Delhi&amp;rsquo;s pollution rises to 26%, the highest this year The share of stubble burning in Delhi PM 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delhi pollution: GRAP stage 3 kicks in as air quality deteriorates, know what all will be affected</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/delhi-pollution-grap-stage-3-kicks-in-as-air-quality-deteriorates-know-wh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 03:07:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/delhi-pollution-grap-stage-3-kicks-in-as-air-quality-deteriorates-know-wh/</guid>
      <description>Delhi pollution: GRAP stage 3 kicks in as air quality deteriorates, know what all will be affected Under GRAP stage 3, states may impose restrictions on the plying of BS III petrol and BS IV diesel four-wheelers in the NCR.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Narendra Dabholkar&#39;s footprints would only deepen; proud to have lived in same era as him: Naseeruddin Shah</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/narendra-dabholkars-footprints-would-only-deepen-proud-to-have-lived-in-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/narendra-dabholkars-footprints-would-only-deepen-proud-to-have-lived-in-s/</guid>
      <description>Narendra Dabholkar&amp;rsquo;s footprints would only deepen; proud to have lived in same era as him: Naseeruddin Shah Dr Narendra Dabholkar&#39;s work can not be wiped out and his &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JSW Steel Expects Margins To Revive After Surprise Loss</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/jsw-steel-expects-margins-to-revive-after-surprise-loss/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 06:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/jsw-steel-expects-margins-to-revive-after-surprise-loss/</guid>
      <description>JSW Steel Expects Margins To Revive After Surprise Loss India’s JSW Steel Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India vs Netherlands T20 head to head records: IND vs NED head to head in T20 history</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-vs-netherlands-t20-head-to-head-records-ind-vs-ned-head-to-head-in-t/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 12:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-vs-netherlands-t20-head-to-head-records-ind-vs-ned-head-to-head-in-t/</guid>
      <description>India vs Netherlands T20 head to head records: IND vs NED head to head in T20 history India vs Netherlands T20 head to head: The SportsRush presents for you the Head to Head statistics for IND vs NED T20 World Cup match.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gujarat: PM Narendra Modi’s meet with Patidar leader sets tongues wagging</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gujarat-pm-narendra-modis-meet-with-patidar-leader-sets-tongues-wagging/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 16:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gujarat-pm-narendra-modis-meet-with-patidar-leader-sets-tongues-wagging/</guid>
      <description>Gujarat: PM Narendra Modi’s meet with Patidar leader sets tongues wagging Ahmedabad: Amid speculation that Prime Minister Narendra Modi may visit influential Patidar organisations on Sardar Patel’s birth anniversary on October 31 in a renewed bid to win over the community, Naresh Patel, Chairman of the Shree Khodaldham Trust, met him at his residence in New Delhi on Saturday evening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gujarat BJP targets Kejriwal over cracker ban in Delhi</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gujarat-bjp-targets-kejriwal-over-cracker-ban-in-delhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 08:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gujarat-bjp-targets-kejriwal-over-cracker-ban-in-delhi/</guid>
      <description>Gujarat BJP targets Kejriwal over cracker ban in Delhi Rajkot: Gujarat BJP chief C R Paatil has hit out at Delhi Chief Minister Arvind Kejriwal over his government’s decision to completely ban firecrackers in the national capital, and dubbed such people “anti-religious” who were stopping citizens from celebrating their festivals.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
