<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bqblue on TechnoStreet</title>
    <link>https://technostreet.github.io/tags/bqblue/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bqblue on TechnoStreet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 04:30:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://technostreet.github.io/tags/bqblue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Baroda Q2 Results Review - Strong Performance; Lower Provisions Drive Earnings: Motilal Oswal</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bank-of-baroda-q2-results-review-strong-performance-lower-provisions-dri/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 04:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bank-of-baroda-q2-results-review-strong-performance-lower-provisions-dri/</guid>
      <description>Bank of Baroda Q2 Results Review - Strong Performance; Lower Provisions Drive Earnings: Motilal Oswal Bank reported a strong performance with healthy NII growth (resulting in margin expansion), lower provisions, driving net earnings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medanta Hospital Operator Global Health’s IPO - Reputed Brand In Hospitals Space: ICICI Direct</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/medanta-hospital-operator-global-healths-ipo-reputed-brand-in-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 06:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/medanta-hospital-operator-global-healths-ipo-reputed-brand-in-hospital/</guid>
      <description>Medanta Hospital Operator Global Health’s IPO - Reputed Brand In Hospitals Space: ICICI Direct It provides healthcare services in over 30 medical specialties and engage over 1,300 doctors spanning an area of 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bikaji Foods IPO - Large Play In Ethnic Snacks Industry: ICICI Direct</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bikaji-foods-ipo-large-play-in-ethnic-snacks-industry-icici-direct/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 06:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bikaji-foods-ipo-large-play-in-ethnic-snacks-industry-icici-direct/</guid>
      <description>Bikaji Foods IPO - Large Play In Ethnic Snacks Industry: ICICI Direct Bikaji Foods is expanding across geographies and trying to emerge as a dominant pan-India player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bikaji Foods IPO - Leading Snacks Player With Pan India Presence: Reliance Securities</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bikaji-foods-ipo-leading-snacks-player-with-pan-india-presence-reliance-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 05:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bikaji-foods-ipo-leading-snacks-player-with-pan-india-presence-reliance-/</guid>
      <description>Bikaji Foods IPO - Leading Snacks Player With Pan India Presence: Reliance Securities The company is coming out with an IPO of Rs 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kajaria Ceramics Q2 Results Review - Margins To Improve From H2: Yes Securities</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/kajaria-ceramics-q2-results-review-margins-to-improve-from-h2-yes-securi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 05:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/kajaria-ceramics-q2-results-review-margins-to-improve-from-h2-yes-securi/</guid>
      <description>Kajaria Ceramics Q2 Results Review - Margins To Improve From H2: Yes Securities On margins, management is confident that worst seems to behind as gas cost have started to tapper-down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dalmia Bharat Q2 Results Review - Healthy Volumes Coupled With Cost Discipline: ICICI Securities</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dalmia-bharat-q2-results-review-healthy-volumes-coupled-with-cost-discipl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 05:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dalmia-bharat-q2-results-review-healthy-volumes-coupled-with-cost-discipl/</guid>
      <description>Dalmia Bharat Q2 Results Review - Healthy Volumes Coupled With Cost Discipline: ICICI Securities Volumes grew at a strong rate of 14% YoY (on a low base, ramping-up its newly commissioned plants), implying a 3-year CAGR of 9%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adani Ports Q2 Results Review - Bulk Expected To Grow Ahead Of Container Volumes: ICICI Direct</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/adani-ports-q2-results-review-bulk-expected-to-grow-ahead-of-container-vo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 05:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/adani-ports-q2-results-review-bulk-expected-to-grow-ahead-of-container-vo/</guid>
      <description>Adani Ports Q2 Results Review - Bulk Expected To Grow Ahead Of Container Volumes: ICICI Direct For H2, volume boost expected from five new services at Mundra and Hazira; four bulk contract wins at Gangavaram and Dhamra.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fusion Micro Finance IPO - Investment Rationale, Strengths, Key Strategies, Risks, Financials: Anand Rathi</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/fusion-micro-finance-ipo-investment-rationale-strengths-key-strategies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 07:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/fusion-micro-finance-ipo-investment-rationale-strengths-key-strategies/</guid>
      <description>Fusion Micro Finance IPO - Investment Rationale, Strengths, Key Strategies, Risks, Financials: Anand Rathi Fusion Micro Finance provides financial services to unserved and underserved women in rural and peri-rural areas across India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SBI Cards Q2 Review - Receivables Growth Strong, Revolver Mix Falling Again A Dampener: Prabhudas Lilladher</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sbi-cards-q2-review-receivables-growth-strong-revolver-mix-falling-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 07:12:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sbi-cards-q2-review-receivables-growth-strong-revolver-mix-falling-again/</guid>
      <description>SBI Cards Q2 Review - Receivables Growth Strong, Revolver Mix Falling Again A Dampener: Prabhudas Lilladher Yields fell as higher yielding revolver mix decreased to 24% from 26% in Q1 FY23 of overall receivables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ye’s Antisemitic Rants Wreck Path To Multibillion-Dollar Fortune</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/yes-antisemitic-rants-wreck-path-to-multibillion-dollar-fortune/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/yes-antisemitic-rants-wreck-path-to-multibillion-dollar-fortune/</guid>
      <description>Ye’s Antisemitic Rants Wreck Path To Multibillion-Dollar Fortune The rapper lost out on a lucrative deal with Adidas, which said it would end the Yeezy line after facing blowback.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
