<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ICC T20 World Cup 2022 on TechnoStreet</title>
    <link>https://technostreet.github.io/tags/icc-t20-world-cup-2022/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ICC T20 World Cup 2022 on TechnoStreet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 13:59:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://technostreet.github.io/tags/icc-t20-world-cup-2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>“You know I love you but just chill”: Kevin Pietersen requests Virat Kohli to have a day off during India vs England World Cup semi final 2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/you-know-i-love-you-but-just-chill-kevin-pietersen-requests-virat-ko/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 13:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/you-know-i-love-you-but-just-chill-kevin-pietersen-requests-virat-ko/</guid>
      <description>“You know I love you but just chill”: Kevin Pietersen requests Virat Kohli to have a day off during India vs England World Cup semi final 2022 The Adelaide Oval in Adelaide is set to host the 2nd semi-final of the ICC T20 World Cup 2022 between India and England.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Which teams have qualified in T20 World Cup semi final: Which team will India play against in semi final of 2022 World Cup?</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/which-teams-have-qualified-in-t20-world-cup-semi-final-which-team-will-ind/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 11:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/which-teams-have-qualified-in-t20-world-cup-semi-final-which-team-will-ind/</guid>
      <description>Which teams have qualified in T20 World Cup semi final: Which team will India play against in semi final of 2022 World Cup?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Babar Azam T20 World Cup runs 2022: Pakistani captain T20 World Cup innings list</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/babar-azam-t20-world-cup-runs-2022-pakistani-captain-t20-world-cup-innings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 07:33:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/babar-azam-t20-world-cup-runs-2022-pakistani-captain-t20-world-cup-innings/</guid>
      <description>Babar Azam T20 World Cup runs 2022: Pakistani captain T20 World Cup innings list Pakistan’s captain Babar Azam’s horrid T20 World Cup 2022 continued in the match against South Africa as well where he managed to score 6 runs in 15 deliveries before getting dismissed to Lungi Ngidi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rohit Sharma vs Bangladesh stats: Rohit Sharma record against Bangladesh T20 innings list</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rohit-sharma-vs-bangladesh-stats-rohit-sharma-record-against-bangladesh-t2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 07:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rohit-sharma-vs-bangladesh-stats-rohit-sharma-record-against-bangladesh-t2/</guid>
      <description>Rohit Sharma vs Bangladesh stats: Rohit Sharma record against Bangladesh T20 innings list India will face Bangladesh in the Super-12 match of the ICC T20 World Cup 2022 at the Adelaide Oval in Adelaide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“He’s probably gonna make you pay”: Kane Williamson rues Jos Buttler’s drop catch after losing ICC T20 World Cup match vs England</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hes-probably-gonna-make-you-pay-kane-williamson-rues-jos-buttler/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hes-probably-gonna-make-you-pay-kane-williamson-rues-jos-buttler/</guid>
      <description>“He’s probably gonna make you pay”: Kane Williamson rues Jos Buttler’s drop catch after losing ICC T20 World Cup match vs England England defeated New Zealand by 20 runs at the Gabba to make a strong step towards the semi-final of the tournament.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AFG vs SL Brisbane pitch report: Pitch report of The Gabba Brisbane for tomorrow match</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/afg-vs-sl-brisbane-pitch-report-pitch-report-of-the-gabba-brisbane-for-tom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 09:50:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/afg-vs-sl-brisbane-pitch-report-pitch-report-of-the-gabba-brisbane-for-tom/</guid>
      <description>AFG vs SL Brisbane pitch report: Pitch report of The Gabba Brisbane for tomorrow match The Gabba in Brisbane will be hosting the ICC T20 World Cup 2022 match between Sri Lanka and Afghanistan on 1 November 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brisbane Cricket Ground weather forecast November 1: Weather report in Gabba Brisbane tomorrow matches</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/brisbane-cricket-ground-weather-forecast-november-1-weather-report-in-gabb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 09:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/brisbane-cricket-ground-weather-forecast-november-1-weather-report-in-gabb/</guid>
      <description>Brisbane Cricket Ground weather forecast November 1: Weather report in Gabba Brisbane tomorrow matches Brisbane might become another venue to witness a rain-affected match in the ongoing eighth edition of ICC T20 World Cup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Bhai kya badla le liya teri team ne”: Virender Sehwag terms Zimbabwe win vs Pakistan as great revenge for fake Mr Bean</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bhai-kya-badla-le-liya-teri-team-ne-virender-sehwag-terms-zimbabwe-w/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bhai-kya-badla-le-liya-teri-team-ne-virender-sehwag-terms-zimbabwe-w/</guid>
      <description>“Bhai kya badla le liya teri team ne”: Virender Sehwag terms Zimbabwe win vs Pakistan as great revenge for fake Mr Bean Virender Sehwag terms Zimbabwe win: The former Indian batter further added meat to the Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Pakistan out of T20 World Cup: Can Pakistan qualify for ICC T20 World Cup 2022 semi final?</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/is-pakistan-out-of-t20-world-cup-can-pakistan-qualify-for-icc-t20-world-cu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 15:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/is-pakistan-out-of-t20-world-cup-can-pakistan-qualify-for-icc-t20-world-cu/</guid>
      <description>Is Pakistan out of T20 World Cup: Can Pakistan qualify for ICC T20 World Cup 2022 semi final?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India vs Netherlands T20 head to head records: IND vs NED head to head in T20 history</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-vs-netherlands-t20-head-to-head-records-ind-vs-ned-head-to-head-in-t/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 12:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-vs-netherlands-t20-head-to-head-records-ind-vs-ned-head-to-head-in-t/</guid>
      <description>India vs Netherlands T20 head to head records: IND vs NED head to head in T20 history India vs Netherlands T20 head to head: The SportsRush presents for you the Head to Head statistics for IND vs NED T20 World Cup match.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“No excuses at all”: Michael Vaughan criticizes England for not being good enough vs Ireland at the MCG</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/no-excuses-at-all-michael-vaughan-criticizes-england-for-not-being-g/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 08:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/no-excuses-at-all-michael-vaughan-criticizes-england-for-not-being-g/</guid>
      <description>“No excuses at all”: Michael Vaughan criticizes England for not being good enough vs Ireland at the MCG Former English captain Michael Vaughan has criticized England for their performance against Ireland in ICC T20 World Cup 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Hardik wants to play all the games”: Paras Mhambrey confirms India won’t rest Hardik Pandya or other key players for Super 12 match vs Netherlands</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hardik-wants-to-play-all-the-games-paras-mhambrey-confirms-india-won/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 07:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/hardik-wants-to-play-all-the-games-paras-mhambrey-confirms-india-won/</guid>
      <description>“Hardik wants to play all the games”: Paras Mhambrey confirms India won’t rest Hardik Pandya or other key players for Super 12 match vs Netherlands India’s bowling coach Paras Mhambrey has said that Hardik Pandya wants to play all the game and he won’t be rested against the Netherlands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Wow, Marcus Stoinis you beauty”: Shoaib Akhtar compliments Marcus Stoinis for scoring fastest 50 in T20 international among Australian batters</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/wow-marcus-stoinis-you-beauty-shoaib-akhtar-compliments-marcus-stoi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/wow-marcus-stoinis-you-beauty-shoaib-akhtar-compliments-marcus-stoi/</guid>
      <description>“Wow, Marcus Stoinis you beauty”: Shoaib Akhtar compliments Marcus Stoinis for scoring fastest 50 in T20 international among Australian batters Shoaib Akhtar compliments Marcus Stoinis: The former Pakistani speedster expressed approval of the Australian all-rounder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“We must have a Bonus Point”: Aakash Chopra propounds rule change in T20 World Cup points system</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/we-must-have-a-bonus-point-aakash-chopra-propounds-rule-change-in-t2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 11:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/we-must-have-a-bonus-point-aakash-chopra-propounds-rule-change-in-t2/</guid>
      <description>“We must have a Bonus Point”: Aakash Chopra propounds rule change in T20 World Cup points system Aakash Chopra propounds rule change: The former Indian batter proposed a new rule with respect to points system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SA vs ZIM pitch report Blundstone Arena: Hobart pitch report for South Africa vs Zimbabwe T20 World Cup match</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sa-vs-zim-pitch-report-blundstone-arena-hobart-pitch-report-for-south-afri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 17:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sa-vs-zim-pitch-report-blundstone-arena-hobart-pitch-report-for-south-afri/</guid>
      <description>SA vs ZIM pitch report Blundstone Arena: Hobart pitch report for South Africa vs Zimbabwe T20 World Cup match SA vs ZIM pitch report Blundstone Arena: The venue will host the sixth ‘Super 12’ stage match of the ongoing T20 World Cup 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
