<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NE News,Assam News on TechnoStreet</title>
    <link>https://technostreet.github.io/tags/ne-newsassam-news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NE News,Assam News on TechnoStreet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 07:24:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://technostreet.github.io/tags/ne-newsassam-news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Birth anniversary of Sri Guru Nanak Dev celebrated in Udalguri district</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/birth-anniversary-of-sri-guru-nanak-dev-celebrated-in-udalguri-district/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 07:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/birth-anniversary-of-sri-guru-nanak-dev-celebrated-in-udalguri-district/</guid>
      <description>Birth anniversary of Sri Guru Nanak Dev celebrated in Udalguri district Along with the rest of the State, Guru Nanak Jayanti was also celebrated with religious fervour here at Sri Guru Singh Sabha Gurudwara in Tangla town of Udalguri district</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABSU expresses resentment over decision to abolish 8,000 regular vacant posts</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/absu-expresses-resentment-over-decision-to-abolish-8000-regular-vacant-pos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 07:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/absu-expresses-resentment-over-decision-to-abolish-8000-regular-vacant-pos/</guid>
      <description>ABSU expresses resentment over decision to abolish 8,000 regular vacant posts The decision for abolishing 8,000 regular vacant posts in elementary education will destroy the very spirit of the vernacular medium, hamper the teaching-learning process and will close the way for permanent recruitment against vacant positions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deori Autonomous Council Poll: Polling peaceful in Thowra constituency</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/deori-autonomous-council-poll-polling-peaceful-in-thowra-constituency/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 07:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/deori-autonomous-council-poll-polling-peaceful-in-thowra-constituency/</guid>
      <description>Deori Autonomous Council Poll: Polling peaceful in Thowra constituency The Deori Autonomous Council Poll was held in 5 no Tengapani Constituency, 6 no Kotiori Constituency and 7 no Rajabari Constituency of Thowra Constituency</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vigilance Awareness Week organized by Dibrugarh Airport management</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/vigilance-awareness-week-organized-by-dibrugarh-airport-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 07:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/vigilance-awareness-week-organized-by-dibrugarh-airport-management/</guid>
      <description>Vigilance Awareness Week organized by Dibrugarh Airport management This year Vigilance Awareness Week was organized by Dibrugarh Airport management between October 31 to November 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shops gutted in devastating fire at Jagiroad town</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/shops-gutted-in-devastating-fire-at-jagiroad-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 07:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/shops-gutted-in-devastating-fire-at-jagiroad-town/</guid>
      <description>Shops gutted in devastating fire at Jagiroad town A devastating fire broke out at Jagiroad town in the wee hours of Thursday causing heavy loss to property.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Small boat carrying school students capsizes, no casualty reported in Nagaon district</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/small-boat-carrying-school-students-capsizes-no-casualty-reported-in-nagao/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 07:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/small-boat-carrying-school-students-capsizes-no-casualty-reported-in-nagao/</guid>
      <description>Small boat carrying school students capsizes, no casualty reported in Nagaon district Hundreds of school students had a narrow escape from a possible tragic incident after a local small boat carrying the students capsized in a stream of the mighty Brahmaputra near Sutirpar of the greater Juria in the Nagaon district.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental health programme held at Sonitpur</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mental-health-programme-held-at-sonitpur/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 07:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mental-health-programme-held-at-sonitpur/</guid>
      <description>Mental health programme held at Sonitpur A lecture on mental health problems was organized by the District Mental Health Programme, Sonitpur at Tyagbir Hem Baruah College on Thursday in collaboration with Women Cell, THB College.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goalpara DC calls for non-health sector involvement to eradicate Tuberculosis</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/goalpara-dc-calls-for-non-health-sector-involvement-to-eradicate-tuberculos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 07:21:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/goalpara-dc-calls-for-non-health-sector-involvement-to-eradicate-tuberculos/</guid>
      <description>Goalpara DC calls for non-health sector involvement to eradicate Tuberculosis DC of Goalpara Khanindra Choudhury has called for the non-health sector involvement in order to eradicate the Tuberculosis menace from society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minister Ranjit Kumar Dass distributes cheques at Dhubri District Library Auditorium</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/minister-ranjit-kumar-dass-distributes-cheques-at-dhubri-district-library-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 07:18:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/minister-ranjit-kumar-dass-distributes-cheques-at-dhubri-district-library-a/</guid>
      <description>Minister Ranjit Kumar Dass distributes cheques at Dhubri District Library Auditorium Minister of Panchayat and Rural Development, Food and Civil Supplies Ranjit Kumar Dass distributed the second phase of cheques</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oil and Natural Gas Corporation Ltd. to donate 9 advanced ambulances</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oil-and-natural-gas-corporation-ltd-to-donate-9-advanced-ambulances/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 07:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oil-and-natural-gas-corporation-ltd-to-donate-9-advanced-ambulances/</guid>
      <description>Oil and Natural Gas Corporation Ltd. to donate 9 advanced ambulances ONGC is enhancing access to emergency medical services by adding nine advanced life saving ambulances (ADLS) to the existing logistics (ambulance) fleet of Assam state machinery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8,000 litres of stolen condensate oil seized; 4 arrested in Dibrugarh</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/8000-litres-of-stolen-condensate-oil-seized-4-arrested-in-dibrugarh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 07:09:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/8000-litres-of-stolen-condensate-oil-seized-4-arrested-in-dibrugarh/</guid>
      <description>8,000 litres of stolen condensate oil seized; 4 arrested in Dibrugarh In a crackdown against oil thieves, Dibrugarh police seized 8,000 litres of stolen condensate oil from an oil tanker (AS-05-B-6685) near the Bogibeel bridge in Dibrugarh early on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Body recovered from Sarengiya Borduwa Bill</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/body-recovered-from-sarengiya-borduwa-bill/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 07:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/body-recovered-from-sarengiya-borduwa-bill/</guid>
      <description>Body recovered from Sarengiya Borduwa Bill A floating body of one Dilip Darjee (34), a resident of Sarke Aati, Bokabil under Sootea Police Station was recovered from Sarengiya Borduwa Bill</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vigilance Awareness Week observed in Dibrugarh</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/vigilance-awareness-week-observed-in-dibrugarh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 06:57:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/vigilance-awareness-week-observed-in-dibrugarh/</guid>
      <description>Vigilance Awareness Week observed in Dibrugarh Vigilance Awareness Week is observed annually, to create awareness in the minds of every individual about leading a life with absolute integrity and in that process, emphasize the need to combat corruption in public life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huge cache of arms and ammunition recovered in Udalguri district</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/huge-cache-of-arms-and-ammunition-recovered-in-udalguri-district/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 06:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/huge-cache-of-arms-and-ammunition-recovered-in-udalguri-district/</guid>
      <description>Huge cache of arms and ammunition recovered in Udalguri district In a major feat of Assam Police, the police forces recovered a huge cache of arms and ammunitions</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheques under AMFIRS distributed among 9,010 borrowers of Lakhimpur district</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cheques-under-amfirs-distributed-among-9010-borrowers-of-lakhimpur-distric/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 05:09:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cheques-under-amfirs-distributed-among-9010-borrowers-of-lakhimpur-distric/</guid>
      <description>Cheques under AMFIRS distributed among 9,010 borrowers of Lakhimpur district Cheques under Assam Micro-Finance Incentive and Relief Scheme (AMFIRS) - 2021-2022, Category-II were distributed among the borrowers of microfinance loans in Lakhimpur district</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chhath Puja celebrated in Hojai district</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/chhath-puja-celebrated-in-hojai-district/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 05:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/chhath-puja-celebrated-in-hojai-district/</guid>
      <description>Chhath Puja celebrated in Hojai district In different areas of the Hojai district, devotees observed fasting on the third day of Chhath Puja.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cancer awareness programme on the use of tobacco held in Assam&#39;s Lakhimpur</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cancer-awareness-programme-on-the-use-of-tobacco-held-in-assams-lakhimpur/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 10:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cancer-awareness-programme-on-the-use-of-tobacco-held-in-assams-lakhimpur/</guid>
      <description>Cancer awareness programme on the use of tobacco held in Assam&amp;rsquo;s Lakhimpur In association with Assam Cancer Care Foundation (ACCF), organized an awareness programme on the use of tobacco and its relation with cancer and breast cancer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheques given to 4,668 Micro-Finance Incentive and Relief Scheme (AMFIRS) borrowers in Dhemaji district</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cheques-given-to-4668-micro-finance-incentive-and-relief-scheme-amfirs-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 09:53:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/cheques-given-to-4668-micro-finance-incentive-and-relief-scheme-amfirs-b/</guid>
      <description>Cheques given to 4,668 Micro-Finance Incentive and Relief Scheme (AMFIRS) borrowers in Dhemaji district The distribution of the cheques under the AMFIRS - 2021-2022, Category-II was formally inaugurated by Sanjay Kishan, the Minister for Tea Tribes and Labour Welfare</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Series of activities for cleaning and disposal matters conducted in Krishi Vigyan Kendra (KVK) Dibrugarh</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/series-of-activities-for-cleaning-and-disposal-matters-conducted-in-krishi-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 07:39:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/series-of-activities-for-cleaning-and-disposal-matters-conducted-in-krishi-/</guid>
      <description>Series of activities for cleaning and disposal matters conducted in Krishi Vigyan Kendra (KVK) Dibrugarh The main aim is to create a good work environment and work efficiently for the greater interest of delivering good services to public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orientation programme on National Education Policy 2020 held at Assam&#39;s Biswanath College of Education</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/orientation-programme-on-national-education-policy-2020-held-at-assams-bis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 07:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/orientation-programme-on-national-education-policy-2020-held-at-assams-bis/</guid>
      <description>Orientation programme on National Education Policy 2020 held at Assam&amp;rsquo;s Biswanath College of Education The programme was hosted by A Handique, coordinator of CTEF, Biswanath.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legendary Assamese cine artiste Nipon Goswami&#39;s death condoled</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/legendary-assamese-cine-artiste-nipon-goswamis-death-condoled/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 07:37:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/legendary-assamese-cine-artiste-nipon-goswamis-death-condoled/</guid>
      <description>Legendary Assamese cine artiste Nipon Goswami&amp;rsquo;s death condoled ANSS, in a press statement issued by Durga Khatiara, president, Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vermicompost from banana leaves in Krishi Vigyan Kendra, Tinsukia</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/vermicompost-from-banana-leaves-in-krishi-vigyan-kendra-tinsukia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 07:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/vermicompost-from-banana-leaves-in-krishi-vigyan-kendra-tinsukia/</guid>
      <description>Vermicompost from banana leaves in Krishi Vigyan Kendra, Tinsukia KVK, Tinsukia as a part of Swachhata Campaign under SAP initiated a novel plan to recycle banana leaves for manufacturing of vermicompost during post-Diwali days at the kendra’s production unit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Businessman shot at by miscreants in Udalguri district</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/businessman-shot-at-by-miscreants-in-udalguri-district/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:13:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/businessman-shot-at-by-miscreants-in-udalguri-district/</guid>
      <description>Businessman shot at by miscreants in Udalguri district Amidst the Diwali celebration, unidentified masked miscreants shot businessman Gautam Baruah and his wife Bobita Baruah at the latter&#39;s residence in the Jalukbari locality of Tangla town</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DAC election: 19 candidates to contest in 5 constituencies of Dhemaji</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dac-election-19-candidates-to-contest-in-5-constituencies-of-dhemaji/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 09:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dac-election-19-candidates-to-contest-in-5-constituencies-of-dhemaji/</guid>
      <description>DAC election: 19 candidates to contest in 5 constituencies of Dhemaji With October 25 being the last date for the withdrawal of the nomination papers for the Deori Autonomous Council (DAC) Election, 2022</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACS candidates felicitated in Mangaldai</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/acs-candidates-felicitated-in-mangaldai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 07:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/acs-candidates-felicitated-in-mangaldai/</guid>
      <description>ACS candidates felicitated in Mangaldai Various social organizations of Mangaldai including the premier media organization, MMC have greeted and congratulated Dr Jebin Gulnar, the 3rd rank holder in the ACS examination results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overflowing water submerges villages under Kampur revenue circle</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/overflowing-water-submerges-villages-under-kampur-revenue-circle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 06:06:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/overflowing-water-submerges-villages-under-kampur-revenue-circle/</guid>
      <description>Overflowing water submerges villages under Kampur revenue circle Due to the incessant rains across the State, Karbi Langpi Hydro Electric Power Project released additional water through four sluice gates of the big dam of the power project</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9 youths of Sonitpur bring laurels by clearing APSC exam</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/9-youths-of-sonitpur-bring-laurels-by-clearing-apsc-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/9-youths-of-sonitpur-bring-laurels-by-clearing-apsc-exam/</guid>
      <description>9 youths of Sonitpur bring laurels by clearing APSC exam A total of nine candidates in the Sonitpur district have brought laurels to the district by achieving different ranks in the recently declared results of the APSC CCE 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
