<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business on TechnoStreet</title>
    <link>https://technostreet.github.io/tags/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business on TechnoStreet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 05:04:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://technostreet.github.io/tags/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sah Polymers IPO: साह पॉलीमर्स की स्टॉक एक्सचेंज पर बंपर लिस्टिंग, 31 फीसदी के प्रीमियम पर लिस्ट हुआ शेयर</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sah-polymers-ipo-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 05:04:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sah-polymers-ipo-/</guid>
      <description>Sah Polymers IPO: साह पॉलीमर्स की स्टॉक एक्सचेंज पर बंपर लिस्टिंग, 31 फीसदी के प्रीमियम पर लिस्ट हुआ शेयर Sah Polymers IPO Listing: साह पॉलीमर्स (Sah Polymers) की स्टॉक एक्सचेंज पर शानदार लिस्टिंग हुई है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tour Package: कम पैसों में करना चाहते हैं दुबई की सैर तो IRCTC टूर पैकेज में कराएं बुकिंग, मिलेगी रहने खाने की सुविधा</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tour-package-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 04:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/tour-package-/</guid>
      <description>Tour Package: कम पैसों में करना चाहते हैं दुबई की सैर तो IRCTC टूर पैकेज में कराएं बुकिंग, मिलेगी रहने खाने की सुविधा abplive</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FD Rate Hike: Axis बैंक के साथ ही इस सरकारी बैंक ने भी बढ़ाई FD पर अपनी ब्याज दर, यहां जानें ग्राहकों को कितना मिल रहा फायदा</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/fd-rate-hike-axis-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 04:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/fd-rate-hike-axis-/</guid>
      <description>FD Rate Hike: Axis बैंक के साथ ही इस सरकारी बैंक ने भी बढ़ाई FD पर अपनी ब्याज दर, यहां जानें ग्राहकों को कितना मिल रहा फायदा Fixed Deposit Rates: साल 2022 में महंगाई ने आम लोगों की कमर तोड़ रखी थी.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock Market Opening: मामूली तेजी के साथ खुले भारतीय शेयर बाजार, आईटी स्टॉक्स में निवेशकों की खरीदारी</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/stock-market-opening-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 03:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/stock-market-opening-/</guid>
      <description>Stock Market Opening: मामूली तेजी के साथ खुले भारतीय शेयर बाजार, आईटी स्टॉक्स में निवेशकों की खरीदारी Stock Market Opening On 12th January 2023: भारतीय शेयर बाजार में मामूली तेजी के साथ कारोबार की शुरुआत हुई है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BharatPe CEO Suhail Sameer, who had fallen out with former co-founder Ashneer Grover, quits</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bharatpe-ceo-suhail-sameer-who-had-fallen-out-with-former-co-founder-ashne/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 06:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bharatpe-ceo-suhail-sameer-who-had-fallen-out-with-former-co-founder-ashne/</guid>
      <description>BharatPe CEO Suhail Sameer, who had fallen out with former co-founder Ashneer Grover, quits BharatPe announced in a statement that CEO Suhail Sameer &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold rates today stable and silver hikes in Hyderabad, Bangalore, Kerala, Visakhapatnam - 28 December 2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-rates-today-stable-and-silver-hikes-in-hyderabad-bangalore-kerala-v/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 03:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-rates-today-stable-and-silver-hikes-in-hyderabad-bangalore-kerala-v/</guid>
      <description>Gold rates today stable and silver hikes in Hyderabad, Bangalore, Kerala, Visakhapatnam - 28 December 2022 Gold rates today, 28 December 2022 : Gold rate today in Hyderabad is at Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Loan : इन 6 तरीकों से कम करें होम लोन की ईएमआई, जानें क्या कहते हैं एक्सपर्ट?</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/home-loan-6-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 07:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/home-loan-6-/</guid>
      <description>Home Loan : इन 6 तरीकों से कम करें होम लोन की ईएमआई, जानें क्या कहते हैं एक्सपर्ट?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>कोरोना से सहमा बाजार, 60,000 पर आया सेंसेक्स, केवल फॉर्मा सेक्टर में दिख रहा दम</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-60000-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 05:53:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-60000-/</guid>
      <description>कोरोना से सहमा बाजार, 60,000 पर आया सेंसेक्स, केवल फॉर्मा सेक्टर में दिख रहा दम बाजार में तेज गिरावट के बीच भी फार्मा और हेल्थकेयर सेक्टर बढ़त के साथ कारोबार कर रहा है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold Silver Price Today: सोने-चांदी में रौनक लौटी, जानें अपने शहर का ताजा भाव</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-silver-price-today-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 07:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-silver-price-today-/</guid>
      <description>Gold Silver Price Today: सोने-चांदी में रौनक लौटी, जानें अपने शहर का ताजा भाव Gold Silver Price: 999 कैरेट वाला सोना 54180 के आसपास खुला, वहीं 999 चांदी 66444 के भाव पर आज कारोबार कर रही हैं.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oilmeals Exports: भारत के खली निर्यात में जबरदस्त इजाफा! अप्रैल-नवंबर के बीच Export हुआ 23.92 लाख टन के पार</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oilmeals-exports-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 06:59:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/oilmeals-exports-/</guid>
      <description>Oilmeals Exports: भारत के खली निर्यात में जबरदस्त इजाफा! अप्रैल-नवंबर के बीच Export हुआ 23.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Centre cuts windfall tax on domestic crude oil</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/centre-cuts-windfall-tax-on-domestic-crude-oil/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 07:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/centre-cuts-windfall-tax-on-domestic-crude-oil/</guid>
      <description>Centre cuts windfall tax on domestic crude oil The government has also cut the rate on export of diesel to Rs 5 per litre from Rs 8 per litre</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter picks three colours for account verification; details here</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-picks-three-colours-for-account-verification-details-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 04:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-picks-three-colours-for-account-verification-details-here/</guid>
      <description>Twitter picks three colours for account verification; details here Twitter account verification colour: Account verification procedure of twitter has been finally launched.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markets climb in early trade</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/markets-climb-in-early-trade/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 04:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/markets-climb-in-early-trade/</guid>
      <description>Markets climb in early trade Mumbai: Benchmark indices climbed in early trade Tuesday amid firm global market trends and as retail inflation dipped below the RBI’s upper tolerance level of 6 per cent for the first time in 11 months in November.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBI Penalty on Banks: रिजर्व बैंक ने इन 13 बैंकों पर लगाया भारी जुर्माना, जानिए क्या रही वजह</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-penalty-on-banks-13-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 04:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-penalty-on-banks-13-/</guid>
      <description>RBI Penalty on Banks: रिजर्व बैंक ने इन 13 बैंकों पर लगाया भारी जुर्माना, जानिए क्या रही वजह RBI Penalty on Banks: रिजर्व बैंक ऑफ इंडिया (RBI Impose Penalty) ने देश के 13 कॉर्पोरेटिव बैंकों पर जुर्माना लगाया है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vehicle Scrappage Policy: अब 15 साल पुरानी गाड़ियां नहीं चला पाएंगे सरकारी कर्मचारी, वित्त मंत्रालय ने जारी किया आदेश</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/vehicle-scrappage-policy-15-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 04:39:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/vehicle-scrappage-policy-15-/</guid>
      <description>Vehicle Scrappage Policy: अब 15 साल पुरानी गाड़ियां नहीं चला पाएंगे सरकारी कर्मचारी, वित्त मंत्रालय ने जारी किया आदेश Vehicle Scrappage Policy: केंद्र की मोदी सरकार ने 15 साल से अधिक पुरानी गाड़ी के लिए एक बड़ा फैसला किया है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maharashtra government to invest Rs 36,000 crore in textile industry; generate 10 lakh jobs</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/maharashtra-government-to-invest-rs-36000-crore-in-textile-industry-gener/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 10:09:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/maharashtra-government-to-invest-rs-36000-crore-in-textile-industry-gener/</guid>
      <description>Maharashtra government to invest Rs 36,000 crore in textile industry; generate 10 lakh jobs Maharashtra government to invest Rs 36,000 crore in textile industry; generate 10 lakh jobs</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBI hikes benchmark lending rate by 35 basis points to tame inflation</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-hikes-benchmark-lending-rate-by-35-basis-points-to-tame-inflation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 05:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-hikes-benchmark-lending-rate-by-35-basis-points-to-tame-inflation/</guid>
      <description>RBI hikes benchmark lending rate by 35 basis points to tame inflation This is the fifth consecutive rate hike after a 40 basis points increase in May and 50 basis points hike each in June, August and September</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overdraft Facility: Check how to borrow money when you have zero funds in your bank account</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/overdraft-facility-check-how-to-borrow-money-when-you-have-zero-funds-in-y/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 06:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/overdraft-facility-check-how-to-borrow-money-when-you-have-zero-funds-in-y/</guid>
      <description>Overdraft Facility: Check how to borrow money when you have zero funds in your bank account Overdraft Facility: Check how to borrow money when you have zero funds in your bank account</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBI 0.35% तक बढ़ाएगा ब्याज दरें, एक्सपर्ट्स ने महंगाई में कमी को बताया वजह</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-035-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 14:35:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rbi-035-/</guid>
      <description>RBI 0.35% तक बढ़ाएगा ब्याज दरें, एक्सपर्ट्स ने महंगाई में कमी को बताया वजह विशेषज्ञों का अनुमान है कि ब्याज दरों में लगातार तीन बार 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor के VC Vikram Kirloskar का निधन, ये है मौत की वजह</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/toyota-kirloskar-motor-vc-vikram-kirloskar-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 02:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/toyota-kirloskar-motor-vc-vikram-kirloskar-/</guid>
      <description>Toyota Kirloskar Motor के VC Vikram Kirloskar का निधन, ये है मौत की वजह Toyota Kirloskar Motor के उपाध्यक्ष Vikram S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dharmaj Crop Guard IPO Opens Today: Price Band, GMP, Listing; Key Details Investors Should Know</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dharmaj-crop-guard-ipo-opens-today-price-band-gmp-listing-key-details-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 04:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dharmaj-crop-guard-ipo-opens-today-price-band-gmp-listing-key-details-i/</guid>
      <description>Dharmaj Crop Guard IPO Opens Today: Price Band, GMP, Listing; Key Details Investors Should Know Dharmaj Crop Guard IPO will remain open for public subscription for three days between November 28 and 30; the price band has been fixed at Rs 216-237 per share</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviews On Amazon, Flipkart: Govt Guidelines Come Into Effect; What Are These, Compliance?</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/reviews-on-amazon-flipkart-govt-guidelines-come-into-effect-what-are-the/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 05:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/reviews-on-amazon-flipkart-govt-guidelines-come-into-effect-what-are-the/</guid>
      <description>Reviews On Amazon, Flipkart: Govt Guidelines Come Into Effect; What Are These, Compliance?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Central KYC के जरिए अब घर बैठे खोल सकेंगे NPS अकाउंट, करना होगा ये काम</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/central-kyc-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 02:42:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/central-kyc-/</guid>
      <description>Central KYC के जरिए अब घर बैठे खोल सकेंगे NPS अकाउंट, करना होगा ये काम CKYCR का उद्देश्य वित्तीय सेवा प्रदाताओं के खाते खोलने के तरीके को और आसान बनाना है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five Star Business Finance Shares List At 5% Discount to IPO Price; Buy, Sell or Hold?</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/five-star-business-finance-shares-list-at-5-discount-to-ipo-price-buy-se/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 04:45:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/five-star-business-finance-shares-list-at-5-discount-to-ipo-price-buy-se/</guid>
      <description>Five Star Business Finance Shares List At 5% Discount to IPO Price; Buy, Sell or Hold?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New ETF from ICICI Prudential AMC enables you to benefit from growing financial services; details here</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-etf-from-icici-prudential-amc-enables-you-to-benefit-from-growing-finan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 06:29:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/new-etf-from-icici-prudential-amc-enables-you-to-benefit-from-growing-finan/</guid>
      <description>New ETF from ICICI Prudential AMC enables you to benefit from growing financial services; details here New ETF from ICICI Prudential AMC enables you to benefit from growing financial services; details here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thane: Adulteration detected in 27% cooking oil from 4 firms by FDA</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/thane-adulteration-detected-in-27-cooking-oil-from-4-firms-by-fda/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 06:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/thane-adulteration-detected-in-27-cooking-oil-from-4-firms-by-fda/</guid>
      <description>Thane: Adulteration detected in 27% cooking oil from 4 firms by FDA At least 27 per cent of the 56 samples of cooking oil and other food items collected from four companies in Maharashtra&#39;s Thane district have been found adulterated or with false claims, the Food and Drug Administration (FDA) officials said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India A Fastest-Growing Major Economy, To Be Among Top-3 Economic Powers In 10-15 Years: Nirmala Sitharaman</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-a-fastest-growing-major-economy-to-be-among-top-3-economic-powers-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 06:35:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/india-a-fastest-growing-major-economy-to-be-among-top-3-economic-powers-in/</guid>
      <description>India A Fastest-Growing Major Economy, To Be Among Top-3 Economic Powers In 10-15 Years: Nirmala Sitharaman The finance minister says global economic outlook remains challenging and the Indian economy is not insulated from the impact of global economic developments</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petrol, diesel prices today in Hyderabad, Delhi, Chennai and Mumbai on 07 November 2022, check here</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-diesel-prices-today-in-hyderabad-delhi-chennai-and-mumbai-on-07-n/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 05:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-diesel-prices-today-in-hyderabad-delhi-chennai-and-mumbai-on-07-n/</guid>
      <description>Petrol, diesel prices today in Hyderabad, Delhi, Chennai and Mumbai on 07 November 2022, check here Petrol and Diesel prices today, 07 November 2022: Petrol price in Hyderabad is Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petrol, diesel prices today in Hyderabad, Delhi, Chennai and Mumbai on 06 November 2022, check here</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-diesel-prices-today-in-hyderabad-delhi-chennai-and-mumbai-on-06-n/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 04:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-diesel-prices-today-in-hyderabad-delhi-chennai-and-mumbai-on-06-n/</guid>
      <description>Petrol, diesel prices today in Hyderabad, Delhi, Chennai and Mumbai on 06 November 2022, check here Petrol and Diesel prices today, 06 November 2022: Petrol price in Hyderabad is Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold rates today in Delhi, Chennai, Kolkata, Mumbai - 06 November 2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-rates-today-in-delhi-chennai-kolkata-mumbai-06-november-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 04:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-rates-today-in-delhi-chennai-kolkata-mumbai-06-november-2022/</guid>
      <description>Gold rates today in Delhi, Chennai, Kolkata, Mumbai - 06 November 2022 Gold rates today, 06 November 2022: Gold rates in Delhi per 10 grams of 22 carats is at Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter ‘sued by staff’ as layoffs begin; Sizewell new nuclear plant under review – business live</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-sued-by-staff-as-layoffs-begin-sizewell-new-nuclear-plant-un/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 07:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/twitter-sued-by-staff-as-layoffs-begin-sizewell-new-nuclear-plant-un/</guid>
      <description>Twitter ‘sued by staff’ as layoffs begin; Sizewell new nuclear plant under review – business live Rolling coverage of the latest economic and financial newsElon Musk announces Twitter mass layoffs to begin FridayThe Sizewell C nuclear power plant in Suffolk is reportedly under review as the Government looks to cut spending to fill the UK’s fiscal ‘black hole’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold rates today in Delhi, Chennai, Kolkata, Mumbai - 04 November 2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-rates-today-in-delhi-chennai-kolkata-mumbai-04-november-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 04:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-rates-today-in-delhi-chennai-kolkata-mumbai-04-november-2022/</guid>
      <description>Gold rates today in Delhi, Chennai, Kolkata, Mumbai - 04 November 2022 Gold rates today, 04 November 2022: Gold rates in Delhi per 10 grams of 22 carats is at Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mining giant Glencore flew cash bribes to Africa via private jet, UK court hears</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mining-giant-glencore-flew-cash-bribes-to-africa-via-private-jet-uk-court-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 16:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/mining-giant-glencore-flew-cash-bribes-to-africa-via-private-jet-uk-court-/</guid>
      <description>Mining giant Glencore flew cash bribes to Africa via private jet, UK court hears Corruption at FTSE 100 firm described as endemic at sentence hearingGlencore flew cash bribes to officials in Africa via private jet amid “endemic” corruption within the mining company, a London court has heard, in sentencing of the first ever UK corporate conviction on charges of bribing another person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inflation in UK shops hits record high as food prices soar – business live</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/inflation-in-uk-shops-hits-record-high-as-food-prices-soar-business-liv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 07:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/inflation-in-uk-shops-hits-record-high-as-food-prices-soar-business-liv/</guid>
      <description>Inflation in UK shops hits record high as food prices soar – business live Rolling coverage of the latest economic and financial news, as food prices rise at fastest rate since at least 2005 Government tests energy blackout emergency plans as supply fears growSupermarkets need to offer good value this Christmas to win business from cash-strapped customers, adds Mike Watkins, Head of Retailer and Business Insight at NielsenIQ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank Holidays in November 2022: Banks in Telangana to be closed for 7 days</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bank-holidays-in-november-2022-banks-in-telangana-to-be-closed-for-7-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 05:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bank-holidays-in-november-2022-banks-in-telangana-to-be-closed-for-7-days/</guid>
      <description>Bank Holidays in November 2022: Banks in Telangana to be closed for 7 days In November 2022, all the banks across Telangana will remain closed for seven days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petrol, diesel prices today in Hyderabad, Delhi, Chennai and Mumbai on 31 October 2022, check here</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-diesel-prices-today-in-hyderabad-delhi-chennai-and-mumbai-on-31-o/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 05:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-diesel-prices-today-in-hyderabad-delhi-chennai-and-mumbai-on-31-o/</guid>
      <description>Petrol, diesel prices today in Hyderabad, Delhi, Chennai and Mumbai on 31 October 2022, check here Petrol and Diesel prices today, 31 October 2022: Petrol price in Hyderabad is Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T-Hub, MEE School announces Cinepreneur Entrepreneurship Certification course</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/t-hub-mee-school-announces-cinepreneur-entrepreneurship-certification-cour/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/t-hub-mee-school-announces-cinepreneur-entrepreneurship-certification-cour/</guid>
      <description>T-Hub, MEE School announces Cinepreneur Entrepreneurship Certification course Cinepreneur is a Media and Entrepreneurship (M&amp;E) program that imparts module-based learning for media business enthusiasts and aspirants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unilever’s Health Data Shows Junk-Food Metrics Are Up For Debate</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/unilevers-health-data-shows-junk-food-metrics-are-up-for-debate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 07:23:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/unilevers-health-data-shows-junk-food-metrics-are-up-for-debate/</guid>
      <description>Unilever’s Health Data Shows Junk-Food Metrics Are Up For Debate Unilever said Friday it’s now aiming for 85% of its servings to meet its own science-based nutrition criteria by 2028.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musk’s Twitter Roils With Hate Speech As Trolls Test New Limits</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/musks-twitter-roils-with-hate-speech-as-trolls-test-new-limits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 07:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/musks-twitter-roils-with-hate-speech-as-trolls-test-new-limits/</guid>
      <description>Musk’s Twitter Roils With Hate Speech As Trolls Test New Limits Hateful and racist rhetoric swelled on the network as some politicians rejoiced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charting The Global Economy: ECB Boosts Rates; Fed, BOE On Deck</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/charting-the-global-economy-ecb-boosts-rates-fed-boe-on-deck/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 06:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/charting-the-global-economy-ecb-boosts-rates-fed-boe-on-deck/</guid>
      <description>Charting The Global Economy: ECB Boosts Rates; Fed, BOE On Deck Here are some of the charts that appeared this week on the latest developments in the global economy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Slips Below $1 Trillion in Value After Bleak Outlook</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/amazon-slips-below-1-trillion-in-value-after-bleak-outlook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 14:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/amazon-slips-below-1-trillion-in-value-after-bleak-outlook/</guid>
      <description>Amazon Slips Below $1 Trillion in Value After Bleak Outlook The e-commerce giant joins a long list of US companies seeing their market values crumble.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petrol, diesel prices today in Hyderabad, Delhi, Chennai and Mumbai on 28 October 2022, check here</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-diesel-prices-today-in-hyderabad-delhi-chennai-and-mumbai-on-28-o/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-diesel-prices-today-in-hyderabad-delhi-chennai-and-mumbai-on-28-o/</guid>
      <description>Petrol, diesel prices today in Hyderabad, Delhi, Chennai and Mumbai on 28 October 2022, check here Petrol and Diesel prices today, 28 October 2022: Petrol price in Hyderabad is Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota and DC sue Target-owned Shipt delivery service for worker misclassification</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/minnesota-and-dc-sue-target-owned-shipt-delivery-service-for-worker-misclas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/minnesota-and-dc-sue-target-owned-shipt-delivery-service-for-worker-misclas/</guid>
      <description>Minnesota and DC sue Target-owned Shipt delivery service for worker misclassification The Minnesota and District of Columbia attorneys general are suing Target-owned Shipt delivery service over worker misclassification, CBS News has reported.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold rates today in Delhi, Chennai, Kolkata, Mumbai - 28 October 2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-rates-today-in-delhi-chennai-kolkata-mumbai-28-october-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 03:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-rates-today-in-delhi-chennai-kolkata-mumbai-28-october-2022/</guid>
      <description>Gold rates today in Delhi, Chennai, Kolkata, Mumbai - 28 October 2022 Gold rates today, 28 October 2022: Gold rates in Delhi per 10 grams of 22 carats is at Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musk-Twitter Countdown to Close $44 Billion Deal Begins</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/musk-twitter-countdown-to-close-44-billion-deal-begins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 16:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/musk-twitter-countdown-to-close-44-billion-deal-begins/</guid>
      <description>Musk-Twitter Countdown to Close $44 Billion Deal Begins After months of “will they or won’t they,” Elon Musk is running up against a court-ordered deadline to deliver on his promise to buy Twitter Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morgan Stanley Downgrades Meta For First Time As Costs Soar</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/morgan-stanley-downgrades-meta-for-first-time-as-costs-soar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/morgan-stanley-downgrades-meta-for-first-time-as-costs-soar/</guid>
      <description>Morgan Stanley Downgrades Meta For First Time As Costs Soar Shares of the Facebook parent were down 20% in premarket trading after it gave a disappointing quarterly revenue outlook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JSW Steel Expects Margins To Revive After Surprise Loss</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/jsw-steel-expects-margins-to-revive-after-surprise-loss/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 06:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/jsw-steel-expects-margins-to-revive-after-surprise-loss/</guid>
      <description>JSW Steel Expects Margins To Revive After Surprise Loss India’s JSW Steel Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK Bonds Fall After Government Delays Fiscal Plan To Next Month</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/uk-bonds-fall-after-government-delays-fiscal-plan-to-next-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 10:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/uk-bonds-fall-after-government-delays-fiscal-plan-to-next-month/</guid>
      <description>UK Bonds Fall After Government Delays Fiscal Plan To Next Month UK bonds fell as the government delayed its fiscal plan due next week, prolonging uncertainty weighing on the nation’s fragile markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Europe’s Gas Glut to Help Ease Winter LNG Supply Crunch in Asia</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/europes-gas-glut-to-help-ease-winter-lng-supply-crunch-in-asia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 06:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/europes-gas-glut-to-help-ease-winter-lng-supply-crunch-in-asia/</guid>
      <description>Europe’s Gas Glut to Help Ease Winter LNG Supply Crunch in Asia Europe’s near-term natural gas supply glut means more fuel for Asia this winter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Proposes Ban on Borrowing to Fund Cryptocurrency Purchases</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/singapore-proposes-ban-on-borrowing-to-fund-cryptocurrency-purchases/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 06:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/singapore-proposes-ban-on-borrowing-to-fund-cryptocurrency-purchases/</guid>
      <description>Singapore Proposes Ban on Borrowing to Fund Cryptocurrency Purchases Singapore proposed to ban retail investors from borrowing to fund cryptocurrency purchases, moving to tighten regulatory regime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro Stalls In Polls After Ally Clashes With Police</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bolsonaro-stalls-in-polls-after-ally-clashes-with-police/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bolsonaro-stalls-in-polls-after-ally-clashes-with-police/</guid>
      <description>Bolsonaro Stalls In Polls After Ally Clashes With Police Leftist challenger Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva, 76, would take 54% of valid votes, which exclude null and blank ballots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ye’s Antisemitic Rants Wreck Path To Multibillion-Dollar Fortune</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/yes-antisemitic-rants-wreck-path-to-multibillion-dollar-fortune/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/yes-antisemitic-rants-wreck-path-to-multibillion-dollar-fortune/</guid>
      <description>Ye’s Antisemitic Rants Wreck Path To Multibillion-Dollar Fortune The rapper lost out on a lucrative deal with Adidas, which said it would end the Yeezy line after facing blowback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunak’s ‘Dullness Dividend’ Might Not Last</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sunaks-dullness-dividend-might-not-last/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sunaks-dullness-dividend-might-not-last/</guid>
      <description>Sunak’s ‘Dullness Dividend’ Might Not Last Britain’s new prime minister is an improvement over his predecessors — but keeping his promises won’t be easy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Too Much Gas. Europe’s Energy Crisis Takes A Surprise Turn</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/too-much-gas-europes-energy-crisis-takes-a-surprise-turn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 14:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/too-much-gas-europes-energy-crisis-takes-a-surprise-turn/</guid>
      <description>Too Much Gas. Europe’s Energy Crisis Takes A Surprise Turn Europe suddenly has more gas than it can use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rishi Sunak Tells UK Tories To Unite As He Strives To Fix ‘Crisis’</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rishi-sunak-tells-uk-tories-to-unite-as-he-strives-to-fix-crisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/rishi-sunak-tells-uk-tories-to-unite-as-he-strives-to-fix-crisis/</guid>
      <description>Rishi Sunak Tells UK Tories To Unite As He Strives To Fix ‘Crisis’ Rishi Sunak called on his warring Conservative Party to unite as the UK’s incoming prime minister bids to fix the crisis facing the economy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petrol and diesel prices today in Hyderabad, Delhi, Chennai and Mumbai on 24 October 2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-and-diesel-prices-today-in-hyderabad-delhi-chennai-and-mumbai-on-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 04:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/petrol-and-diesel-prices-today-in-hyderabad-delhi-chennai-and-mumbai-on-2/</guid>
      <description>Petrol and diesel prices today in Hyderabad, Delhi, Chennai and Mumbai on 24 October 2022 Petrol and Diesel prices today, 24 October 2022: Petrol price in Hyderabad is Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunak Edges Closer to UK Leadership Prize As Johnson Caves</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sunak-edges-closer-to-uk-leadership-prize-as-johnson-caves/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 04:49:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/sunak-edges-closer-to-uk-leadership-prize-as-johnson-caves/</guid>
      <description>Sunak Edges Closer to UK Leadership Prize As Johnson Caves Boris Johnson pulled out of the race to lead the UK’s ruling Conservative Party and the nation, ending a bid to replace Liz Truss as prime minister.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Striking Benefits Of EHR Software For Healthcare Organizations</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/striking-benefits-of-ehr-software-for-healthcare-organizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 04:46:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/striking-benefits-of-ehr-software-for-healthcare-organizations/</guid>
      <description>Striking Benefits Of EHR Software For Healthcare Organizations Digitizing data is the key to more efficient patient treatment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold rates today in Delhi, Chennai, Kolkata, Mumbai - 24 October 2022</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-rates-today-in-delhi-chennai-kolkata-mumbai-24-october-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 04:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/gold-rates-today-in-delhi-chennai-kolkata-mumbai-24-october-2022/</guid>
      <description>Gold rates today in Delhi, Chennai, Kolkata, Mumbai - 24 October 2022 Gold rates today, 24 October 2022: Gold rates in Delhi per 10 grams of 22 carats is at Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
