<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Uttar Pradesh on TechnoStreet</title>
    <link>https://technostreet.github.io/tags/uttar-pradesh/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Uttar Pradesh on TechnoStreet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 05:15:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://technostreet.github.io/tags/uttar-pradesh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bharat Jodo Yatra resumes journey in Uttar Pradesh</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bharat-jodo-yatra-resumes-journey-in-uttar-pradesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 05:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/bharat-jodo-yatra-resumes-journey-in-uttar-pradesh/</guid>
      <description>Bharat Jodo Yatra resumes journey in Uttar Pradesh Former party chief Rahul Gandhi reached the village from Delhi ahead of the resumption of the march, Congress Uttar Pradesh unit spokesperson Anshu Awasthi said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead body of a girl found on the Eastern Peripheral Highway in Greater Noida, her head crushed, probe initiated</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dead-body-of-a-girl-found-on-the-eastern-peripheral-highway-in-greater-noid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 05:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/dead-body-of-a-girl-found-on-the-eastern-peripheral-highway-in-greater-noid/</guid>
      <description>Dead body of a girl found on the Eastern Peripheral Highway in Greater Noida, her head crushed, probe initiated Initial probe suggests that the girl&#39;s head was smashed to conceal her identity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UP: मोबाइल में गेम खेलने के लिए मां ने डांटा, नाराज होकर बेटे ने लगा ली फांसी</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/up-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 07:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/up-/</guid>
      <description>UP: मोबाइल में गेम खेलने के लिए मां ने डांटा, नाराज होकर बेटे ने लगा ली फांसी परिजनों ने बताया कि बच्चे से मोबाइल को वापस ले लिया गया था.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banda: Jahila Begum sets honey traps for men to extort Rs 40-50 lakhs, had forced one businessman Shailesh to commit suicide, arrested</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/banda-jahila-begum-sets-honey-traps-for-men-to-extort-rs-40-50-lakhs-had-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 05:42:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/banda-jahila-begum-sets-honey-traps-for-men-to-extort-rs-40-50-lakhs-had-/</guid>
      <description>Banda: Jahila Begum sets honey traps for men to extort Rs 40-50 lakhs, had forced one businessman Shailesh to commit suicide, arrested Jahila Begum, a middle-aged woman who honey-trapped people, was caught and detained by Banda police.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHOTO: कोविड की आहट से काशी अलर्ट, अस्सी घाट पर अर्चकों ने मास्क लगाकर की गंगा आरती</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/photo-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 05:38:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/photo-/</guid>
      <description>PHOTO: कोविड की आहट से काशी अलर्ट, अस्सी घाट पर अर्चकों ने मास्क लगाकर की गंगा आरती चीन में कोरोना पांव पसारने के बाद भारत में भी एक बार फिर से दस्तक दे दी है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ghaziabad: 19-year-old hangs herself after Irfan shares her intimate videos online</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ghaziabad-19-year-old-hangs-herself-after-irfan-shares-her-intimate-videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 07:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/ghaziabad-19-year-old-hangs-herself-after-irfan-shares-her-intimate-videos/</guid>
      <description>Ghaziabad: 19-year-old hangs herself after Irfan shares her intimate videos online The accused and his family members are absconding since the suicide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UP के कई जिलों में नकली चांदी के वर्क का कारोबार, दांव पर जिंदगी और प्रशासन बेखबर</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/up-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 15:07:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/up-/</guid>
      <description>UP के कई जिलों में नकली चांदी के वर्क का कारोबार, दांव पर जिंदगी और प्रशासन बेखबर बिजनौर के वरिष्ठ फिजिशियन डॉक्टर नीरज चौधरी के मुताबिक स्टील और एल्युमीनियम से बने नकली चांदी वर्क के लगातार उपयोग करने से एसीडिटी, पेट और आंत संबंधित अल्सर जैसे गंभीर रोग हो जाते हैं.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>वाराणसी आने से पहले PM मोदी ने किया ट्वीट।</title>
      <link>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-pm-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 07:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technostreet.github.io/article/-pm-/</guid>
      <description>वाराणसी आने से पहले PM मोदी ने किया ट्वीट। देवभूमी मीडिया ब्यूरो– बता दें कि काशी तमिल संगमम का शुभारंभ 19 नवंबर को प्रधानमंत्री नरेंद्र मोदी करेंगे। वहीं, आज एक ट्रेन में 210 डेलीगेट्स वाराणसी पहुंचेंगे। प्रधानमंत्री कार्यालय से जारी प्रोटोकॉल के अनुसार पीएम मोदी के बीएचयू के एंफीथियेटर मैदान में आयोजित समारोह में मंच पर पहुंचने के बाद सबसे पहले नादस्वरम से उनका […] The post वाराणसी आने से पहले PM मोदी ने किया ट्वीट। appeared first on Devbhoomi Media.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
